<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0" xmlns:media="http://www.rssboard.org/media-rss" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[波特王好帥[YT+]]]></title>
    <link>http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg</link>
    <image>
      <url>https://yt3.googleusercontent.com/C98TsTDcAjVzrXPHl2cl-nlu2lnML5Q0PKQOzSiC6COBa_4RaicBrIX9XyKkS4CJcwKCuqx5=s900-b50-c-k-c0x008A95A5-no-rj</url>
      <title>波特王好帥[YT+]</title>
      <link>http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg</link>
    </image>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <copyright><![CDATA[波特王好帥[YT+]]]></copyright>
    <itunes:author><![CDATA[波特王好帥[YT+]]]></itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg" target="_blank">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg</a><br />
<br />
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg" target="_blank">https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg</a>
      ]]>
    </itunes:summary>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg" target="_blank">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg</a><br />
<br />
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg" target="_blank">https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsBP1dmKYfcorJ17kfOUTvg</a>
      ]]>
    </description>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name><![CDATA[波特王好帥[YT+]]]></itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://yt3.googleusercontent.com/C98TsTDcAjVzrXPHl2cl-nlu2lnML5Q0PKQOzSiC6COBa_4RaicBrIX9XyKkS4CJcwKCuqx5=s900-b50-c-k-c0x008A95A5-no-rj"/>
<item>
      <title><![CDATA[新錄音檔流出！于朦朧為這件事跟辛奇等人拼命！毛孩也難逃毒手｜粉紅特報148期]]></title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w</link>
      <itunes:title><![CDATA[新錄音檔流出！于朦朧為這件事跟辛奇等人拼命！毛孩也難逃毒手｜粉紅特報148期]]></itunes:title>
      <itunes:author><![CDATA[波特王好帥]]></itunes:author>
      <itunes:summary>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/cu5Gi9mYI0w/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1><ul><li>揭示中共如何利用資訊戰操控輿論，以及其應對敏感事件的慣用策略。</li><li>深入探討于孟龍案的殘酷真相，包括令人髮指的寵物慘遭殺害細節，以及中共權貴的囂張與對公眾的漠視。</li><li>啟發讀者思考在威權體制下，個人尊嚴與反抗的重要性，並見證公眾連署與聲援如何凝聚力量，挑戰國家級的謊言與掩蓋。</li></ul><hr /><h1>摘要</h1><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_0.jpg" /></p> 作為「中國實習生」導師的「波特王」在「粉紅報告」中指出，<strong>于孟龍</strong>案已在全球NGO AVAAZ網站上獲得逾25萬人連署，展現其國際關注度。許多人基於<strong>良知</strong>而非僅是粉絲身份，為被<strong>中共權貴</strong>迫害的于孟龍發聲，質疑當一個擁有2700萬粉絲的明星都能被如此對待時，普通民眾的處境將如何。此案已跨越政治與國界，成為團結<strong>反抗威權</strong>、追求真相的焦點，其持續延燒顯然出乎中共預料。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_160.jpg" /></p> 作者闡述了面對中共<strong>敘事操控</strong>的新策略：過去會避免傳播未經證實的消息，以防中共透過散佈「假事件B」來混淆「真事件A」，然後再「闢謠」B來暗示A也為假，從而稀釋真相。然而，鑒於中共在<strong>于孟龍</strong>案中表現出的公然漠視、權貴的囂張，以及國內嚴酷的言論封鎖，作者決定此次將公開討論所見所聞，即使日後部分消息證實有誤也無妨。此舉旨在保持討論熱度，鼓勵公眾不再懼怕說錯話，甚至反向迫使中共自行「澄清」，以其人之道還治其人之身。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_410.jpg" /></p> 作者透露了一個令人心碎且憤怒的細節：于孟龍生前珍愛的<strong>寵物</strong>，包括柯基犬「福利」和法國鬥牛犬「禍腿」，也慘遭殺害。案情重組顯示，于孟龍被誘騙參加聚會時，帶著「福利」赴約。在遭<strong>中共權貴</strong>施暴時，忠心的「福利」試圖保護主人不斷吠叫，卻被攻擊者當場殺害。後續流出的一段<strong>錄音</strong>中，于孟龍痛苦地哭喊著<strong>寵物</strong>的名字，並誓言反擊。作者強調播放此錄音的目的不僅是為了證明其存在，更是為受害者<strong>于孟龍</strong>保留證據，並揭示事件的殘酷本質。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_660.jpg" /></p> 作者嚴厲批評<strong>中共</strong>對於孟龍案的處理方式：<strong>無屍檢報告</strong>、<strong>無葬禮</strong>、<strong>無立案</strong>，僅草草以「<strong>意外墜樓</strong>」結案，無視所有證據和疑點。他質疑一個高檔社區的<strong>監控攝像頭</strong>「恰好」在關鍵時刻損壞並無錄影的荒謬說法。作者呼籲牆內觀眾應將注意力集中於中共本身編造的「意外」謊言，而非糾結於其他謠言。他強調此案的關鍵意義在於揭露中共政府如何<strong>封鎖資訊</strong>、<strong>迫害于孟龍</strong>，以及<strong>中共權貴</strong>如何壓迫娛樂圈、動用國家機器<strong>消除證據</strong>、<strong>封鎖輿論</strong>。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_14.jpg" /></p> 影片提到，由于孟龍的名字在牆內遭到嚴格審查，許多網民開始使用「<strong>魚</strong>」字作為替代，諷刺的是，這導致大量直播賣魚及漁業相關帳號因「違規」被封禁，顯示<strong>中共</strong>對於孟龍案討論的極度恐懼。即便在中國境內，仍有商場螢幕悄悄播放「我是<strong>于孟龍</strong>」的無聲影像，成為一種無聲的抵抗，以阻止中共的宣傳機器掩埋真相。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_16.jpg" /></p> 作者針對留言區中「為何不當聽話的權貴<strong>奴隸</strong>」的言論進行了反駁。他強調，那樣的生活無異於「被利用、被糟蹋」，如同「牲畜」或「器官銀行」，並非真正的<strong>活著</strong>。<strong>于孟龍</strong>選擇了<strong>有尊嚴</strong>、能<strong>自由選擇</strong>的生活，而非被<strong>中共</strong>操控的<strong>傀儡</strong>。即便付出了沉重代價，他也拒絕屈服，以自己的方式<strong>反抗</strong>，試圖收集證據並<strong>揭露</strong>真相。</p><hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink Report. I’m your mentor for the “Chinese intern” trainees. aka a centrist voter.(ironic trolling). Potter King. A reminder for viewers tuning in for the first time,. you’re watching a show known as. the “Chinese version of Discovery,”. taking you to explore the most authentic China. As of this episode’s cutoff,. on the global NGO. AVAAZ’s website, the. “Justice for Yu Menglong” petition. has surpassed 250,000 signatures. Though a petition may not necessarily reveal the full truth,. without it,. even giving this case. a chance to gain international exposure would be impossible. Many people speak up for Yu Menglong. even if they aren’t his fans. Those willing to join in support. are driven more by their own conscience,. which moves us to act. People see that a kind person. was persecuted by the CCP’s princelings,. while the suspects still roam free,. with not a single person held accountable to this day. Seeing a movie star with 27 million followers in China. be persecuted like this by the CCP,. imagine ordinary people with no fame at all. The wrongful case of Yu Menglong. may not yet be the last straw,. but the chain reactions it has triggered. and the public outrage it has stirred can’t be ignored. I believe this momentum is powerful. From what we’ve seen, those demanding justice for Yu. now span political lines. and even nationalities. It’s people of conscience uniting. to demand a case be opened and justice be served. The fact that this issue has kept burning for so long. is clearly something the CCP didn’t expect. By now, Yu Menglong has become a focal point for pursuing the truth. and a chance to unite against authoritarianism. Viewers are also welcome. to like, comment, and share the video,. stacking the straws one by one together. After watching today’s video, you can also sign the petition online. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">While compiling the facts of Yu’s wrongful case,. I also saw many claims whose authenticity is unclear,. which are honestly hard to verify. I also saw some rumors online. saying this is connected to Xi Jinping’s brother, Xi Yuanping. If I followed my usual way of producing the show,. I wouldn’t air tips that aren’t solid enough yet,. and I wouldn’t mention them on the show. But this time,. I think it’s fine to say it. Let me explain why, for this part. In the past, I’d avoid this with other topics. because sometimes CCP internet trolls. intentionally seed false “dirt,”. and when people begin discussing. topics the CCP doesn’t want discussed,. they plant false info first,. then send people out to “debunk” that false info. Why do that? Here’s an example:. the original, early “Event A” is real,. but to steer the narrative,. they won’t address A,. and instead fabricate an “Event B,”. and once everyone discusses both A and B together,. the trolls show up to “prove” B is fake,. then pull a bait-and-switch,. implying that A must be fake too,. ultimately muddying and diluting the whole matter. That makes some people worry about saying the wrong thing. and stop talking about it. As a result, the original Event A. gradually fades from public view. That’s why, in past topics,. I avoided uncertain claims. and chose not to bring them up yet. Sometimes, to help improve viewers’. media literacy,. I’d even use them as case studies—. even if that indirectly helps the CCP “clarify” fake dirt. My aim is to show everyone. the CCP’s tactics. But I think this case is different. Because Yu Menglong has truly been persecuted to the point of being “logged out” of life. And the CCP’s current methods and attitude. are blatantly indifferent. The princelings basically act like,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">“Ordinary people can’t touch us anyway.”. If you dare discuss it inside the Great Firewall,. posts are deleted and accounts banned; if celebrity friends speak up, they’re threatened. So since that’s the case,. I think we should speak even more openly. Basically, in the case of Yu Menglong—. this time, whatever I see, I’ll talk about it. Even if it turns out to be wrong later, it doesn’t matter. The purpose of doing this. is to keep the discussion alive. By saying it out loud, I hope the audience understands—. there’s no need to fear saying the wrong thing. Let’s use their own force against them. Maybe we can even push the CCP to “clarify” things themselves. As a result, I later learned. something that broke my heart and made me furious. This one is more certain—. even Yu Menglong’s pets. were killed. Before his death, Yu Menglong publicly said. his dogs meant a lot to him. He said he worried about them even when traveling for work. Just to add—. his corgi was named Fuli,. and the French bulldog was Huotui (“Ham”). Piecing the case together so far,. we can see that the CCP princelings. first lured Yu Menglong by deception. to attend a gathering. Before the event,. Yu Menglong himself didn’t realize it was a trap,. so he brought one of his dogs, Fuli,. along to the dinner. Later, Yu Menglong was assaulted. This part was mentioned in earlier summaries,. but the part about the dog wasn’t. At the scene, Yu’s dog. kept barking to protect its owner. Those attackers were already blood-crazy. and didn’t stop. They even killed Yu’s pet on the spot. Because of that, a recording later surfaced—. from a neighbor in the same community. who secretly recorded audio in their kitchen. In it, Yu Menglong. cries out his pet’s name in agony,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">saying his pet was killed,. vowing to fight back. When I saw this part while compiling materials,. I felt deep pain and sorrow. When I was a kid, my family had dogs too,. so stories about pets. hit me especially hard. It’s heartbreaking. A reminder: the leaked audio clip to follow. may be distressing. But my reason for playing it. is not only to prove the recording exists,. but also to preserve evidence. for Yu Menglong, the victim. Of course, I understand some may not want to listen. So if you think it’ll be too hard for you,. you can mute the audio. and just read the subtitles. The following content is heavy,. but I don’t think it should be skipped—. it shows the cruel nature of the event. The CCP’s princelings and third-generation elites. are truly insane. They not only kill bodies but crush souls. After learning about this,. this is why I believe this time—. even if some leaks. get exaggerated in retelling,. that’s fine. Because it’s the CCP. that refuses to open an investigation. And the CCP itself spreads lies. To this day, the case has—. no autopsy report,. no funeral,. no official filing. They simply called it. an accidental fall and closed the case,. ignoring all the evidence and suspicious points. In that situation,. why should we fact-check. rumors unfavorable to the CCP? Why help the CCP “clarify” anything? China is a surveillance-state superpower—. yet at times like this,. they claim the community cameras broke and recorded nothing. And just happened to break at that time—. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">who believes that? Yu Menglong’s residence was a high-end community. To viewers inside the firewall sneaking out to watch my videos—. if you want to see daylight once and for all—. seriously,. don’t waste your effort worrying about. whether certain Yu Menglong rumors are true or not. That’s not the main point now. Because the biggest rumor right now—. is the one the CCP itself created. They’re lying that the whole incident was just an “accident.”. What matters most right now—. is to use the Yu Menglong case—. to help more people see the true face of the CCP government:. how it blocks information,. how it persecutes Menglong,. and to make those who normally don’t care about politics. understand how the CCP’s princelings and elites. oppress China’s entertainment industry—. and how they use the state machine to erase evidence. and silence the public. The more people understand this, the better. By the way—. because the name “Yu Menglong”. is censored inside the firewall,. many Chinese netizens who want to discuss this. or mention his name. to raise awareness among others. started using the word “fish” as a substitute for “Yu.”. But because too many people used it,. it ironically caused countless fish sellers’ livestreams. and fishing accounts. to get banned since late September. Fishing got banned. Selling fish got banned too. Those people were just unlucky. But this shows. how terrified the CCP really is—. of people discussing Yu Menglong’s case. Inside China, there were even shopping mall screens. quietly playing Yu Menglong’s image. Although the projection didn’t contain much info—. it only said, “I am Yu Menglong,”. and the video on the wall had no sound—. this has become a silent way for people inside China. to keep public attention on his wrongful death. and prevent the CCP’s propaganda machine from burying the truth. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Under my last video,. aside from the CCP internet trolls trying to whitewash,. I also saw a comment like this:. “Wouldn’t it have been better if Menglong had just stayed a rich arms dealer?”. “He could’ve lived comfortably as a top star.”. Honestly, when I first saw that comment,. I was stunned. Someone actually thinks—. since resisting the CCP means risking death,. it’s smarter to just obey and be their slave. There are really people who think that way. But thinking about it—. there are all kinds of people in this world. I guess we can’t be too surprised. Still, I’d say that person. is just the kind of person the CCP loves to exploit. That commenter probably hasn’t thought deeply enough—. because if you go that route,. you’re offering up your body to be used and abused—. by both men and women. Could you really do that? Before you say such things,. ask yourself what it means to live. Is life meant to be lived as someone’s slave? As livestock raised by those in power? Or as an organ bank for the Party? Impossible, right? And living like that—. is that even really living? Some people may still breathe,. but Yu Menglong chose to live with dignity. He wanted to live. as someone who could choose freely—. not as a puppet controlled by the CCP. Even though the price was heavy,. he refused to bow down. He chose to resist in his own way—. to gather evidence and expose the truth. Because for him, the moment he agreed to surrender—. that would be the moment he truly died. Maybe, like you said,. if Yu Menglong had cooperated with the CCP,. letting those in power harass him at will,. treating him like a toy,. he might have kept his life for a while. But the role of “the persecuted” wouldn’t disappear—. because the system stays the same. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">The next victim. would just be someone else. And his role would shift—. from victim to accomplice. Just like the 17 people. who took his life that day. Some of those involved. might not have truly wanted him dead—. but out of fear for themselves,. they didn’t dare stop it,. and went along,. just to avoid becoming the next target. That’s why Yu Menglong. didn’t choose to submit and become a plaything for the elites. And precisely because of that—. Yu Menglong remained who he truly was. The injustice against him—. is something we will all continue to follow. We can all see that Yu was a kind person by nature—. but he had boundaries and refused to be kept by others. That’s why he was blacklisted for three years. After finally making a comeback,. he started acting again and gradually became well-known. But then another group of monsters set their eyes on him. Yet he still refused to cooperate with them. He even tried to resist. Although in the end—. his resistance failed and he lost his life,. can we really say he died? From my point of view—. he didn’t truly die. Yu Menglong’s body was taken,. but what he left behind. was a soul that refused to kneel. And a person like that—. is someone truly alive. As for us—. what we can do is to make sure. that this soul is never forgotten. What do you all think about today’s video? Feel free to leave your thoughts below. That’s it for today’s video. If you enjoyed it, please like and subscribe. You’re also welcome to join my YouTube channel. or support this series. with a one-time Super Thanks donation. I’m Potter King. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">see you in the next video. Bye-bye. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w</a></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>新錄音檔流出！于朦朧為這件事跟辛奇等人拼命！</p><p>毛小孩也難逃毒手！鄰居冒險紀錄證據</p><p>禁止說魚！中國賣魚與釣魚直播主無辜遭殃</p><p>粉紅特報148期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </itunes:summary>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/cu5Gi9mYI0w/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1><ul><li>揭示中共如何利用資訊戰操控輿論，以及其應對敏感事件的慣用策略。</li><li>深入探討于孟龍案的殘酷真相，包括令人髮指的寵物慘遭殺害細節，以及中共權貴的囂張與對公眾的漠視。</li><li>啟發讀者思考在威權體制下，個人尊嚴與反抗的重要性，並見證公眾連署與聲援如何凝聚力量，挑戰國家級的謊言與掩蓋。</li></ul><hr /><h1>摘要</h1><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_0.jpg" /></p> 作為「中國實習生」導師的「波特王」在「粉紅報告」中指出，<strong>于孟龍</strong>案已在全球NGO AVAAZ網站上獲得逾25萬人連署，展現其國際關注度。許多人基於<strong>良知</strong>而非僅是粉絲身份，為被<strong>中共權貴</strong>迫害的于孟龍發聲，質疑當一個擁有2700萬粉絲的明星都能被如此對待時，普通民眾的處境將如何。此案已跨越政治與國界，成為團結<strong>反抗威權</strong>、追求真相的焦點，其持續延燒顯然出乎中共預料。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_160.jpg" /></p> 作者闡述了面對中共<strong>敘事操控</strong>的新策略：過去會避免傳播未經證實的消息，以防中共透過散佈「假事件B」來混淆「真事件A」，然後再「闢謠」B來暗示A也為假，從而稀釋真相。然而，鑒於中共在<strong>于孟龍</strong>案中表現出的公然漠視、權貴的囂張，以及國內嚴酷的言論封鎖，作者決定此次將公開討論所見所聞，即使日後部分消息證實有誤也無妨。此舉旨在保持討論熱度，鼓勵公眾不再懼怕說錯話，甚至反向迫使中共自行「澄清」，以其人之道還治其人之身。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_410.jpg" /></p> 作者透露了一個令人心碎且憤怒的細節：于孟龍生前珍愛的<strong>寵物</strong>，包括柯基犬「福利」和法國鬥牛犬「禍腿」，也慘遭殺害。案情重組顯示，于孟龍被誘騙參加聚會時，帶著「福利」赴約。在遭<strong>中共權貴</strong>施暴時，忠心的「福利」試圖保護主人不斷吠叫，卻被攻擊者當場殺害。後續流出的一段<strong>錄音</strong>中，于孟龍痛苦地哭喊著<strong>寵物</strong>的名字，並誓言反擊。作者強調播放此錄音的目的不僅是為了證明其存在，更是為受害者<strong>于孟龍</strong>保留證據，並揭示事件的殘酷本質。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_660.jpg" /></p> 作者嚴厲批評<strong>中共</strong>對於孟龍案的處理方式：<strong>無屍檢報告</strong>、<strong>無葬禮</strong>、<strong>無立案</strong>，僅草草以「<strong>意外墜樓</strong>」結案，無視所有證據和疑點。他質疑一個高檔社區的<strong>監控攝像頭</strong>「恰好」在關鍵時刻損壞並無錄影的荒謬說法。作者呼籲牆內觀眾應將注意力集中於中共本身編造的「意外」謊言，而非糾結於其他謠言。他強調此案的關鍵意義在於揭露中共政府如何<strong>封鎖資訊</strong>、<strong>迫害于孟龍</strong>，以及<strong>中共權貴</strong>如何壓迫娛樂圈、動用國家機器<strong>消除證據</strong>、<strong>封鎖輿論</strong>。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_14.jpg" /></p> 影片提到，由于孟龍的名字在牆內遭到嚴格審查，許多網民開始使用「<strong>魚</strong>」字作為替代，諷刺的是，這導致大量直播賣魚及漁業相關帳號因「違規」被封禁，顯示<strong>中共</strong>對於孟龍案討論的極度恐懼。即便在中國境內，仍有商場螢幕悄悄播放「我是<strong>于孟龍</strong>」的無聲影像，成為一種無聲的抵抗，以阻止中共的宣傳機器掩埋真相。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_16.jpg" /></p> 作者針對留言區中「為何不當聽話的權貴<strong>奴隸</strong>」的言論進行了反駁。他強調，那樣的生活無異於「被利用、被糟蹋」，如同「牲畜」或「器官銀行」，並非真正的<strong>活著</strong>。<strong>于孟龍</strong>選擇了<strong>有尊嚴</strong>、能<strong>自由選擇</strong>的生活，而非被<strong>中共</strong>操控的<strong>傀儡</strong>。即便付出了沉重代價，他也拒絕屈服，以自己的方式<strong>反抗</strong>，試圖收集證據並<strong>揭露</strong>真相。</p><hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink Report. I’m your mentor for the “Chinese intern” trainees. aka a centrist voter.(ironic trolling). Potter King. A reminder for viewers tuning in for the first time,. you’re watching a show known as. the “Chinese version of Discovery,”. taking you to explore the most authentic China. As of this episode’s cutoff,. on the global NGO. AVAAZ’s website, the. “Justice for Yu Menglong” petition. has surpassed 250,000 signatures. Though a petition may not necessarily reveal the full truth,. without it,. even giving this case. a chance to gain international exposure would be impossible. Many people speak up for Yu Menglong. even if they aren’t his fans. Those willing to join in support. are driven more by their own conscience,. which moves us to act. People see that a kind person. was persecuted by the CCP’s princelings,. while the suspects still roam free,. with not a single person held accountable to this day. Seeing a movie star with 27 million followers in China. be persecuted like this by the CCP,. imagine ordinary people with no fame at all. The wrongful case of Yu Menglong. may not yet be the last straw,. but the chain reactions it has triggered. and the public outrage it has stirred can’t be ignored. I believe this momentum is powerful. From what we’ve seen, those demanding justice for Yu. now span political lines. and even nationalities. It’s people of conscience uniting. to demand a case be opened and justice be served. The fact that this issue has kept burning for so long. is clearly something the CCP didn’t expect. By now, Yu Menglong has become a focal point for pursuing the truth. and a chance to unite against authoritarianism. Viewers are also welcome. to like, comment, and share the video,. stacking the straws one by one together. After watching today’s video, you can also sign the petition online. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">While compiling the facts of Yu’s wrongful case,. I also saw many claims whose authenticity is unclear,. which are honestly hard to verify. I also saw some rumors online. saying this is connected to Xi Jinping’s brother, Xi Yuanping. If I followed my usual way of producing the show,. I wouldn’t air tips that aren’t solid enough yet,. and I wouldn’t mention them on the show. But this time,. I think it’s fine to say it. Let me explain why, for this part. In the past, I’d avoid this with other topics. because sometimes CCP internet trolls. intentionally seed false “dirt,”. and when people begin discussing. topics the CCP doesn’t want discussed,. they plant false info first,. then send people out to “debunk” that false info. Why do that? Here’s an example:. the original, early “Event A” is real,. but to steer the narrative,. they won’t address A,. and instead fabricate an “Event B,”. and once everyone discusses both A and B together,. the trolls show up to “prove” B is fake,. then pull a bait-and-switch,. implying that A must be fake too,. ultimately muddying and diluting the whole matter. That makes some people worry about saying the wrong thing. and stop talking about it. As a result, the original Event A. gradually fades from public view. That’s why, in past topics,. I avoided uncertain claims. and chose not to bring them up yet. Sometimes, to help improve viewers’. media literacy,. I’d even use them as case studies—. even if that indirectly helps the CCP “clarify” fake dirt. My aim is to show everyone. the CCP’s tactics. But I think this case is different. Because Yu Menglong has truly been persecuted to the point of being “logged out” of life. And the CCP’s current methods and attitude. are blatantly indifferent. The princelings basically act like,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">“Ordinary people can’t touch us anyway.”. If you dare discuss it inside the Great Firewall,. posts are deleted and accounts banned; if celebrity friends speak up, they’re threatened. So since that’s the case,. I think we should speak even more openly. Basically, in the case of Yu Menglong—. this time, whatever I see, I’ll talk about it. Even if it turns out to be wrong later, it doesn’t matter. The purpose of doing this. is to keep the discussion alive. By saying it out loud, I hope the audience understands—. there’s no need to fear saying the wrong thing. Let’s use their own force against them. Maybe we can even push the CCP to “clarify” things themselves. As a result, I later learned. something that broke my heart and made me furious. This one is more certain—. even Yu Menglong’s pets. were killed. Before his death, Yu Menglong publicly said. his dogs meant a lot to him. He said he worried about them even when traveling for work. Just to add—. his corgi was named Fuli,. and the French bulldog was Huotui (“Ham”). Piecing the case together so far,. we can see that the CCP princelings. first lured Yu Menglong by deception. to attend a gathering. Before the event,. Yu Menglong himself didn’t realize it was a trap,. so he brought one of his dogs, Fuli,. along to the dinner. Later, Yu Menglong was assaulted. This part was mentioned in earlier summaries,. but the part about the dog wasn’t. At the scene, Yu’s dog. kept barking to protect its owner. Those attackers were already blood-crazy. and didn’t stop. They even killed Yu’s pet on the spot. Because of that, a recording later surfaced—. from a neighbor in the same community. who secretly recorded audio in their kitchen. In it, Yu Menglong. cries out his pet’s name in agony,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">saying his pet was killed,. vowing to fight back. When I saw this part while compiling materials,. I felt deep pain and sorrow. When I was a kid, my family had dogs too,. so stories about pets. hit me especially hard. It’s heartbreaking. A reminder: the leaked audio clip to follow. may be distressing. But my reason for playing it. is not only to prove the recording exists,. but also to preserve evidence. for Yu Menglong, the victim. Of course, I understand some may not want to listen. So if you think it’ll be too hard for you,. you can mute the audio. and just read the subtitles. The following content is heavy,. but I don’t think it should be skipped—. it shows the cruel nature of the event. The CCP’s princelings and third-generation elites. are truly insane. They not only kill bodies but crush souls. After learning about this,. this is why I believe this time—. even if some leaks. get exaggerated in retelling,. that’s fine. Because it’s the CCP. that refuses to open an investigation. And the CCP itself spreads lies. To this day, the case has—. no autopsy report,. no funeral,. no official filing. They simply called it. an accidental fall and closed the case,. ignoring all the evidence and suspicious points. In that situation,. why should we fact-check. rumors unfavorable to the CCP? Why help the CCP “clarify” anything? China is a surveillance-state superpower—. yet at times like this,. they claim the community cameras broke and recorded nothing. And just happened to break at that time—. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">who believes that? Yu Menglong’s residence was a high-end community. To viewers inside the firewall sneaking out to watch my videos—. if you want to see daylight once and for all—. seriously,. don’t waste your effort worrying about. whether certain Yu Menglong rumors are true or not. That’s not the main point now. Because the biggest rumor right now—. is the one the CCP itself created. They’re lying that the whole incident was just an “accident.”. What matters most right now—. is to use the Yu Menglong case—. to help more people see the true face of the CCP government:. how it blocks information,. how it persecutes Menglong,. and to make those who normally don’t care about politics. understand how the CCP’s princelings and elites. oppress China’s entertainment industry—. and how they use the state machine to erase evidence. and silence the public. The more people understand this, the better. By the way—. because the name “Yu Menglong”. is censored inside the firewall,. many Chinese netizens who want to discuss this. or mention his name. to raise awareness among others. started using the word “fish” as a substitute for “Yu.”. But because too many people used it,. it ironically caused countless fish sellers’ livestreams. and fishing accounts. to get banned since late September. Fishing got banned. Selling fish got banned too. Those people were just unlucky. But this shows. how terrified the CCP really is—. of people discussing Yu Menglong’s case. Inside China, there were even shopping mall screens. quietly playing Yu Menglong’s image. Although the projection didn’t contain much info—. it only said, “I am Yu Menglong,”. and the video on the wall had no sound—. this has become a silent way for people inside China. to keep public attention on his wrongful death. and prevent the CCP’s propaganda machine from burying the truth. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Under my last video,. aside from the CCP internet trolls trying to whitewash,. I also saw a comment like this:. “Wouldn’t it have been better if Menglong had just stayed a rich arms dealer?”. “He could’ve lived comfortably as a top star.”. Honestly, when I first saw that comment,. I was stunned. Someone actually thinks—. since resisting the CCP means risking death,. it’s smarter to just obey and be their slave. There are really people who think that way. But thinking about it—. there are all kinds of people in this world. I guess we can’t be too surprised. Still, I’d say that person. is just the kind of person the CCP loves to exploit. That commenter probably hasn’t thought deeply enough—. because if you go that route,. you’re offering up your body to be used and abused—. by both men and women. Could you really do that? Before you say such things,. ask yourself what it means to live. Is life meant to be lived as someone’s slave? As livestock raised by those in power? Or as an organ bank for the Party? Impossible, right? And living like that—. is that even really living? Some people may still breathe,. but Yu Menglong chose to live with dignity. He wanted to live. as someone who could choose freely—. not as a puppet controlled by the CCP. Even though the price was heavy,. he refused to bow down. He chose to resist in his own way—. to gather evidence and expose the truth. Because for him, the moment he agreed to surrender—. that would be the moment he truly died. Maybe, like you said,. if Yu Menglong had cooperated with the CCP,. letting those in power harass him at will,. treating him like a toy,. he might have kept his life for a while. But the role of “the persecuted” wouldn’t disappear—. because the system stays the same. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">The next victim. would just be someone else. And his role would shift—. from victim to accomplice. Just like the 17 people. who took his life that day. Some of those involved. might not have truly wanted him dead—. but out of fear for themselves,. they didn’t dare stop it,. and went along,. just to avoid becoming the next target. That’s why Yu Menglong. didn’t choose to submit and become a plaything for the elites. And precisely because of that—. Yu Menglong remained who he truly was. The injustice against him—. is something we will all continue to follow. We can all see that Yu was a kind person by nature—. but he had boundaries and refused to be kept by others. That’s why he was blacklisted for three years. After finally making a comeback,. he started acting again and gradually became well-known. But then another group of monsters set their eyes on him. Yet he still refused to cooperate with them. He even tried to resist. Although in the end—. his resistance failed and he lost his life,. can we really say he died? From my point of view—. he didn’t truly die. Yu Menglong’s body was taken,. but what he left behind. was a soul that refused to kneel. And a person like that—. is someone truly alive. As for us—. what we can do is to make sure. that this soul is never forgotten. What do you all think about today’s video? Feel free to leave your thoughts below. That’s it for today’s video. If you enjoyed it, please like and subscribe. You’re also welcome to join my YouTube channel. or support this series. with a one-time Super Thanks donation. I’m Potter King. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">see you in the next video. Bye-bye. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w</a></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>新錄音檔流出！于朦朧為這件事跟辛奇等人拼命！</p><p>毛小孩也難逃毒手！鄰居冒險紀錄證據</p><p>禁止說魚！中國賣魚與釣魚直播主無辜遭殃</p><p>粉紅特報148期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/cu5Gi9mYI0w/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1><ul><li>揭示中共如何利用資訊戰操控輿論，以及其應對敏感事件的慣用策略。</li><li>深入探討于孟龍案的殘酷真相，包括令人髮指的寵物慘遭殺害細節，以及中共權貴的囂張與對公眾的漠視。</li><li>啟發讀者思考在威權體制下，個人尊嚴與反抗的重要性，並見證公眾連署與聲援如何凝聚力量，挑戰國家級的謊言與掩蓋。</li></ul><hr /><h1>摘要</h1><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_0.jpg" /></p> 作為「中國實習生」導師的「波特王」在「粉紅報告」中指出，<strong>于孟龍</strong>案已在全球NGO AVAAZ網站上獲得逾25萬人連署，展現其國際關注度。許多人基於<strong>良知</strong>而非僅是粉絲身份，為被<strong>中共權貴</strong>迫害的于孟龍發聲，質疑當一個擁有2700萬粉絲的明星都能被如此對待時，普通民眾的處境將如何。此案已跨越政治與國界，成為團結<strong>反抗威權</strong>、追求真相的焦點，其持續延燒顯然出乎中共預料。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_160.jpg" /></p> 作者闡述了面對中共<strong>敘事操控</strong>的新策略：過去會避免傳播未經證實的消息，以防中共透過散佈「假事件B」來混淆「真事件A」，然後再「闢謠」B來暗示A也為假，從而稀釋真相。然而，鑒於中共在<strong>于孟龍</strong>案中表現出的公然漠視、權貴的囂張，以及國內嚴酷的言論封鎖，作者決定此次將公開討論所見所聞，即使日後部分消息證實有誤也無妨。此舉旨在保持討論熱度，鼓勵公眾不再懼怕說錯話，甚至反向迫使中共自行「澄清」，以其人之道還治其人之身。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_410.jpg" /></p> 作者透露了一個令人心碎且憤怒的細節：于孟龍生前珍愛的<strong>寵物</strong>，包括柯基犬「福利」和法國鬥牛犬「禍腿」，也慘遭殺害。案情重組顯示，于孟龍被誘騙參加聚會時，帶著「福利」赴約。在遭<strong>中共權貴</strong>施暴時，忠心的「福利」試圖保護主人不斷吠叫，卻被攻擊者當場殺害。後續流出的一段<strong>錄音</strong>中，于孟龍痛苦地哭喊著<strong>寵物</strong>的名字，並誓言反擊。作者強調播放此錄音的目的不僅是為了證明其存在，更是為受害者<strong>于孟龍</strong>保留證據，並揭示事件的殘酷本質。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_660.jpg" /></p> 作者嚴厲批評<strong>中共</strong>對於孟龍案的處理方式：<strong>無屍檢報告</strong>、<strong>無葬禮</strong>、<strong>無立案</strong>，僅草草以「<strong>意外墜樓</strong>」結案，無視所有證據和疑點。他質疑一個高檔社區的<strong>監控攝像頭</strong>「恰好」在關鍵時刻損壞並無錄影的荒謬說法。作者呼籲牆內觀眾應將注意力集中於中共本身編造的「意外」謊言，而非糾結於其他謠言。他強調此案的關鍵意義在於揭露中共政府如何<strong>封鎖資訊</strong>、<strong>迫害于孟龍</strong>，以及<strong>中共權貴</strong>如何壓迫娛樂圈、動用國家機器<strong>消除證據</strong>、<strong>封鎖輿論</strong>。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_14.jpg" /></p> 影片提到，由于孟龍的名字在牆內遭到嚴格審查，許多網民開始使用「<strong>魚</strong>」字作為替代，諷刺的是，這導致大量直播賣魚及漁業相關帳號因「違規」被封禁，顯示<strong>中共</strong>對於孟龍案討論的極度恐懼。即便在中國境內，仍有商場螢幕悄悄播放「我是<strong>于孟龍</strong>」的無聲影像，成為一種無聲的抵抗，以阻止中共的宣傳機器掩埋真相。</p><p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/cu5Gi9mYI0w_16.jpg" /></p> 作者針對留言區中「為何不當聽話的權貴<strong>奴隸</strong>」的言論進行了反駁。他強調，那樣的生活無異於「被利用、被糟蹋」，如同「牲畜」或「器官銀行」，並非真正的<strong>活著</strong>。<strong>于孟龍</strong>選擇了<strong>有尊嚴</strong>、能<strong>自由選擇</strong>的生活，而非被<strong>中共</strong>操控的<strong>傀儡</strong>。即便付出了沉重代價，他也拒絕屈服，以自己的方式<strong>反抗</strong>，試圖收集證據並<strong>揭露</strong>真相。</p><hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink Report. I’m your mentor for the “Chinese intern” trainees. aka a centrist voter.(ironic trolling). Potter King. A reminder for viewers tuning in for the first time,. you’re watching a show known as. the “Chinese version of Discovery,”. taking you to explore the most authentic China. As of this episode’s cutoff,. on the global NGO. AVAAZ’s website, the. “Justice for Yu Menglong” petition. has surpassed 250,000 signatures. Though a petition may not necessarily reveal the full truth,. without it,. even giving this case. a chance to gain international exposure would be impossible. Many people speak up for Yu Menglong. even if they aren’t his fans. Those willing to join in support. are driven more by their own conscience,. which moves us to act. People see that a kind person. was persecuted by the CCP’s princelings,. while the suspects still roam free,. with not a single person held accountable to this day. Seeing a movie star with 27 million followers in China. be persecuted like this by the CCP,. imagine ordinary people with no fame at all. The wrongful case of Yu Menglong. may not yet be the last straw,. but the chain reactions it has triggered. and the public outrage it has stirred can’t be ignored. I believe this momentum is powerful. From what we’ve seen, those demanding justice for Yu. now span political lines. and even nationalities. It’s people of conscience uniting. to demand a case be opened and justice be served. The fact that this issue has kept burning for so long. is clearly something the CCP didn’t expect. By now, Yu Menglong has become a focal point for pursuing the truth. and a chance to unite against authoritarianism. Viewers are also welcome. to like, comment, and share the video,. stacking the straws one by one together. After watching today’s video, you can also sign the petition online. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">While compiling the facts of Yu’s wrongful case,. I also saw many claims whose authenticity is unclear,. which are honestly hard to verify. I also saw some rumors online. saying this is connected to Xi Jinping’s brother, Xi Yuanping. If I followed my usual way of producing the show,. I wouldn’t air tips that aren’t solid enough yet,. and I wouldn’t mention them on the show. But this time,. I think it’s fine to say it. Let me explain why, for this part. In the past, I’d avoid this with other topics. because sometimes CCP internet trolls. intentionally seed false “dirt,”. and when people begin discussing. topics the CCP doesn’t want discussed,. they plant false info first,. then send people out to “debunk” that false info. Why do that? Here’s an example:. the original, early “Event A” is real,. but to steer the narrative,. they won’t address A,. and instead fabricate an “Event B,”. and once everyone discusses both A and B together,. the trolls show up to “prove” B is fake,. then pull a bait-and-switch,. implying that A must be fake too,. ultimately muddying and diluting the whole matter. That makes some people worry about saying the wrong thing. and stop talking about it. As a result, the original Event A. gradually fades from public view. That’s why, in past topics,. I avoided uncertain claims. and chose not to bring them up yet. Sometimes, to help improve viewers’. media literacy,. I’d even use them as case studies—. even if that indirectly helps the CCP “clarify” fake dirt. My aim is to show everyone. the CCP’s tactics. But I think this case is different. Because Yu Menglong has truly been persecuted to the point of being “logged out” of life. And the CCP’s current methods and attitude. are blatantly indifferent. The princelings basically act like,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">“Ordinary people can’t touch us anyway.”. If you dare discuss it inside the Great Firewall,. posts are deleted and accounts banned; if celebrity friends speak up, they’re threatened. So since that’s the case,. I think we should speak even more openly. Basically, in the case of Yu Menglong—. this time, whatever I see, I’ll talk about it. Even if it turns out to be wrong later, it doesn’t matter. The purpose of doing this. is to keep the discussion alive. By saying it out loud, I hope the audience understands—. there’s no need to fear saying the wrong thing. Let’s use their own force against them. Maybe we can even push the CCP to “clarify” things themselves. As a result, I later learned. something that broke my heart and made me furious. This one is more certain—. even Yu Menglong’s pets. were killed. Before his death, Yu Menglong publicly said. his dogs meant a lot to him. He said he worried about them even when traveling for work. Just to add—. his corgi was named Fuli,. and the French bulldog was Huotui (“Ham”). Piecing the case together so far,. we can see that the CCP princelings. first lured Yu Menglong by deception. to attend a gathering. Before the event,. Yu Menglong himself didn’t realize it was a trap,. so he brought one of his dogs, Fuli,. along to the dinner. Later, Yu Menglong was assaulted. This part was mentioned in earlier summaries,. but the part about the dog wasn’t. At the scene, Yu’s dog. kept barking to protect its owner. Those attackers were already blood-crazy. and didn’t stop. They even killed Yu’s pet on the spot. Because of that, a recording later surfaced—. from a neighbor in the same community. who secretly recorded audio in their kitchen. In it, Yu Menglong. cries out his pet’s name in agony,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">saying his pet was killed,. vowing to fight back. When I saw this part while compiling materials,. I felt deep pain and sorrow. When I was a kid, my family had dogs too,. so stories about pets. hit me especially hard. It’s heartbreaking. A reminder: the leaked audio clip to follow. may be distressing. But my reason for playing it. is not only to prove the recording exists,. but also to preserve evidence. for Yu Menglong, the victim. Of course, I understand some may not want to listen. So if you think it’ll be too hard for you,. you can mute the audio. and just read the subtitles. The following content is heavy,. but I don’t think it should be skipped—. it shows the cruel nature of the event. The CCP’s princelings and third-generation elites. are truly insane. They not only kill bodies but crush souls. After learning about this,. this is why I believe this time—. even if some leaks. get exaggerated in retelling,. that’s fine. Because it’s the CCP. that refuses to open an investigation. And the CCP itself spreads lies. To this day, the case has—. no autopsy report,. no funeral,. no official filing. They simply called it. an accidental fall and closed the case,. ignoring all the evidence and suspicious points. In that situation,. why should we fact-check. rumors unfavorable to the CCP? Why help the CCP “clarify” anything? China is a surveillance-state superpower—. yet at times like this,. they claim the community cameras broke and recorded nothing. And just happened to break at that time—. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">who believes that? Yu Menglong’s residence was a high-end community. To viewers inside the firewall sneaking out to watch my videos—. if you want to see daylight once and for all—. seriously,. don’t waste your effort worrying about. whether certain Yu Menglong rumors are true or not. That’s not the main point now. Because the biggest rumor right now—. is the one the CCP itself created. They’re lying that the whole incident was just an “accident.”. What matters most right now—. is to use the Yu Menglong case—. to help more people see the true face of the CCP government:. how it blocks information,. how it persecutes Menglong,. and to make those who normally don’t care about politics. understand how the CCP’s princelings and elites. oppress China’s entertainment industry—. and how they use the state machine to erase evidence. and silence the public. The more people understand this, the better. By the way—. because the name “Yu Menglong”. is censored inside the firewall,. many Chinese netizens who want to discuss this. or mention his name. to raise awareness among others. started using the word “fish” as a substitute for “Yu.”. But because too many people used it,. it ironically caused countless fish sellers’ livestreams. and fishing accounts. to get banned since late September. Fishing got banned. Selling fish got banned too. Those people were just unlucky. But this shows. how terrified the CCP really is—. of people discussing Yu Menglong’s case. Inside China, there were even shopping mall screens. quietly playing Yu Menglong’s image. Although the projection didn’t contain much info—. it only said, “I am Yu Menglong,”. and the video on the wall had no sound—. this has become a silent way for people inside China. to keep public attention on his wrongful death. and prevent the CCP’s propaganda machine from burying the truth. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Under my last video,. aside from the CCP internet trolls trying to whitewash,. I also saw a comment like this:. “Wouldn’t it have been better if Menglong had just stayed a rich arms dealer?”. “He could’ve lived comfortably as a top star.”. Honestly, when I first saw that comment,. I was stunned. Someone actually thinks—. since resisting the CCP means risking death,. it’s smarter to just obey and be their slave. There are really people who think that way. But thinking about it—. there are all kinds of people in this world. I guess we can’t be too surprised. Still, I’d say that person. is just the kind of person the CCP loves to exploit. That commenter probably hasn’t thought deeply enough—. because if you go that route,. you’re offering up your body to be used and abused—. by both men and women. Could you really do that? Before you say such things,. ask yourself what it means to live. Is life meant to be lived as someone’s slave? As livestock raised by those in power? Or as an organ bank for the Party? Impossible, right? And living like that—. is that even really living? Some people may still breathe,. but Yu Menglong chose to live with dignity. He wanted to live. as someone who could choose freely—. not as a puppet controlled by the CCP. Even though the price was heavy,. he refused to bow down. He chose to resist in his own way—. to gather evidence and expose the truth. Because for him, the moment he agreed to surrender—. that would be the moment he truly died. Maybe, like you said,. if Yu Menglong had cooperated with the CCP,. letting those in power harass him at will,. treating him like a toy,. he might have kept his life for a while. But the role of “the persecuted” wouldn’t disappear—. because the system stays the same. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">The next victim. would just be someone else. And his role would shift—. from victim to accomplice. Just like the 17 people. who took his life that day. Some of those involved. might not have truly wanted him dead—. but out of fear for themselves,. they didn’t dare stop it,. and went along,. just to avoid becoming the next target. That’s why Yu Menglong. didn’t choose to submit and become a plaything for the elites. And precisely because of that—. Yu Menglong remained who he truly was. The injustice against him—. is something we will all continue to follow. We can all see that Yu was a kind person by nature—. but he had boundaries and refused to be kept by others. That’s why he was blacklisted for three years. After finally making a comeback,. he started acting again and gradually became well-known. But then another group of monsters set their eyes on him. Yet he still refused to cooperate with them. He even tried to resist. Although in the end—. his resistance failed and he lost his life,. can we really say he died? From my point of view—. he didn’t truly die. Yu Menglong’s body was taken,. but what he left behind. was a soul that refused to kneel. And a person like that—. is someone truly alive. As for us—. what we can do is to make sure. that this soul is never forgotten. What do you all think about today’s video? Feel free to leave your thoughts below. That’s it for today’s video. If you enjoyed it, please like and subscribe. You’re also welcome to join my YouTube channel. or support this series. with a one-time Super Thanks donation. I’m Potter King. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">see you in the next video. Bye-bye. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cu5Gi9mYI0w</a></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>新錄音檔流出！于朦朧為這件事跟辛奇等人拼命！</p><p>毛小孩也難逃毒手！鄰居冒險紀錄證據</p><p>禁止說魚！中國賣魚與釣魚直播主無辜遭殃</p><p>粉紅特報148期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cu5Gi9mYI0w/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <pubDate>2025-10-11T09:30:17.000Z</pubDate>
    </item><item>
      <title><![CDATA[中國明星公司登記軍火商？于朦朧冤案揭開更大黑幕！于朦朧生前喊范小花救我！范小花冷回：打暈刨了｜韓國聲紋機構鑑定：范世錡聲紋吻合99%！｜粉紅特報147期]]></title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI</link>
      <itunes:title><![CDATA[中國明星公司登記軍火商？于朦朧冤案揭開更大黑幕！于朦朧生前喊范小花救我！范小花冷回：打暈刨了｜韓國聲紋機構鑑定：范世錡聲紋吻合99%！｜粉紅特報147期]]></itunes:title>
      <itunes:author><![CDATA[波特王好帥]]></itunes:author>
      <itunes:summary>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/Mxlo_SBcPeI/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1> <ul><li>揭露中共權貴如何利用娛樂圈名人進行洗錢及迫害異己的黑幕，呈現中國社會深層的腐敗問題。</li><li>展現國際媒體及海外聲紋鑑定機構在突破中共信息封鎖、挖掘敏感案件真相方面的關鍵作用。</li><li>深入探討中國娛樂產業中「潛規則」的普遍性，以及中共對異議的嚴厲打壓與信息封鎖，揭示中國公民所面臨的言論審查困境。</li></ul><hr /> <h1>摘要</h1> <p>這段影片的<strong>作者</strong>，作為「中國實習生指導員」（AKA 中間選民、波特王），首先對影片更新延遲表達歉意，並說明原因是前一週忙碌及參與花蓮賑災志工。他隨後介紹自己的頻道是「中國版的探索頻道」，旨在帶領觀眾探索真實的中國。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_30.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>余孟龍案的初步曝光與當局壓制</h2> <p><strong>作者</strong>首先跟進了<strong>余孟龍冤案</strong>的後續發展。儘管案件疑點重重，中國警方卻迅速結案，後來發現涉案嫌疑人與中共高官的「紅二代、紅三代」有關。此事件也間接揭露了中國娛樂圈的<strong>潛規則黑幕</strong>。在中國的防火牆內，該話題至今仍被禁止討論，中共當局積極封鎖相關貼文、刪除討論此案的中國網民帳號，試圖徹底抹去余孟龍的存在痕跡。然而，<strong>作者</strong>強調，越是壓制越能引起好奇心，而防火牆外的觀衆持續關注此議題，促使海外媒體持續報導並深入挖掘真相。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_105.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>國際媒體的關注與關鍵證人的消失</h2> <p><strong>作者</strong>指出，透過海外社群的努力，余孟龍案已獲得一定程度的關注。美國雜誌《外交政策》（Foreign Policy）將余孟龍案刊登在其英文頭版，讓國際讀者了解這起冤案，包括這位擁有2700萬粉絲的電影明星如何被中共權貴子弟迫害並一夜之間消失，以及中共政府對此案實施嚴厲的言論審查。余孟龍的母親曾為兒子尋求公道，但隨後與外界失聯，下落不明，很可能已被中共控制。同時，印度《金融快報》（Financial Express）也報導，余孟龍死亡的社區有數百戶家庭面臨威脅性集體出售，居民生活在恐懼之中，記者試圖採訪或調閱監視器畫面時，居民多保持沉默或斷然拒絕，深怕引火上身，成為下一個余孟龍。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_210.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>關鍵錄音檔與范世錡的涉案嫌疑</h2> <p>除了外媒報導，一段據稱是余孟龍死前求救的錄音檔在海外廣為流傳。錄音中包含他被折磨的聲音，余孟龍曾喊出「范小華救我！」顯示現場有位名叫范小華的人，而「范小華」正是<strong>范世錡</strong>的暱稱。<strong>范世錡</strong>與余孟龍是從選秀節目《快樂男聲》一同出道的朋友，<strong>范世錡</strong>也與中共高官蔡奇的私生子辛琦關係密切。錄音檔中，除了余孟龍的求救聲，還捕捉到疑似范世錡在附近呼喊的聲音，命令「吐出來！快點！」「把他打暈，把他剖了！」暗示著肢解余孟龍的意圖。因此，中國網民普遍認為范世錡是這場迫害的共犯之一。儘管范世錡在網上發文聲稱無辜，但說法疑點太多，導致其演唱會的門票銷量慘淡，只售出十五張。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_360.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>聲紋鑑定與中共權貴的黑幕</h2> <p>近期，有中國網民將該錄音檔委託給韓國聲紋比對機構進行鑑定，結果顯示音頻中的聲音與<strong>范世錡</strong>的聲音相似度高達99.57%。這項鑑定結果成為了關鍵證據，但<strong>作者</strong>指出中共顯然無意調查，公安部門持續視而不見，至今未立案。<strong>作者</strong>強調，余孟龍案絕非孤立事件，他的名字被「太子黨」用來註冊<strong>空殼公司進行洗錢</strong>，且公司營業範圍竟包含「<strong>軍火商</strong>」類別，這表明余孟龍被當作中共的「白手套」進行大筆洗錢，而他正是因為掌握了相關證據而遭滅口。更深入挖掘會發現，許多中國頂級藝人的公司也都註冊了軍火相關類別，例如易烊千璽、郭俊辰、龔俊等人，這顯示中國娛樂圈的A咖藝人都牢牢掌握在中共手中，因此幾乎沒有人敢為余孟龍發聲。一位曾與余孟龍合作過的小演員也在直播中暗示，中國演藝圈的<strong>潛規則</strong>非常普遍，無論男女，一旦被盯上，便無力反抗，而中共極力害怕這些黑幕被揭露。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_540.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>作者對惡意評論的回應與呼籲</h2> <p>影片後半段，<strong>作者</strong>針對幾則惡意評論進行了幽默且犀利的回應。面對「小雜碎還沒死」的評論，<strong>作者</strong>回擊自己比對方健康。對於被批評「別再自稱中間選民，噁心」，<strong>作者</strong>解釋自己曾是「挺台派」，因批評中共而被貼標籤，才轉而自稱「中間選民」，並半開玩笑地表示若台灣人想成為「中共韭菜」，他會帶大家一同「實習」；他強調自己現在是「中間搗蛋選民」，不談政治，只質疑國民黨縣市長稅收超徵卻不發錢的政策。面對「一群低能兒還在自嗨」及「井蛙就是狂」的評論，<strong>作者</strong>對比了小粉紅對本國受害者余孟龍的冷漠與對自己的攻擊，指出身為台灣人的他反而幫忙傳播真相，呼籲小粉紅反思。他強調余孟龍被中共權貴迫害離世，有何「自嗨」可言？並反諷若覺得「嗨」，願為其提供類似遭遇。最後，<strong>作者</strong>鄭重呼籲觀眾廣泛分享影片，提高大眾對此類事件的關注，以阻止更多人間悲劇發生，因為關注余孟龍，就是關注我們自己。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_13.jpg" /></p> <hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Sorry, dear viewers. The update is late. I was a bit busy last week. Plus, I went to Hualien to volunteer for disaster relief. So I’m only updating now. Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Satirical Report. I’m your Chinese intern instructor (satirical). AKA the centrist voter. Potter King. A quick reminder for those watching this channel for the first time—. You’re watching a show known as—. The Chinese version of Discovery. Taking you to explore the real China. Today’s video will first follow up on—. The aftermath of Yu Menglong’s wrongful case. Yu Menglong’s cause of death remains mysterious. Chinese police quickly closed the case despite many suspicious points. Later, people discovered that the suspects involved—. Were linked to the “second- and third-generation red” offspring of high-ranking CCP officials. This incident also indirectly exposed—. The dark side of hidden rules in China’s entertainment industry. As a result, within China’s Great Firewall—. The topic is still forbidden to discuss. Facing the CCP authorities—. Who aggressively blocked related posts,. And deleted Chinese netizens’ accounts discussing the case,. Trying to completely erase—. All traces of Yu Menglong’s existence from this world. But the more they suppress it, the more curiosity it arouses. Thanks to you and me outside the firewall—. My dear viewers—. You are important. By continuing to pay attention to this issue—. Overseas media—. Will keep reporting and digging deeper into the truth. I’ve been continuously following the case’s developments—. And noticed that everyone’s discussions weren’t in vain. The topic has maintained a certain level of attention. And foreign media have begun reporting on it. The magazine Foreign Policy—. Published Yu Menglong’s case on its English front page. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Allowing international readers to learn about this wrongful case. They now know—. That this movie star with 27 million followers in China—. Was persecuted and disappeared overnight by children of CCP elites. The CCP government even imposed censorship—. Banning Chinese citizens from discussing or following the case. Yu’s mother once stepped forward—. Trying to seek justice for her son. But she later lost contact with the outside world. Her whereabouts are unknown. It’s highly likely she’s under CCP control. No one knows where she’s being held under house arrest. Meanwhile, India’s Financial Express also reported—. That the neighborhood where Yu Menglong died—. Saw hundreds of homes threatened into collective sales. Residents of the apartments are living in panic. When reporters tried to contact residents—. For interviews or access to surveillance footage,. They either remained silent or flatly refused—. Afraid of bringing trouble upon themselves—. And becoming the next Yu Menglong. Besides the foreign media coverage—. A leaked audio recording went viral overseas—. Said to capture Yu Menglong’s cries for help before his death. The recording contains sounds of him being tortured. You can hear his screams. Yu Menglong shouts—. “Fan Xiaohua, save me!”. He said his hands were losing strength. Which shows that a person named Fan Xiaohua was at the crime scene. And “Fan Xiaohua” happens to be Fan Shiqi’s nickname. Let me give you a bit of background about him. Fan Shiqi and Yu Menglong—. Were friends who debuted together on the show Happy Boys. Fan Shiqi also had close ties with—. Xin Qi, the illegitimate son of senior CCP official Cai Qi—. Their relationship is very close. As for the recording—. Besides Yu Menglong’s cries for help—. It also captured a voice suspected to be Fan Shiqi’s—. Shouting nearby,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">“Spit it out! Hurry!”. Then, “Knock him out, cut him open!”. Urging others to cut open Yu Menglong’s stomach. Thus, Chinese netizens believe Fan Shiqi—. Was one of the accomplices in the persecution. Although Fan Shiqi claimed he was innocent—. Posting explanations online—. It was just too suspicious. So Chinese netizens didn’t believe his statement. Recently, ticket sales for his concert were terrible—. Only fifteen tickets sold. Up to this point—. There wasn’t any crucial evidence against Fan yet. So by the end of September—. He was only considered a suspect. But just these past few days—. Some Chinese citizens took the recording—. And commissioned a Korean voice-print comparison agency. They found that the audio clip. matched Fan Shiqi’s voice with 99.57% similarity. This Chinese netizen originally wanted to debunk rumors,. so they hired a Korean professional voiceprint team to analyze it,. specifically choosing people unfamiliar with Chinese celebrities. to do an unbiased analysis. Unexpectedly, the appraisal showed instead. that the cries for help were from Yu Menglong himself,. and that another man shouting at the scene. was a very high match with Fan Shiqi’s voice—. almost certainly the same person. This appraisal is a highly critical piece of evidence. Investigate it properly. Combined with the building’s CCTV footage,. it could absolutely reconstruct what happened that night. and deliver justice for Yu Menglong. But clearly the CCP has no intention of investigating. Public security continues to look the other way,. and there’s still no case opened. Let me stress again: Yu Menglong’s case. is definitely not an isolated one. His name was used by a princeling. to register shell companies. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">for money laundering. Yu is an entertainer,. yet the business scope of the shell company. included “arms dealer” categories. Why would a film star’s company. be registered for the arms industry? Those items cover defense contractors,. manufacturers, traders, suppliers—etc. All of that is arms-dealer business. In plain terms,. he was made into a white glove for the CCP,. used to launder large sums. Yu gathered relevant evidence,. and that’s why he was silenced. And it wasn’t only Yu’s companies being used like this. Dig a little deeper and you’ll find. many top-tier Chinese celebrities’ companies. are also registered with arms categories—. Jackson Yee,. Guo Junchen,. Gong Jun…. I doubt any of these artists intended their companies. to be listed as arms businesses. You could say the A-list of China’s entertainment world. is firmly under CCP control. No wonder almost no one dares to speak out for Yu. At most, they hint at it in very veiled ways. Here’s a short clip for you:. a minor Chinese actor. who had worked with Yu,. not very famous himself,. went live after the incident and talked about similar things,. saying this kind of thing is rampant in China’s showbiz. After watching the whole thing,. I think what he really wanted to tell viewers. is that the unspoken rules of China’s entertainment industry. are real. If you’re targeted—male or female—. you can run into it,. and there’s nothing you can do. But the CCP. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">is very afraid of this being exposed,. so we need to discuss and understand it more. That’s it for today’s “Intern as a Chinese” session. What did you think of today’s video? Share in the comments below. In the second half,. let’s look at a few “self-own” comments. First one:. “?? Why are you still here? A small fry like you isn’t dead yet?”. I’m healthier than you, of course I’m still here. Next:. “Stop calling yourself a centrist voter—. disgusting.”. This person’s pretty low, too—. has to trash-talk everyone. I used to say I was “pro-Taiwan”:. whoever treats Taiwan well,. I’d support them. I never joined any party. Yet a bunch of people called me a partisan shill. just because I criticized CCP nonsense. So I changed. I thought, fine—. forget it. If Taiwanese want to be Chinese,. I’ll go with the mainstream opinion, okay? If you can’t beat ’em, join ’em. I switched to “centrist voter.”. If Taiwanese don’t want to be Taiwanese. and want to become CCP chives,. then I’ll first take everyone. to intern in Chinese life together. I’m “joining” you, right? And still you come to scold me? Sorry—mind telling me your mother’s maiden name? Someone wants to be a centrist voter—do they need your permission? I never stopped you from being an idiot. Yet you’re here trying to stop me from being a centrist voter. You think you’re way too important. And I’m not just a centrist voter now—. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I’m a centrist troublemaker. Don’t talk politics with me. I’m just asking why KMT mayors over-collected taxes. But won’t hand out cash to everyone. A lot of my friends are waiting. Next comment. A bunch of low-IQ idiots still hyping themselves up. Such clichéd tactics. Those “toads” are as outrageous as it gets. For the past two weeks, my videos. Have been speaking up about Yu Menglong’s wrongful case. Logically,. Yu Menglong,. As a Chinese citizen,. Is your compatriot, Little Pink. He was persecuted—. You should be standing up for him. But you didn’t. Instead, it’s me, a Taiwanese,. Who’s helping spread the information,. Hoping more people will pay attention. Yu Menglong was a kind person. He shouldn’t have died like this. If you won’t help, fine. You can’t even discuss my video’s content—. You just hurl insults and slap on labels,. Calling people “toads,”. Saying everyone’s self-hyping. Yu Menglong was persecuted by CCP elites. And has already “logged out of Life Online.”. What’s there to be excited about? If that’s “exciting” to you,. Then tell me where you live—. We’ll get a group together. To hang you upside down outside a high-rise window,. So you can experience what Yu went through,. And see if you’re still “excited.”. If this can’t raise more awareness,. Then, as I’ve said,. Yu Menglong won’t be the last. Focusing on him is really focusing on yourself. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">To stop such human tragedies from happening again,. Besides me spreading the word,. I also need you, the viewers, to share it widely. This “Little Pink” is obviously. A CCP troll here to whitewash. Any normal person with a conscience. Couldn’t possibly. Stand on the CCP government’s side on this. Next comment. Hilarious. “The green side wing,”. Habitual rumor-mongering and defamation. I’ve already switched to helping everyone understand the real China—. And you still call that the “green side wing”? Also, the legally correct term is “defamation,”. Not “huibang.”. “Huibang” is the wrong term. Are you legally illiterate? So, did you all notice? Whether it’s these haters or troll accounts,. They can’t actually address the video’s content. With relevant comments. They start by slapping on labels,. And once the tag sticks,. They just keep cursing,. Regardless of what the video actually says. But the more they do this,. The more it shows. That what we’re discussing right now. Is exactly what the CCP doesn’t want discussed. Please share the video widely,. So more people can join the discussion. That’s it for today’s video. If you enjoy my videos,. Please like and subscribe. You’re also welcome to join my YouTube channel membership,. Or support the show with a one-time Super Thanks. I’m Potter King. See you in the next video. Bye-bye. Bye. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI</a></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>中國明星公司登記軍火商？于朦朧冤案揭開更大黑幕！</p><p>于朦朧生前喊范小花救我！范小花冷回：打暈刨了</p><p>韓國聲紋機構鑑定：范世錡聲紋吻合99%！</p><p>粉紅特報147期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </itunes:summary>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/Mxlo_SBcPeI/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1> <ul><li>揭露中共權貴如何利用娛樂圈名人進行洗錢及迫害異己的黑幕，呈現中國社會深層的腐敗問題。</li><li>展現國際媒體及海外聲紋鑑定機構在突破中共信息封鎖、挖掘敏感案件真相方面的關鍵作用。</li><li>深入探討中國娛樂產業中「潛規則」的普遍性，以及中共對異議的嚴厲打壓與信息封鎖，揭示中國公民所面臨的言論審查困境。</li></ul><hr /> <h1>摘要</h1> <p>這段影片的<strong>作者</strong>，作為「中國實習生指導員」（AKA 中間選民、波特王），首先對影片更新延遲表達歉意，並說明原因是前一週忙碌及參與花蓮賑災志工。他隨後介紹自己的頻道是「中國版的探索頻道」，旨在帶領觀眾探索真實的中國。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_30.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>余孟龍案的初步曝光與當局壓制</h2> <p><strong>作者</strong>首先跟進了<strong>余孟龍冤案</strong>的後續發展。儘管案件疑點重重，中國警方卻迅速結案，後來發現涉案嫌疑人與中共高官的「紅二代、紅三代」有關。此事件也間接揭露了中國娛樂圈的<strong>潛規則黑幕</strong>。在中國的防火牆內，該話題至今仍被禁止討論，中共當局積極封鎖相關貼文、刪除討論此案的中國網民帳號，試圖徹底抹去余孟龍的存在痕跡。然而，<strong>作者</strong>強調，越是壓制越能引起好奇心，而防火牆外的觀衆持續關注此議題，促使海外媒體持續報導並深入挖掘真相。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_105.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>國際媒體的關注與關鍵證人的消失</h2> <p><strong>作者</strong>指出，透過海外社群的努力，余孟龍案已獲得一定程度的關注。美國雜誌《外交政策》（Foreign Policy）將余孟龍案刊登在其英文頭版，讓國際讀者了解這起冤案，包括這位擁有2700萬粉絲的電影明星如何被中共權貴子弟迫害並一夜之間消失，以及中共政府對此案實施嚴厲的言論審查。余孟龍的母親曾為兒子尋求公道，但隨後與外界失聯，下落不明，很可能已被中共控制。同時，印度《金融快報》（Financial Express）也報導，余孟龍死亡的社區有數百戶家庭面臨威脅性集體出售，居民生活在恐懼之中，記者試圖採訪或調閱監視器畫面時，居民多保持沉默或斷然拒絕，深怕引火上身，成為下一個余孟龍。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_210.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>關鍵錄音檔與范世錡的涉案嫌疑</h2> <p>除了外媒報導，一段據稱是余孟龍死前求救的錄音檔在海外廣為流傳。錄音中包含他被折磨的聲音，余孟龍曾喊出「范小華救我！」顯示現場有位名叫范小華的人，而「范小華」正是<strong>范世錡</strong>的暱稱。<strong>范世錡</strong>與余孟龍是從選秀節目《快樂男聲》一同出道的朋友，<strong>范世錡</strong>也與中共高官蔡奇的私生子辛琦關係密切。錄音檔中，除了余孟龍的求救聲，還捕捉到疑似范世錡在附近呼喊的聲音，命令「吐出來！快點！」「把他打暈，把他剖了！」暗示著肢解余孟龍的意圖。因此，中國網民普遍認為范世錡是這場迫害的共犯之一。儘管范世錡在網上發文聲稱無辜，但說法疑點太多，導致其演唱會的門票銷量慘淡，只售出十五張。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_360.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>聲紋鑑定與中共權貴的黑幕</h2> <p>近期，有中國網民將該錄音檔委託給韓國聲紋比對機構進行鑑定，結果顯示音頻中的聲音與<strong>范世錡</strong>的聲音相似度高達99.57%。這項鑑定結果成為了關鍵證據，但<strong>作者</strong>指出中共顯然無意調查，公安部門持續視而不見，至今未立案。<strong>作者</strong>強調，余孟龍案絕非孤立事件，他的名字被「太子黨」用來註冊<strong>空殼公司進行洗錢</strong>，且公司營業範圍竟包含「<strong>軍火商</strong>」類別，這表明余孟龍被當作中共的「白手套」進行大筆洗錢，而他正是因為掌握了相關證據而遭滅口。更深入挖掘會發現，許多中國頂級藝人的公司也都註冊了軍火相關類別，例如易烊千璽、郭俊辰、龔俊等人，這顯示中國娛樂圈的A咖藝人都牢牢掌握在中共手中，因此幾乎沒有人敢為余孟龍發聲。一位曾與余孟龍合作過的小演員也在直播中暗示，中國演藝圈的<strong>潛規則</strong>非常普遍，無論男女，一旦被盯上，便無力反抗，而中共極力害怕這些黑幕被揭露。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_540.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>作者對惡意評論的回應與呼籲</h2> <p>影片後半段，<strong>作者</strong>針對幾則惡意評論進行了幽默且犀利的回應。面對「小雜碎還沒死」的評論，<strong>作者</strong>回擊自己比對方健康。對於被批評「別再自稱中間選民，噁心」，<strong>作者</strong>解釋自己曾是「挺台派」，因批評中共而被貼標籤，才轉而自稱「中間選民」，並半開玩笑地表示若台灣人想成為「中共韭菜」，他會帶大家一同「實習」；他強調自己現在是「中間搗蛋選民」，不談政治，只質疑國民黨縣市長稅收超徵卻不發錢的政策。面對「一群低能兒還在自嗨」及「井蛙就是狂」的評論，<strong>作者</strong>對比了小粉紅對本國受害者余孟龍的冷漠與對自己的攻擊，指出身為台灣人的他反而幫忙傳播真相，呼籲小粉紅反思。他強調余孟龍被中共權貴迫害離世，有何「自嗨」可言？並反諷若覺得「嗨」，願為其提供類似遭遇。最後，<strong>作者</strong>鄭重呼籲觀眾廣泛分享影片，提高大眾對此類事件的關注，以阻止更多人間悲劇發生，因為關注余孟龍，就是關注我們自己。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_13.jpg" /></p> <hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Sorry, dear viewers. The update is late. I was a bit busy last week. Plus, I went to Hualien to volunteer for disaster relief. So I’m only updating now. Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Satirical Report. I’m your Chinese intern instructor (satirical). AKA the centrist voter. Potter King. A quick reminder for those watching this channel for the first time—. You’re watching a show known as—. The Chinese version of Discovery. Taking you to explore the real China. Today’s video will first follow up on—. The aftermath of Yu Menglong’s wrongful case. Yu Menglong’s cause of death remains mysterious. Chinese police quickly closed the case despite many suspicious points. Later, people discovered that the suspects involved—. Were linked to the “second- and third-generation red” offspring of high-ranking CCP officials. This incident also indirectly exposed—. The dark side of hidden rules in China’s entertainment industry. As a result, within China’s Great Firewall—. The topic is still forbidden to discuss. Facing the CCP authorities—. Who aggressively blocked related posts,. And deleted Chinese netizens’ accounts discussing the case,. Trying to completely erase—. All traces of Yu Menglong’s existence from this world. But the more they suppress it, the more curiosity it arouses. Thanks to you and me outside the firewall—. My dear viewers—. You are important. By continuing to pay attention to this issue—. Overseas media—. Will keep reporting and digging deeper into the truth. I’ve been continuously following the case’s developments—. And noticed that everyone’s discussions weren’t in vain. The topic has maintained a certain level of attention. And foreign media have begun reporting on it. The magazine Foreign Policy—. Published Yu Menglong’s case on its English front page. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Allowing international readers to learn about this wrongful case. They now know—. That this movie star with 27 million followers in China—. Was persecuted and disappeared overnight by children of CCP elites. The CCP government even imposed censorship—. Banning Chinese citizens from discussing or following the case. Yu’s mother once stepped forward—. Trying to seek justice for her son. But she later lost contact with the outside world. Her whereabouts are unknown. It’s highly likely she’s under CCP control. No one knows where she’s being held under house arrest. Meanwhile, India’s Financial Express also reported—. That the neighborhood where Yu Menglong died—. Saw hundreds of homes threatened into collective sales. Residents of the apartments are living in panic. When reporters tried to contact residents—. For interviews or access to surveillance footage,. They either remained silent or flatly refused—. Afraid of bringing trouble upon themselves—. And becoming the next Yu Menglong. Besides the foreign media coverage—. A leaked audio recording went viral overseas—. Said to capture Yu Menglong’s cries for help before his death. The recording contains sounds of him being tortured. You can hear his screams. Yu Menglong shouts—. “Fan Xiaohua, save me!”. He said his hands were losing strength. Which shows that a person named Fan Xiaohua was at the crime scene. And “Fan Xiaohua” happens to be Fan Shiqi’s nickname. Let me give you a bit of background about him. Fan Shiqi and Yu Menglong—. Were friends who debuted together on the show Happy Boys. Fan Shiqi also had close ties with—. Xin Qi, the illegitimate son of senior CCP official Cai Qi—. Their relationship is very close. As for the recording—. Besides Yu Menglong’s cries for help—. It also captured a voice suspected to be Fan Shiqi’s—. Shouting nearby,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">“Spit it out! Hurry!”. Then, “Knock him out, cut him open!”. Urging others to cut open Yu Menglong’s stomach. Thus, Chinese netizens believe Fan Shiqi—. Was one of the accomplices in the persecution. Although Fan Shiqi claimed he was innocent—. Posting explanations online—. It was just too suspicious. So Chinese netizens didn’t believe his statement. Recently, ticket sales for his concert were terrible—. Only fifteen tickets sold. Up to this point—. There wasn’t any crucial evidence against Fan yet. So by the end of September—. He was only considered a suspect. But just these past few days—. Some Chinese citizens took the recording—. And commissioned a Korean voice-print comparison agency. They found that the audio clip. matched Fan Shiqi’s voice with 99.57% similarity. This Chinese netizen originally wanted to debunk rumors,. so they hired a Korean professional voiceprint team to analyze it,. specifically choosing people unfamiliar with Chinese celebrities. to do an unbiased analysis. Unexpectedly, the appraisal showed instead. that the cries for help were from Yu Menglong himself,. and that another man shouting at the scene. was a very high match with Fan Shiqi’s voice—. almost certainly the same person. This appraisal is a highly critical piece of evidence. Investigate it properly. Combined with the building’s CCTV footage,. it could absolutely reconstruct what happened that night. and deliver justice for Yu Menglong. But clearly the CCP has no intention of investigating. Public security continues to look the other way,. and there’s still no case opened. Let me stress again: Yu Menglong’s case. is definitely not an isolated one. His name was used by a princeling. to register shell companies. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">for money laundering. Yu is an entertainer,. yet the business scope of the shell company. included “arms dealer” categories. Why would a film star’s company. be registered for the arms industry? Those items cover defense contractors,. manufacturers, traders, suppliers—etc. All of that is arms-dealer business. In plain terms,. he was made into a white glove for the CCP,. used to launder large sums. Yu gathered relevant evidence,. and that’s why he was silenced. And it wasn’t only Yu’s companies being used like this. Dig a little deeper and you’ll find. many top-tier Chinese celebrities’ companies. are also registered with arms categories—. Jackson Yee,. Guo Junchen,. Gong Jun…. I doubt any of these artists intended their companies. to be listed as arms businesses. You could say the A-list of China’s entertainment world. is firmly under CCP control. No wonder almost no one dares to speak out for Yu. At most, they hint at it in very veiled ways. Here’s a short clip for you:. a minor Chinese actor. who had worked with Yu,. not very famous himself,. went live after the incident and talked about similar things,. saying this kind of thing is rampant in China’s showbiz. After watching the whole thing,. I think what he really wanted to tell viewers. is that the unspoken rules of China’s entertainment industry. are real. If you’re targeted—male or female—. you can run into it,. and there’s nothing you can do. But the CCP. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">is very afraid of this being exposed,. so we need to discuss and understand it more. That’s it for today’s “Intern as a Chinese” session. What did you think of today’s video? Share in the comments below. In the second half,. let’s look at a few “self-own” comments. First one:. “?? Why are you still here? A small fry like you isn’t dead yet?”. I’m healthier than you, of course I’m still here. Next:. “Stop calling yourself a centrist voter—. disgusting.”. This person’s pretty low, too—. has to trash-talk everyone. I used to say I was “pro-Taiwan”:. whoever treats Taiwan well,. I’d support them. I never joined any party. Yet a bunch of people called me a partisan shill. just because I criticized CCP nonsense. So I changed. I thought, fine—. forget it. If Taiwanese want to be Chinese,. I’ll go with the mainstream opinion, okay? If you can’t beat ’em, join ’em. I switched to “centrist voter.”. If Taiwanese don’t want to be Taiwanese. and want to become CCP chives,. then I’ll first take everyone. to intern in Chinese life together. I’m “joining” you, right? And still you come to scold me? Sorry—mind telling me your mother’s maiden name? Someone wants to be a centrist voter—do they need your permission? I never stopped you from being an idiot. Yet you’re here trying to stop me from being a centrist voter. You think you’re way too important. And I’m not just a centrist voter now—. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I’m a centrist troublemaker. Don’t talk politics with me. I’m just asking why KMT mayors over-collected taxes. But won’t hand out cash to everyone. A lot of my friends are waiting. Next comment. A bunch of low-IQ idiots still hyping themselves up. Such clichéd tactics. Those “toads” are as outrageous as it gets. For the past two weeks, my videos. Have been speaking up about Yu Menglong’s wrongful case. Logically,. Yu Menglong,. As a Chinese citizen,. Is your compatriot, Little Pink. He was persecuted—. You should be standing up for him. But you didn’t. Instead, it’s me, a Taiwanese,. Who’s helping spread the information,. Hoping more people will pay attention. Yu Menglong was a kind person. He shouldn’t have died like this. If you won’t help, fine. You can’t even discuss my video’s content—. You just hurl insults and slap on labels,. Calling people “toads,”. Saying everyone’s self-hyping. Yu Menglong was persecuted by CCP elites. And has already “logged out of Life Online.”. What’s there to be excited about? If that’s “exciting” to you,. Then tell me where you live—. We’ll get a group together. To hang you upside down outside a high-rise window,. So you can experience what Yu went through,. And see if you’re still “excited.”. If this can’t raise more awareness,. Then, as I’ve said,. Yu Menglong won’t be the last. Focusing on him is really focusing on yourself. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">To stop such human tragedies from happening again,. Besides me spreading the word,. I also need you, the viewers, to share it widely. This “Little Pink” is obviously. A CCP troll here to whitewash. Any normal person with a conscience. Couldn’t possibly. Stand on the CCP government’s side on this. Next comment. Hilarious. “The green side wing,”. Habitual rumor-mongering and defamation. I’ve already switched to helping everyone understand the real China—. And you still call that the “green side wing”? Also, the legally correct term is “defamation,”. Not “huibang.”. “Huibang” is the wrong term. Are you legally illiterate? So, did you all notice? Whether it’s these haters or troll accounts,. They can’t actually address the video’s content. With relevant comments. They start by slapping on labels,. And once the tag sticks,. They just keep cursing,. Regardless of what the video actually says. But the more they do this,. The more it shows. That what we’re discussing right now. Is exactly what the CCP doesn’t want discussed. Please share the video widely,. So more people can join the discussion. That’s it for today’s video. If you enjoy my videos,. Please like and subscribe. You’re also welcome to join my YouTube channel membership,. Or support the show with a one-time Super Thanks. I’m Potter King. See you in the next video. Bye-bye. Bye. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI</a></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>中國明星公司登記軍火商？于朦朧冤案揭開更大黑幕！</p><p>于朦朧生前喊范小花救我！范小花冷回：打暈刨了</p><p>韓國聲紋機構鑑定：范世錡聲紋吻合99%！</p><p>粉紅特報147期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/Mxlo_SBcPeI/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1> <ul><li>揭露中共權貴如何利用娛樂圈名人進行洗錢及迫害異己的黑幕，呈現中國社會深層的腐敗問題。</li><li>展現國際媒體及海外聲紋鑑定機構在突破中共信息封鎖、挖掘敏感案件真相方面的關鍵作用。</li><li>深入探討中國娛樂產業中「潛規則」的普遍性，以及中共對異議的嚴厲打壓與信息封鎖，揭示中國公民所面臨的言論審查困境。</li></ul><hr /> <h1>摘要</h1> <p>這段影片的<strong>作者</strong>，作為「中國實習生指導員」（AKA 中間選民、波特王），首先對影片更新延遲表達歉意，並說明原因是前一週忙碌及參與花蓮賑災志工。他隨後介紹自己的頻道是「中國版的探索頻道」，旨在帶領觀眾探索真實的中國。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_30.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>余孟龍案的初步曝光與當局壓制</h2> <p><strong>作者</strong>首先跟進了<strong>余孟龍冤案</strong>的後續發展。儘管案件疑點重重，中國警方卻迅速結案，後來發現涉案嫌疑人與中共高官的「紅二代、紅三代」有關。此事件也間接揭露了中國娛樂圈的<strong>潛規則黑幕</strong>。在中國的防火牆內，該話題至今仍被禁止討論，中共當局積極封鎖相關貼文、刪除討論此案的中國網民帳號，試圖徹底抹去余孟龍的存在痕跡。然而，<strong>作者</strong>強調，越是壓制越能引起好奇心，而防火牆外的觀衆持續關注此議題，促使海外媒體持續報導並深入挖掘真相。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_105.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>國際媒體的關注與關鍵證人的消失</h2> <p><strong>作者</strong>指出，透過海外社群的努力，余孟龍案已獲得一定程度的關注。美國雜誌《外交政策》（Foreign Policy）將余孟龍案刊登在其英文頭版，讓國際讀者了解這起冤案，包括這位擁有2700萬粉絲的電影明星如何被中共權貴子弟迫害並一夜之間消失，以及中共政府對此案實施嚴厲的言論審查。余孟龍的母親曾為兒子尋求公道，但隨後與外界失聯，下落不明，很可能已被中共控制。同時，印度《金融快報》（Financial Express）也報導，余孟龍死亡的社區有數百戶家庭面臨威脅性集體出售，居民生活在恐懼之中，記者試圖採訪或調閱監視器畫面時，居民多保持沉默或斷然拒絕，深怕引火上身，成為下一個余孟龍。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_210.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>關鍵錄音檔與范世錡的涉案嫌疑</h2> <p>除了外媒報導，一段據稱是余孟龍死前求救的錄音檔在海外廣為流傳。錄音中包含他被折磨的聲音，余孟龍曾喊出「范小華救我！」顯示現場有位名叫范小華的人，而「范小華」正是<strong>范世錡</strong>的暱稱。<strong>范世錡</strong>與余孟龍是從選秀節目《快樂男聲》一同出道的朋友，<strong>范世錡</strong>也與中共高官蔡奇的私生子辛琦關係密切。錄音檔中，除了余孟龍的求救聲，還捕捉到疑似范世錡在附近呼喊的聲音，命令「吐出來！快點！」「把他打暈，把他剖了！」暗示著肢解余孟龍的意圖。因此，中國網民普遍認為范世錡是這場迫害的共犯之一。儘管范世錡在網上發文聲稱無辜，但說法疑點太多，導致其演唱會的門票銷量慘淡，只售出十五張。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_360.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>聲紋鑑定與中共權貴的黑幕</h2> <p>近期，有中國網民將該錄音檔委託給韓國聲紋比對機構進行鑑定，結果顯示音頻中的聲音與<strong>范世錡</strong>的聲音相似度高達99.57%。這項鑑定結果成為了關鍵證據，但<strong>作者</strong>指出中共顯然無意調查，公安部門持續視而不見，至今未立案。<strong>作者</strong>強調，余孟龍案絕非孤立事件，他的名字被「太子黨」用來註冊<strong>空殼公司進行洗錢</strong>，且公司營業範圍竟包含「<strong>軍火商</strong>」類別，這表明余孟龍被當作中共的「白手套」進行大筆洗錢，而他正是因為掌握了相關證據而遭滅口。更深入挖掘會發現，許多中國頂級藝人的公司也都註冊了軍火相關類別，例如易烊千璽、郭俊辰、龔俊等人，這顯示中國娛樂圈的A咖藝人都牢牢掌握在中共手中，因此幾乎沒有人敢為余孟龍發聲。一位曾與余孟龍合作過的小演員也在直播中暗示，中國演藝圈的<strong>潛規則</strong>非常普遍，無論男女，一旦被盯上，便無力反抗，而中共極力害怕這些黑幕被揭露。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_540.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>作者對惡意評論的回應與呼籲</h2> <p>影片後半段，<strong>作者</strong>針對幾則惡意評論進行了幽默且犀利的回應。面對「小雜碎還沒死」的評論，<strong>作者</strong>回擊自己比對方健康。對於被批評「別再自稱中間選民，噁心」，<strong>作者</strong>解釋自己曾是「挺台派」，因批評中共而被貼標籤，才轉而自稱「中間選民」，並半開玩笑地表示若台灣人想成為「中共韭菜」，他會帶大家一同「實習」；他強調自己現在是「中間搗蛋選民」，不談政治，只質疑國民黨縣市長稅收超徵卻不發錢的政策。面對「一群低能兒還在自嗨」及「井蛙就是狂」的評論，<strong>作者</strong>對比了小粉紅對本國受害者余孟龍的冷漠與對自己的攻擊，指出身為台灣人的他反而幫忙傳播真相，呼籲小粉紅反思。他強調余孟龍被中共權貴迫害離世，有何「自嗨」可言？並反諷若覺得「嗨」，願為其提供類似遭遇。最後，<strong>作者</strong>鄭重呼籲觀眾廣泛分享影片，提高大眾對此類事件的關注，以阻止更多人間悲劇發生，因為關注余孟龍，就是關注我們自己。</p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/Mxlo_SBcPeI_13.jpg" /></p> <hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Sorry, dear viewers. The update is late. I was a bit busy last week. Plus, I went to Hualien to volunteer for disaster relief. So I’m only updating now. Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Satirical Report. I’m your Chinese intern instructor (satirical). AKA the centrist voter. Potter King. A quick reminder for those watching this channel for the first time—. You’re watching a show known as—. The Chinese version of Discovery. Taking you to explore the real China. Today’s video will first follow up on—. The aftermath of Yu Menglong’s wrongful case. Yu Menglong’s cause of death remains mysterious. Chinese police quickly closed the case despite many suspicious points. Later, people discovered that the suspects involved—. Were linked to the “second- and third-generation red” offspring of high-ranking CCP officials. This incident also indirectly exposed—. The dark side of hidden rules in China’s entertainment industry. As a result, within China’s Great Firewall—. The topic is still forbidden to discuss. Facing the CCP authorities—. Who aggressively blocked related posts,. And deleted Chinese netizens’ accounts discussing the case,. Trying to completely erase—. All traces of Yu Menglong’s existence from this world. But the more they suppress it, the more curiosity it arouses. Thanks to you and me outside the firewall—. My dear viewers—. You are important. By continuing to pay attention to this issue—. Overseas media—. Will keep reporting and digging deeper into the truth. I’ve been continuously following the case’s developments—. And noticed that everyone’s discussions weren’t in vain. The topic has maintained a certain level of attention. And foreign media have begun reporting on it. The magazine Foreign Policy—. Published Yu Menglong’s case on its English front page. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Allowing international readers to learn about this wrongful case. They now know—. That this movie star with 27 million followers in China—. Was persecuted and disappeared overnight by children of CCP elites. The CCP government even imposed censorship—. Banning Chinese citizens from discussing or following the case. Yu’s mother once stepped forward—. Trying to seek justice for her son. But she later lost contact with the outside world. Her whereabouts are unknown. It’s highly likely she’s under CCP control. No one knows where she’s being held under house arrest. Meanwhile, India’s Financial Express also reported—. That the neighborhood where Yu Menglong died—. Saw hundreds of homes threatened into collective sales. Residents of the apartments are living in panic. When reporters tried to contact residents—. For interviews or access to surveillance footage,. They either remained silent or flatly refused—. Afraid of bringing trouble upon themselves—. And becoming the next Yu Menglong. Besides the foreign media coverage—. A leaked audio recording went viral overseas—. Said to capture Yu Menglong’s cries for help before his death. The recording contains sounds of him being tortured. You can hear his screams. Yu Menglong shouts—. “Fan Xiaohua, save me!”. He said his hands were losing strength. Which shows that a person named Fan Xiaohua was at the crime scene. And “Fan Xiaohua” happens to be Fan Shiqi’s nickname. Let me give you a bit of background about him. Fan Shiqi and Yu Menglong—. Were friends who debuted together on the show Happy Boys. Fan Shiqi also had close ties with—. Xin Qi, the illegitimate son of senior CCP official Cai Qi—. Their relationship is very close. As for the recording—. Besides Yu Menglong’s cries for help—. It also captured a voice suspected to be Fan Shiqi’s—. Shouting nearby,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">“Spit it out! Hurry!”. Then, “Knock him out, cut him open!”. Urging others to cut open Yu Menglong’s stomach. Thus, Chinese netizens believe Fan Shiqi—. Was one of the accomplices in the persecution. Although Fan Shiqi claimed he was innocent—. Posting explanations online—. It was just too suspicious. So Chinese netizens didn’t believe his statement. Recently, ticket sales for his concert were terrible—. Only fifteen tickets sold. Up to this point—. There wasn’t any crucial evidence against Fan yet. So by the end of September—. He was only considered a suspect. But just these past few days—. Some Chinese citizens took the recording—. And commissioned a Korean voice-print comparison agency. They found that the audio clip. matched Fan Shiqi’s voice with 99.57% similarity. This Chinese netizen originally wanted to debunk rumors,. so they hired a Korean professional voiceprint team to analyze it,. specifically choosing people unfamiliar with Chinese celebrities. to do an unbiased analysis. Unexpectedly, the appraisal showed instead. that the cries for help were from Yu Menglong himself,. and that another man shouting at the scene. was a very high match with Fan Shiqi’s voice—. almost certainly the same person. This appraisal is a highly critical piece of evidence. Investigate it properly. Combined with the building’s CCTV footage,. it could absolutely reconstruct what happened that night. and deliver justice for Yu Menglong. But clearly the CCP has no intention of investigating. Public security continues to look the other way,. and there’s still no case opened. Let me stress again: Yu Menglong’s case. is definitely not an isolated one. His name was used by a princeling. to register shell companies. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">for money laundering. Yu is an entertainer,. yet the business scope of the shell company. included “arms dealer” categories. Why would a film star’s company. be registered for the arms industry? Those items cover defense contractors,. manufacturers, traders, suppliers—etc. All of that is arms-dealer business. In plain terms,. he was made into a white glove for the CCP,. used to launder large sums. Yu gathered relevant evidence,. and that’s why he was silenced. And it wasn’t only Yu’s companies being used like this. Dig a little deeper and you’ll find. many top-tier Chinese celebrities’ companies. are also registered with arms categories—. Jackson Yee,. Guo Junchen,. Gong Jun…. I doubt any of these artists intended their companies. to be listed as arms businesses. You could say the A-list of China’s entertainment world. is firmly under CCP control. No wonder almost no one dares to speak out for Yu. At most, they hint at it in very veiled ways. Here’s a short clip for you:. a minor Chinese actor. who had worked with Yu,. not very famous himself,. went live after the incident and talked about similar things,. saying this kind of thing is rampant in China’s showbiz. After watching the whole thing,. I think what he really wanted to tell viewers. is that the unspoken rules of China’s entertainment industry. are real. If you’re targeted—male or female—. you can run into it,. and there’s nothing you can do. But the CCP. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">is very afraid of this being exposed,. so we need to discuss and understand it more. That’s it for today’s “Intern as a Chinese” session. What did you think of today’s video? Share in the comments below. In the second half,. let’s look at a few “self-own” comments. First one:. “?? Why are you still here? A small fry like you isn’t dead yet?”. I’m healthier than you, of course I’m still here. Next:. “Stop calling yourself a centrist voter—. disgusting.”. This person’s pretty low, too—. has to trash-talk everyone. I used to say I was “pro-Taiwan”:. whoever treats Taiwan well,. I’d support them. I never joined any party. Yet a bunch of people called me a partisan shill. just because I criticized CCP nonsense. So I changed. I thought, fine—. forget it. If Taiwanese want to be Chinese,. I’ll go with the mainstream opinion, okay? If you can’t beat ’em, join ’em. I switched to “centrist voter.”. If Taiwanese don’t want to be Taiwanese. and want to become CCP chives,. then I’ll first take everyone. to intern in Chinese life together. I’m “joining” you, right? And still you come to scold me? Sorry—mind telling me your mother’s maiden name? Someone wants to be a centrist voter—do they need your permission? I never stopped you from being an idiot. Yet you’re here trying to stop me from being a centrist voter. You think you’re way too important. And I’m not just a centrist voter now—. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I’m a centrist troublemaker. Don’t talk politics with me. I’m just asking why KMT mayors over-collected taxes. But won’t hand out cash to everyone. A lot of my friends are waiting. Next comment. A bunch of low-IQ idiots still hyping themselves up. Such clichéd tactics. Those “toads” are as outrageous as it gets. For the past two weeks, my videos. Have been speaking up about Yu Menglong’s wrongful case. Logically,. Yu Menglong,. As a Chinese citizen,. Is your compatriot, Little Pink. He was persecuted—. You should be standing up for him. But you didn’t. Instead, it’s me, a Taiwanese,. Who’s helping spread the information,. Hoping more people will pay attention. Yu Menglong was a kind person. He shouldn’t have died like this. If you won’t help, fine. You can’t even discuss my video’s content—. You just hurl insults and slap on labels,. Calling people “toads,”. Saying everyone’s self-hyping. Yu Menglong was persecuted by CCP elites. And has already “logged out of Life Online.”. What’s there to be excited about? If that’s “exciting” to you,. Then tell me where you live—. We’ll get a group together. To hang you upside down outside a high-rise window,. So you can experience what Yu went through,. And see if you’re still “excited.”. If this can’t raise more awareness,. Then, as I’ve said,. Yu Menglong won’t be the last. Focusing on him is really focusing on yourself. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">To stop such human tragedies from happening again,. Besides me spreading the word,. I also need you, the viewers, to share it widely. This “Little Pink” is obviously. A CCP troll here to whitewash. Any normal person with a conscience. Couldn’t possibly. Stand on the CCP government’s side on this. Next comment. Hilarious. “The green side wing,”. Habitual rumor-mongering and defamation. I’ve already switched to helping everyone understand the real China—. And you still call that the “green side wing”? Also, the legally correct term is “defamation,”. Not “huibang.”. “Huibang” is the wrong term. Are you legally illiterate? So, did you all notice? Whether it’s these haters or troll accounts,. They can’t actually address the video’s content. With relevant comments. They start by slapping on labels,. And once the tag sticks,. They just keep cursing,. Regardless of what the video actually says. But the more they do this,. The more it shows. That what we’re discussing right now. Is exactly what the CCP doesn’t want discussed. Please share the video widely,. So more people can join the discussion. That’s it for today’s video. If you enjoy my videos,. Please like and subscribe. You’re also welcome to join my YouTube channel membership,. Or support the show with a one-time Super Thanks. I’m Potter King. See you in the next video. Bye-bye. Bye. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mxlo_SBcPeI</a></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>中國明星公司登記軍火商？于朦朧冤案揭開更大黑幕！</p><p>于朦朧生前喊范小花救我！范小花冷回：打暈刨了</p><p>韓國聲紋機構鑑定：范世錡聲紋吻合99%！</p><p>粉紅特報147期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Mxlo_SBcPeI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <pubDate>2025-10-07T09:15:06.000Z</pubDate>
    </item><item>
      <title><![CDATA[于朦朧案最新消息！替于發聲慘遭公安逮捕！中國藝人無聲挺于朦朧｜全智賢辱華事件是中共網軍操作出來的｜粉紅特報146期]]></title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ</link>
      <itunes:title><![CDATA[于朦朧案最新消息！替于發聲慘遭公安逮捕！中國藝人無聲挺于朦朧｜全智賢辱華事件是中共網軍操作出來的｜粉紅特報146期]]></itunes:title>
      <itunes:author><![CDATA[波特王好帥]]></itunes:author>
      <itunes:summary>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/g4wKwqw4LhQ/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1> <ul> <li>揭露中共當局如何系統性地壓制異議與敏感案件的討論，特別是涉及高層官員的醜聞。</li> <li>深入分析中國娛樂圈背後的「潛規則」及藝人面臨的言論審查與人身安全威脅。</li> <li>剖析中共透過轉移焦點、引導輿論來維護其統治合法性的宣傳手法。</li> </ul> <hr /> <h1>摘要</h1> <h2>離奇死亡與官方的制式說法</h2> <p>這段影片探討了<strong>余夢龍</strong>的離奇死亡事件，作者指出這不僅是一場人間悲劇，更因中國共產黨（CCP）的審查而完全被封鎖。作者強調，余夢龍的遭遇並非孤立事件，而是與自2015年以來多起年輕人不明死亡案例類似，例如央視主持人<strong>邊策</strong>、演員<strong>喬任梁</strong>、歌手<strong>本兮</strong>、演員<strong>任嬌</strong>以及江西致遠中學的<strong>胡鑫宇</strong>。這些案例的共同點是，中共警方總是以「自殺」或「意外」草草結案，且缺乏可信證據，引發家屬與大眾的普遍質疑。作者舉例，邊策的母親曾質疑官方的吸毒墜樓說法，認為兩包毒品和吸管不可能在16樓墜落後「恰好」整齊落在兒子身旁，更像是有人刻意佈置，她懷疑這是一起涉及權貴的謀殺案。然而，中共警方一如既往地迴避關鍵點，草率結案，如同處理余夢龍案。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_166.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>官方打壓與言論審查</h2> <p>作者在本集節目中，除了更新余夢龍案的最新進展，也旨在讓觀眾了解中共慣用的消音手法。他提到，在余夢龍去世後，中共當局發現境內刪帖封號仍無法壓制輿論，於是發布官方聲明。然而，這份聲明並非為了順應民意展開調查，而是選擇率先打擊討論此案的中國網民。聲明的主要內容是將持續「淨化網絡」，打擊所謂的「謠言」，聲稱余夢龍被設局、毆打、釘指甲、開膛破肚、吊掛等說法均屬捏造，並已懲處三人。作者質疑，在中共警方慣用逼供手段下，這些「認罪」的真實性存疑。當局並未立案調查，而是以幾句簡單的話語敷衍一切，聲稱一切都是捏造，甚至暗示將持續逮捕「造謠者」，這使得等待許久的民眾感到失望。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_347.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>案件疑點與高層涉入傳聞</h2> <p>作者指出，余夢龍案在事發24小時內即被定調為「意外」，甚至其已解散的工作室也代為發表聲明，排除刑事嫌疑。一位擁有兩千多萬粉絲的明星，死因充滿疑點，卻沒有立案、沒有驗屍、沒有告別式、沒有監控畫面，且在死後立刻被火化，這是不尋常的。即便余母親自按指紋發聲，要求為兒子伸張正義，官方仍視為「謠言」。作者強調，此事件最大的爭議點在於，有內部消息洩漏，指向中共高層官員<strong>蔡奇</strong>的私生子涉嫌將余夢龍玩弄致死。這也解釋了為何案件遭到徹底封鎖，甚至連質疑死因都被禁止。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_522.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>發聲者的遭遇與行業潛規則</h2> <p>許多為余夢龍案發聲的人士也面臨了打壓。中國博主兼退役軍人<strong>林北川</strong>，曾發文證實有「不准討論、不准關注、趕緊結案」的指令，隨後在被「傳喚」至北京後便從此失聯，其支持余夢龍的帖子也被刪除。另一位中國女演員<strong>孫琳</strong>，質疑余夢龍的死因，呼籲警方不要結案，但在發帖後數秒即被刪除。她更在當晚外出時遭到不明人士從高處拋擲花盆襲擊，並收到匿名威脅，警告她停止發聲，否則微博將被封鎖。此外，常在牆內評論明星八卦的<strong>向太</strong>，在直播中被問及余夢龍案時，直接表示「我不能說」，但仍暗示中國娛樂圈中男性也面臨「潛規則」。余夢龍的生前好友<strong>華晨宇</strong>，在音樂節上演唱歌曲《好想我回來啊》，並特地更換視覺背景，畫面中隱約暗示一名男子被黑手推落，最終被另一隻手接住。另一位藝人<strong>易烊千璽</strong>則在直播中面無表情地疊石頭，似乎也藉此表達無言的抗議。作者指出，許多中國娛樂圈人士都深知行業內幕，卻無人敢公開發聲。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_810.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>轉移焦點的輿論戰術</h2> <p>當中共壓制余夢龍案的討論時，他們也同時設置了一個新的攻擊目標：韓國演員<strong>全智賢</strong>。起因是Disney+上的一部韓劇《特區》中，全智賢飾演的聯合國大使說了一句「中國為什麼寧願開戰？」這句話被「小粉紅」斷章取義，指責她「辱華」。作者解釋，這句話是全智賢的角色在劇中根據邏輯質疑，因為戰爭爆發的核爆地點也會影響中國，角色其實是在為中國說話，試圖澄清誤解。然而，許多未看過原片的中國網民和「小粉紅」，在網絡水軍的引導下，在牆內發布大量攻擊全智賢的帖子。作者強調，中國互聯網的審查制度決定了哪些議題可以討論，哪些不行。他指出，全智賢這樣一個微不足道的、甚至是捏造出來的事件能夠在內部網絡上迅速發酵，正是因為它得到了中共的允許。中共不希望公眾討論余夢龍這樣被高官迫害的案件，因此透過引導輿論攻擊另一個無辜者全智賢來分散民眾注意力。作者認為，這次的「辱華」事件與過往不同，因為它百分之百是由中共網絡水軍所推動。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_19.jpg" /></p> <hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Yu Menglong’s case is truly a human tragedy. But due to CCP censorship,. discussion inside the Great Firewall is now completely banned. But what can’t be spoken inside,. will be spread by me outside the wall and by all of you viewers. Yu Menglong’s injustice is not an isolated case in China. Let me list a few similar cases since 2015. CCTV host Bian Ce, age 32. Actor Qiao Renliang, age 29. Singer Ben Xi, age 22. Actress Ren Jiao, age 29. Including earlier, at Zhiyuan Middle School in Jiangxi. Hu Xinyu, only 15 years old. All died mysteriously at a young age. Yet the CCP police gave the same explanation:. “Su*cide” or “accident,”. without credible evidence. Which triggered widespread doubt among families and the public. For example, Bian Ce’s mother. also questioned her son’s cause of death,. saying her child never touched drugs. Even just an hour before the incident,. he was still on the phone with her. As for Beijing police. claiming her son died from drug use after falling,. with two small packets of drugs and straws beside him,. she felt deeply puzzled. She asked: after falling from the 16th floor,. those two packets of drugs and straws. just happened to land neatly right beside him? This makes no sense at all. It’s more like someone deliberately placed them there. She suspected it was a murder involving powerful figures. But the CCP police simply. avoided the key points,. closed the case hastily,. just like in Yu Menglong’s case. So when CCP announcements lack credibility,. the public tends to believe unofficial reports. Yet only hard evidence and truth. can truly stop rumors. But the police have yet to release any. Instead, they accuse the public. of “spreading rumors” and “fabricating lies,”. completely disregarding human life. Oh right—. Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink News Report. If you’re watching this show for the first time,. just a reminder—. you’re now watching. what’s called the “Chinese version of Discovery.”. And I’m your internship mentor in China,. AKA “centrist voter,”. Potter King. If you don’t mind being a Chinese Taiwanese,. congratulations—. you’ve found this program. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Remember to subscribe,. and let’s take a look at the real China together. Last episode we talked about Yu Menglong’s case. For those who haven’t watched that video,. you can check it out later,. so more people can understand this case. Because the discussion heat on this issue. is already fading away. A big reason behind this. is the CCP government’s suppression. So today I’d like to take this opportunity. to update you on Yu Menglong’s case,. and at the same time. let everyone understand. the CCP’s usual methods of silencing speech. Through real-life cases,. we’ll see how the CCP systematically controls. the issues they don’t want people to discuss. After a one-minute ad,. Following Yu Menglong’s death,. the CCP saw that deleting posts and banning accounts inside the wall. still couldn’t suppress public opinion. So the authorities finally spoke up. But not to follow public opinion. by opening a proper investigation. The CCP didn’t intend to reveal the truth for Yu Menglong. Instead, they chose to crack down first. on Chinese netizens discussing the case. Let’s take a look at the official statement. It’s a long one—. but the main point is clear:. they will continue “cleansing the internet”. to crack down on so-called rumors. Regarding Yu’s fall from a building,. they claim some people just wanted attention,. maliciously spreading false information online,. and producing fake videos. They said three people have been punished by law. Including claims that Yu was set up, assaulted, and then fell,. that he was hung from a high building,. had his nails pulled out,. was cut open and thrown down,. and that his mother was being controlled, etc. They said these were all lies. They also said the arrested people had confessed. But given the CCP police’s usual ways,. the number of times they force confessions—. I don’t need to spell it out. We can see that. the authorities didn’t even open a case to investigate,. but instead used a few simple lines. to gloss over everything,. saying it was all fabricated,. and even hinting at threats,. saying they’ll keep arresting those who “spread rumors.”. After everyone waited so long,. the first notice they issued. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">turned out to be a crackdown. on all Chinese netizens seeking justice for Yu. After reading this police bulletin,. I felt they didn’t need to write that long,. because they never intended to handle it. Next time they could just write four words:. “What can you do?”. After the death occurred,. within 24 hours they set the line:. it was an accident. And even the studio that Yu himself had already dissolved. issued a statement on his behalf,. saying criminal suspicion had been ruled out. A film star with over twenty million followers in China. dies in a case full of doubts,. yet there’s no case opened,. no autopsy,. no farewell ceremony,. no surveillance footage. Yu wasn’t some heinous criminal,. nor did he die of an infectious disease,. yet right after his death. he was immediately sent for cremation. To silence an artist with no wrongdoing. to this extent—. is that normal? Even Yu’s mother issued a statement herself,. with her fingerprint,. asking everyone to seek justice for her son,. yet in the authorities’ eyes that’s “rumor” too. It makes no sense. Allow me to point out something:. though there’s been lots of messy online “exposés,”. they’re chaotic—. but the core of this whole matter,. the biggest controversy,. is that insiders’ leaks all indicate. involvement of senior CCP official Cai Qi. They allege Cai Qi’s illegitimate son. toyed with Yu to death. Hence the total blackout on Yu,. and even questioning his cause of death is forbidden. Beyond the obvious total blackout. that everyone can see,. another Chinese blogger,. Lin Beichuan, came forward to confirm,. a retired Chinese soldier. He later spoke up for Yu inside the wall,. and now he’s disappeared. He had posted, revealing that. orders had been handed down from somewhere. to “pay no attention” to Yu’s case,. not to discuss it,. and to settle it quickly. His last post said he. was called to Beijing from Hong Kong,. stressing he was “called,”. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">so he couldn’t refuse. But after he was called to Beijing on September 19,. someone who used to post almost daily. up to now—. the cutoff for this video is the 25th—. he hasn’t posted again. Even his posts supporting Yu. have been deleted. Another Chinese actress, Sun Lin,. also questioned Yu’s cause of death,. pleading with the police not to close the case. There are still many doubts to verify. But soon after her post went up,. it was deleted in seconds. On the night of the 21st, when she went out,. she was attacked:. someone threw a flowerpot from above, hitting her head,. and she received anonymous threats,. warning her. to stop speaking up,. or her Weibo would be shut down. They said this was just a “small lesson.”. Another key indicator:. Xiang Tai, who often gossips about celebrities inside the wall,. didn’t dare comment on Yu. Chinese netizens flooded her livestream with,. “Help Yu.”. She replied directly:. “Stop spamming.”. I can’t talk about this. But although she avoided mentioning Yu Menglong,. she still had things to say about the unspoken rules. in China’s entertainment industry. She hinted that. men face this too. It seemed like she said nothing,. yet it felt like she said everything. And Yu’s close friend while alive, Hua Chenyu,. recently, at the Foshan Music Festival,. performed his own song,. “I Really Wish I Could Come Back,”. and specifically changed to a new visual backdrop. The visuals subtly suggested. a man being thrown downward by a black hand,. and by the end, another hand. catches the falling man. Another Chinese artist, Jackson Yee (Yi Yangqianxi),. also suddenly went live—. but didn’t interact with viewers at all,. just stacked stones with a somber look. Let me show you a short clip,. so you can watch his expression change. You can see that many Chinese entertainers. know the industry’s inside stories,. yet no one dares to speak up. When the CCP suppressed discussion of Yu’s case,. besides banning netizens from discussing it,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">they also set up a new target to attack—. Jun Ji-hyun. Let me briefly explain the Jun Ji-hyun issue. There’s a new K-drama on Disney+. called “Storm Zone.”. In it, Jun Ji-hyun plays a UN ambassador. There’s a line that says,. “Why would China prefer war?”. The “little pinks” seized on that and started hurling abuse,. accusing her of “insulting China.”. But the point is,. the line Jun says in the show—. “Why would China prefer war?”—. is her character questioning it. Because in this spy-thriller’s setup,. if war breaks out,. the nuclear blast location. would also affect China in the story. So Jun’s character. says that line. Her character’s logic. is that war would not benefit China,. so she finds the push for war suspicious. Sorry for the spoiler. But in the show, Jun Ji-hyun. actually seeks help from China’s ambassador. In fact, her character speaks up for China. She’s trying to clear up a misunderstanding. But many who never watched the original,. Chinese netizens and “little pinks,”. were blindly steered by bot armies. As a result, inside the firewall. there were tons of posts attacking Jun Ji-hyun. Allow me to remind everyone again:. China’s internet is censored. What you may discuss,. and what you may not,. as Yu’s case already showed,. should be clear to you. So think about this:. why can such a trivial matter about Jun,. and one fabricated at that,. blow up across the internal internet? Exactly. It’s just as you suspect:. it’s allowed by the CCP. Inside the wall, it’s rule by men. The CCP doesn’t want the public discussing. Yu, persecuted by high-ranking officials,. so they want you distracted. by attacking another innocent—Jun Ji-hyun. I must say, this so-called “insulting China” case. is different from past ones. I’ve covered many such incidents before,. where the “little pinks” lashed out,. but this time it’s different,. because this is 100%. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">driven by CCP cyber-armies. Take a look at these attack pieces:. they claim she read the script, so she’s not innocent; that the show smears China as warmongering; that it uses fabric with yellow stars as a carpet; that the villains speak Chinese; and that it vilifies Dalian and Hong Kong, etc. These astroturf marketing accounts. are the ones truly smearing others. If you’ve watched the show,. you’ll know. the starry carpet scene is set in the White House,. and the crew used it to recreate the real setting. 299. Take a look at President Biden’s earlier video tour. See? You saw it, right? The real White House carpet does have stars. And that’s because the U.S. flag. itself has stars, okay? Also, the villains in that show are Koreans themselves,. not Chinese. Nor does it smear Dalian or Hong Kong or anything like that. But the posts inside the firewall. keep churning out piece after piece,. sounding all “credible,”. and the narrative gets steered. Uninformed Chinese netizens. are used to attack Jun Ji-hyun,. thinking they’re righteous. I find it ironic. Stirred-up netizens go after Jun Ji-hyun. while forgetting their fellow Chinese. are the ones being persecuted. Yu Menglong hadn’t even been laid to rest,. before CCP bot armies spun the story away,. and the authorities suppressed public opinion. From this case you should understand:. Menglong won’t be the last,. and neither will Jun Ji-hyun be the only target. The CCP is good at manufacturing enemies. for the public to attack,. to divert attention from what’s happening at home. Taking a step back, though,. if the “little pinks” truly think Jun insulted China,. she’s just acting,. she didn’t write the script. If you’re really that upset,. Chinese netizens shouldn’t support the Korea-ban; I suggest doing the opposite:. the “little pinks” should fund Korean artists. to shoot pro-CCP patriotic films. Don’t you say the motherland is powerful? Whatever the fee is,. have Chinese producers. pay a hundred times more and hire Jun Ji-hyun,. and have her, in a patriotic CCP film,. shout “I love China.”. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Wouldn’t that be great? Otherwise, why are you yelling while watching pirated copies? So, what did you think of today’s video? Feel free to share in the comments below. In the latter part of today’s video,. let me show you a few. “self-own” comments on the channel. “I’m watching from beyond the wall, but I’m not a little pink.”. “So don’t call everyone who climbs the wall a little pink.”. Looks like you’re new here. Let me remind you of one thing:. if it’s not your seat,. don’t sit in it. The wording I use on this show. is carefully considered. I strive to be precise. Of course I know. there are Chinese people we can talk to. and there are party-blind “little pinks.”. So when I refer to Chinese people,. I say “Chinese netizens outside the wall.”. Likewise, when I mean the little pinks,. I say “little pinks outside the wall.”. Clear enough? Lately I kind of feel. Taiwan and China have flipped. I’m seeing many Chinese. gradually waking up,. while some in Taiwan. are moving closer to the CCP. Like this one:. “Isn’t Taiwan part of China?”. “Why can Taiwan talk about it,. but people inside the wall can’t?”. That made me think they watched my video. and started to reflect. Next one:. “It’s meaningless to elevate an isolated case to a national level.”. “Which country doesn’t have money–power–sex deals?”. With Yu Menglong wronged like that,. you still say such nonsense? If you’re not a CCP troll. sent here on a cleanup mission,. I’d suspect you might be one of the perpetrators. Using a burner account to comment here. CCP bot armies, stop muddying the waters. with “other countries do it too,”. or “don’t make it a national issue.”. That’s whitewashing. Back to the core question:. let me ask you—. who took Yu Menglong’s life? Multiple pieces of evidence and insider leaks. point straight to a senior official’s child. persecuted by the red second and third generations. Why do they dare do this? Because they control China,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">and officials shield one another. They know they have the CCP regime backing them. That’s why they dare to do whatever they want inside the wall,. and then suppress Chinese netizens afterward,. not allowing them to speak up for Yu Menglong. The ones doing all this. are the CCP authorities. So you’re saying this matter. is something I alone elevated to a national level? Absolutely not. The ones who persecuted Yu Menglong. are the CCP authorities. It’s the CCP government suppressing the Chinese people. It’s your state persecuting your fellow citizens. Every country has bad actors,. but wrongdoers in other countries. can they act like the CCP princelings? Suppose this happened in Taiwan:. an official’s illegitimate son colludes with a celebrity. to abuse another star—. it would absolutely rock the country. The media would report it morning, noon, night—and late-night. Taiwanese netizens would share and discuss it online,. and they wouldn’t be purged or banned. In the end, besides that politician. getting blasted out of office,. people would support jailing the perpetrators. Prosecutors would open a case. So compared with Yu Menglong’s case,. where the CCP deployed state machinery. to suppress, persecute, and silence,. it’s entirely different. Ha—trying to cover up the SET executive’s son assaulting a woman? Using lies to cover facts—. so “humane,” huh? I’m speechless. This idiot is here to whitewash too,. and trying to slap a label on me. The case of SET vice GM’s son, Gong Yiting, assaulting an actress—. what’s there to be afraid to talk about? If you dared say that to my face,. I’d land a full combo on you. People like you are scum. Why are you conflating two real tragedies? Yu Menglong has already “logged off,”. and you say I’m spreading rumors? What’s wrong with you? Besides, in my work. I’ve collaborated with Chiang Tsu-ping,. whom I respect deeply,. and she’s very kind in private. So regarding what she went through,. I’m really saddened,. and I truly hope Taiwan’s judiciary. gives her justice. The point is—this case. has been formally opened in Taiwan. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">You can look up the news online. Gong Yiting is currently barred from leaving the country. People can discuss it online freely. This is completely different from Yu Menglong’s case. Tying the two together—. all I can say is, if you’re not using your brain,. go donate it. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ</a></p><p>點擊優惠連結👉<a href="https://surfshark.com/potterking">https://surfshark.com/potterking</a> </p><p>或用優惠碼 [potterking] 以獲得額外 4 個月 Surfshark 服務！</p><p></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>于朦朧案最新消息！替于朦朧發聲慘遭公安逮捕！中國藝人無聲挺于朦朧</p><p>全智賢因為一句話辱華？</p><p>分析中共網軍如何製造辱華事件煽動中國人</p><p>粉紅特報146期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </itunes:summary>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/g4wKwqw4LhQ/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1> <ul> <li>揭露中共當局如何系統性地壓制異議與敏感案件的討論，特別是涉及高層官員的醜聞。</li> <li>深入分析中國娛樂圈背後的「潛規則」及藝人面臨的言論審查與人身安全威脅。</li> <li>剖析中共透過轉移焦點、引導輿論來維護其統治合法性的宣傳手法。</li> </ul> <hr /> <h1>摘要</h1> <h2>離奇死亡與官方的制式說法</h2> <p>這段影片探討了<strong>余夢龍</strong>的離奇死亡事件，作者指出這不僅是一場人間悲劇，更因中國共產黨（CCP）的審查而完全被封鎖。作者強調，余夢龍的遭遇並非孤立事件，而是與自2015年以來多起年輕人不明死亡案例類似，例如央視主持人<strong>邊策</strong>、演員<strong>喬任梁</strong>、歌手<strong>本兮</strong>、演員<strong>任嬌</strong>以及江西致遠中學的<strong>胡鑫宇</strong>。這些案例的共同點是，中共警方總是以「自殺」或「意外」草草結案，且缺乏可信證據，引發家屬與大眾的普遍質疑。作者舉例，邊策的母親曾質疑官方的吸毒墜樓說法，認為兩包毒品和吸管不可能在16樓墜落後「恰好」整齊落在兒子身旁，更像是有人刻意佈置，她懷疑這是一起涉及權貴的謀殺案。然而，中共警方一如既往地迴避關鍵點，草率結案，如同處理余夢龍案。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_166.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>官方打壓與言論審查</h2> <p>作者在本集節目中，除了更新余夢龍案的最新進展，也旨在讓觀眾了解中共慣用的消音手法。他提到，在余夢龍去世後，中共當局發現境內刪帖封號仍無法壓制輿論，於是發布官方聲明。然而，這份聲明並非為了順應民意展開調查，而是選擇率先打擊討論此案的中國網民。聲明的主要內容是將持續「淨化網絡」，打擊所謂的「謠言」，聲稱余夢龍被設局、毆打、釘指甲、開膛破肚、吊掛等說法均屬捏造，並已懲處三人。作者質疑，在中共警方慣用逼供手段下，這些「認罪」的真實性存疑。當局並未立案調查，而是以幾句簡單的話語敷衍一切，聲稱一切都是捏造，甚至暗示將持續逮捕「造謠者」，這使得等待許久的民眾感到失望。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_347.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>案件疑點與高層涉入傳聞</h2> <p>作者指出，余夢龍案在事發24小時內即被定調為「意外」，甚至其已解散的工作室也代為發表聲明，排除刑事嫌疑。一位擁有兩千多萬粉絲的明星，死因充滿疑點，卻沒有立案、沒有驗屍、沒有告別式、沒有監控畫面，且在死後立刻被火化，這是不尋常的。即便余母親自按指紋發聲，要求為兒子伸張正義，官方仍視為「謠言」。作者強調，此事件最大的爭議點在於，有內部消息洩漏，指向中共高層官員<strong>蔡奇</strong>的私生子涉嫌將余夢龍玩弄致死。這也解釋了為何案件遭到徹底封鎖，甚至連質疑死因都被禁止。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_522.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>發聲者的遭遇與行業潛規則</h2> <p>許多為余夢龍案發聲的人士也面臨了打壓。中國博主兼退役軍人<strong>林北川</strong>，曾發文證實有「不准討論、不准關注、趕緊結案」的指令，隨後在被「傳喚」至北京後便從此失聯，其支持余夢龍的帖子也被刪除。另一位中國女演員<strong>孫琳</strong>，質疑余夢龍的死因，呼籲警方不要結案，但在發帖後數秒即被刪除。她更在當晚外出時遭到不明人士從高處拋擲花盆襲擊，並收到匿名威脅，警告她停止發聲，否則微博將被封鎖。此外，常在牆內評論明星八卦的<strong>向太</strong>，在直播中被問及余夢龍案時，直接表示「我不能說」，但仍暗示中國娛樂圈中男性也面臨「潛規則」。余夢龍的生前好友<strong>華晨宇</strong>，在音樂節上演唱歌曲《好想我回來啊》，並特地更換視覺背景，畫面中隱約暗示一名男子被黑手推落，最終被另一隻手接住。另一位藝人<strong>易烊千璽</strong>則在直播中面無表情地疊石頭，似乎也藉此表達無言的抗議。作者指出，許多中國娛樂圈人士都深知行業內幕，卻無人敢公開發聲。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_810.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>轉移焦點的輿論戰術</h2> <p>當中共壓制余夢龍案的討論時，他們也同時設置了一個新的攻擊目標：韓國演員<strong>全智賢</strong>。起因是Disney+上的一部韓劇《特區》中，全智賢飾演的聯合國大使說了一句「中國為什麼寧願開戰？」這句話被「小粉紅」斷章取義，指責她「辱華」。作者解釋，這句話是全智賢的角色在劇中根據邏輯質疑，因為戰爭爆發的核爆地點也會影響中國，角色其實是在為中國說話，試圖澄清誤解。然而，許多未看過原片的中國網民和「小粉紅」，在網絡水軍的引導下，在牆內發布大量攻擊全智賢的帖子。作者強調，中國互聯網的審查制度決定了哪些議題可以討論，哪些不行。他指出，全智賢這樣一個微不足道的、甚至是捏造出來的事件能夠在內部網絡上迅速發酵，正是因為它得到了中共的允許。中共不希望公眾討論余夢龍這樣被高官迫害的案件，因此透過引導輿論攻擊另一個無辜者全智賢來分散民眾注意力。作者認為，這次的「辱華」事件與過往不同，因為它百分之百是由中共網絡水軍所推動。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_19.jpg" /></p> <hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Yu Menglong’s case is truly a human tragedy. But due to CCP censorship,. discussion inside the Great Firewall is now completely banned. But what can’t be spoken inside,. will be spread by me outside the wall and by all of you viewers. Yu Menglong’s injustice is not an isolated case in China. Let me list a few similar cases since 2015. CCTV host Bian Ce, age 32. Actor Qiao Renliang, age 29. Singer Ben Xi, age 22. Actress Ren Jiao, age 29. Including earlier, at Zhiyuan Middle School in Jiangxi. Hu Xinyu, only 15 years old. All died mysteriously at a young age. Yet the CCP police gave the same explanation:. “Su*cide” or “accident,”. without credible evidence. Which triggered widespread doubt among families and the public. For example, Bian Ce’s mother. also questioned her son’s cause of death,. saying her child never touched drugs. Even just an hour before the incident,. he was still on the phone with her. As for Beijing police. claiming her son died from drug use after falling,. with two small packets of drugs and straws beside him,. she felt deeply puzzled. She asked: after falling from the 16th floor,. those two packets of drugs and straws. just happened to land neatly right beside him? This makes no sense at all. It’s more like someone deliberately placed them there. She suspected it was a murder involving powerful figures. But the CCP police simply. avoided the key points,. closed the case hastily,. just like in Yu Menglong’s case. So when CCP announcements lack credibility,. the public tends to believe unofficial reports. Yet only hard evidence and truth. can truly stop rumors. But the police have yet to release any. Instead, they accuse the public. of “spreading rumors” and “fabricating lies,”. completely disregarding human life. Oh right—. Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink News Report. If you’re watching this show for the first time,. just a reminder—. you’re now watching. what’s called the “Chinese version of Discovery.”. And I’m your internship mentor in China,. AKA “centrist voter,”. Potter King. If you don’t mind being a Chinese Taiwanese,. congratulations—. you’ve found this program. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Remember to subscribe,. and let’s take a look at the real China together. Last episode we talked about Yu Menglong’s case. For those who haven’t watched that video,. you can check it out later,. so more people can understand this case. Because the discussion heat on this issue. is already fading away. A big reason behind this. is the CCP government’s suppression. So today I’d like to take this opportunity. to update you on Yu Menglong’s case,. and at the same time. let everyone understand. the CCP’s usual methods of silencing speech. Through real-life cases,. we’ll see how the CCP systematically controls. the issues they don’t want people to discuss. After a one-minute ad,. Following Yu Menglong’s death,. the CCP saw that deleting posts and banning accounts inside the wall. still couldn’t suppress public opinion. So the authorities finally spoke up. But not to follow public opinion. by opening a proper investigation. The CCP didn’t intend to reveal the truth for Yu Menglong. Instead, they chose to crack down first. on Chinese netizens discussing the case. Let’s take a look at the official statement. It’s a long one—. but the main point is clear:. they will continue “cleansing the internet”. to crack down on so-called rumors. Regarding Yu’s fall from a building,. they claim some people just wanted attention,. maliciously spreading false information online,. and producing fake videos. They said three people have been punished by law. Including claims that Yu was set up, assaulted, and then fell,. that he was hung from a high building,. had his nails pulled out,. was cut open and thrown down,. and that his mother was being controlled, etc. They said these were all lies. They also said the arrested people had confessed. But given the CCP police’s usual ways,. the number of times they force confessions—. I don’t need to spell it out. We can see that. the authorities didn’t even open a case to investigate,. but instead used a few simple lines. to gloss over everything,. saying it was all fabricated,. and even hinting at threats,. saying they’ll keep arresting those who “spread rumors.”. After everyone waited so long,. the first notice they issued. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">turned out to be a crackdown. on all Chinese netizens seeking justice for Yu. After reading this police bulletin,. I felt they didn’t need to write that long,. because they never intended to handle it. Next time they could just write four words:. “What can you do?”. After the death occurred,. within 24 hours they set the line:. it was an accident. And even the studio that Yu himself had already dissolved. issued a statement on his behalf,. saying criminal suspicion had been ruled out. A film star with over twenty million followers in China. dies in a case full of doubts,. yet there’s no case opened,. no autopsy,. no farewell ceremony,. no surveillance footage. Yu wasn’t some heinous criminal,. nor did he die of an infectious disease,. yet right after his death. he was immediately sent for cremation. To silence an artist with no wrongdoing. to this extent—. is that normal? Even Yu’s mother issued a statement herself,. with her fingerprint,. asking everyone to seek justice for her son,. yet in the authorities’ eyes that’s “rumor” too. It makes no sense. Allow me to point out something:. though there’s been lots of messy online “exposés,”. they’re chaotic—. but the core of this whole matter,. the biggest controversy,. is that insiders’ leaks all indicate. involvement of senior CCP official Cai Qi. They allege Cai Qi’s illegitimate son. toyed with Yu to death. Hence the total blackout on Yu,. and even questioning his cause of death is forbidden. Beyond the obvious total blackout. that everyone can see,. another Chinese blogger,. Lin Beichuan, came forward to confirm,. a retired Chinese soldier. He later spoke up for Yu inside the wall,. and now he’s disappeared. He had posted, revealing that. orders had been handed down from somewhere. to “pay no attention” to Yu’s case,. not to discuss it,. and to settle it quickly. His last post said he. was called to Beijing from Hong Kong,. stressing he was “called,”. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">so he couldn’t refuse. But after he was called to Beijing on September 19,. someone who used to post almost daily. up to now—. the cutoff for this video is the 25th—. he hasn’t posted again. Even his posts supporting Yu. have been deleted. Another Chinese actress, Sun Lin,. also questioned Yu’s cause of death,. pleading with the police not to close the case. There are still many doubts to verify. But soon after her post went up,. it was deleted in seconds. On the night of the 21st, when she went out,. she was attacked:. someone threw a flowerpot from above, hitting her head,. and she received anonymous threats,. warning her. to stop speaking up,. or her Weibo would be shut down. They said this was just a “small lesson.”. Another key indicator:. Xiang Tai, who often gossips about celebrities inside the wall,. didn’t dare comment on Yu. Chinese netizens flooded her livestream with,. “Help Yu.”. She replied directly:. “Stop spamming.”. I can’t talk about this. But although she avoided mentioning Yu Menglong,. she still had things to say about the unspoken rules. in China’s entertainment industry. She hinted that. men face this too. It seemed like she said nothing,. yet it felt like she said everything. And Yu’s close friend while alive, Hua Chenyu,. recently, at the Foshan Music Festival,. performed his own song,. “I Really Wish I Could Come Back,”. and specifically changed to a new visual backdrop. The visuals subtly suggested. a man being thrown downward by a black hand,. and by the end, another hand. catches the falling man. Another Chinese artist, Jackson Yee (Yi Yangqianxi),. also suddenly went live—. but didn’t interact with viewers at all,. just stacked stones with a somber look. Let me show you a short clip,. so you can watch his expression change. You can see that many Chinese entertainers. know the industry’s inside stories,. yet no one dares to speak up. When the CCP suppressed discussion of Yu’s case,. besides banning netizens from discussing it,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">they also set up a new target to attack—. Jun Ji-hyun. Let me briefly explain the Jun Ji-hyun issue. There’s a new K-drama on Disney+. called “Storm Zone.”. In it, Jun Ji-hyun plays a UN ambassador. There’s a line that says,. “Why would China prefer war?”. The “little pinks” seized on that and started hurling abuse,. accusing her of “insulting China.”. But the point is,. the line Jun says in the show—. “Why would China prefer war?”—. is her character questioning it. Because in this spy-thriller’s setup,. if war breaks out,. the nuclear blast location. would also affect China in the story. So Jun’s character. says that line. Her character’s logic. is that war would not benefit China,. so she finds the push for war suspicious. Sorry for the spoiler. But in the show, Jun Ji-hyun. actually seeks help from China’s ambassador. In fact, her character speaks up for China. She’s trying to clear up a misunderstanding. But many who never watched the original,. Chinese netizens and “little pinks,”. were blindly steered by bot armies. As a result, inside the firewall. there were tons of posts attacking Jun Ji-hyun. Allow me to remind everyone again:. China’s internet is censored. What you may discuss,. and what you may not,. as Yu’s case already showed,. should be clear to you. So think about this:. why can such a trivial matter about Jun,. and one fabricated at that,. blow up across the internal internet? Exactly. It’s just as you suspect:. it’s allowed by the CCP. Inside the wall, it’s rule by men. The CCP doesn’t want the public discussing. Yu, persecuted by high-ranking officials,. so they want you distracted. by attacking another innocent—Jun Ji-hyun. I must say, this so-called “insulting China” case. is different from past ones. I’ve covered many such incidents before,. where the “little pinks” lashed out,. but this time it’s different,. because this is 100%. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">driven by CCP cyber-armies. Take a look at these attack pieces:. they claim she read the script, so she’s not innocent; that the show smears China as warmongering; that it uses fabric with yellow stars as a carpet; that the villains speak Chinese; and that it vilifies Dalian and Hong Kong, etc. These astroturf marketing accounts. are the ones truly smearing others. If you’ve watched the show,. you’ll know. the starry carpet scene is set in the White House,. and the crew used it to recreate the real setting. 299. Take a look at President Biden’s earlier video tour. See? You saw it, right? The real White House carpet does have stars. And that’s because the U.S. flag. itself has stars, okay? Also, the villains in that show are Koreans themselves,. not Chinese. Nor does it smear Dalian or Hong Kong or anything like that. But the posts inside the firewall. keep churning out piece after piece,. sounding all “credible,”. and the narrative gets steered. Uninformed Chinese netizens. are used to attack Jun Ji-hyun,. thinking they’re righteous. I find it ironic. Stirred-up netizens go after Jun Ji-hyun. while forgetting their fellow Chinese. are the ones being persecuted. Yu Menglong hadn’t even been laid to rest,. before CCP bot armies spun the story away,. and the authorities suppressed public opinion. From this case you should understand:. Menglong won’t be the last,. and neither will Jun Ji-hyun be the only target. The CCP is good at manufacturing enemies. for the public to attack,. to divert attention from what’s happening at home. Taking a step back, though,. if the “little pinks” truly think Jun insulted China,. she’s just acting,. she didn’t write the script. If you’re really that upset,. Chinese netizens shouldn’t support the Korea-ban; I suggest doing the opposite:. the “little pinks” should fund Korean artists. to shoot pro-CCP patriotic films. Don’t you say the motherland is powerful? Whatever the fee is,. have Chinese producers. pay a hundred times more and hire Jun Ji-hyun,. and have her, in a patriotic CCP film,. shout “I love China.”. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Wouldn’t that be great? Otherwise, why are you yelling while watching pirated copies? So, what did you think of today’s video? Feel free to share in the comments below. In the latter part of today’s video,. let me show you a few. “self-own” comments on the channel. “I’m watching from beyond the wall, but I’m not a little pink.”. “So don’t call everyone who climbs the wall a little pink.”. Looks like you’re new here. Let me remind you of one thing:. if it’s not your seat,. don’t sit in it. The wording I use on this show. is carefully considered. I strive to be precise. Of course I know. there are Chinese people we can talk to. and there are party-blind “little pinks.”. So when I refer to Chinese people,. I say “Chinese netizens outside the wall.”. Likewise, when I mean the little pinks,. I say “little pinks outside the wall.”. Clear enough? Lately I kind of feel. Taiwan and China have flipped. I’m seeing many Chinese. gradually waking up,. while some in Taiwan. are moving closer to the CCP. Like this one:. “Isn’t Taiwan part of China?”. “Why can Taiwan talk about it,. but people inside the wall can’t?”. That made me think they watched my video. and started to reflect. Next one:. “It’s meaningless to elevate an isolated case to a national level.”. “Which country doesn’t have money–power–sex deals?”. With Yu Menglong wronged like that,. you still say such nonsense? If you’re not a CCP troll. sent here on a cleanup mission,. I’d suspect you might be one of the perpetrators. Using a burner account to comment here. CCP bot armies, stop muddying the waters. with “other countries do it too,”. or “don’t make it a national issue.”. That’s whitewashing. Back to the core question:. let me ask you—. who took Yu Menglong’s life? Multiple pieces of evidence and insider leaks. point straight to a senior official’s child. persecuted by the red second and third generations. Why do they dare do this? Because they control China,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">and officials shield one another. They know they have the CCP regime backing them. That’s why they dare to do whatever they want inside the wall,. and then suppress Chinese netizens afterward,. not allowing them to speak up for Yu Menglong. The ones doing all this. are the CCP authorities. So you’re saying this matter. is something I alone elevated to a national level? Absolutely not. The ones who persecuted Yu Menglong. are the CCP authorities. It’s the CCP government suppressing the Chinese people. It’s your state persecuting your fellow citizens. Every country has bad actors,. but wrongdoers in other countries. can they act like the CCP princelings? Suppose this happened in Taiwan:. an official’s illegitimate son colludes with a celebrity. to abuse another star—. it would absolutely rock the country. The media would report it morning, noon, night—and late-night. Taiwanese netizens would share and discuss it online,. and they wouldn’t be purged or banned. In the end, besides that politician. getting blasted out of office,. people would support jailing the perpetrators. Prosecutors would open a case. So compared with Yu Menglong’s case,. where the CCP deployed state machinery. to suppress, persecute, and silence,. it’s entirely different. Ha—trying to cover up the SET executive’s son assaulting a woman? Using lies to cover facts—. so “humane,” huh? I’m speechless. This idiot is here to whitewash too,. and trying to slap a label on me. The case of SET vice GM’s son, Gong Yiting, assaulting an actress—. what’s there to be afraid to talk about? If you dared say that to my face,. I’d land a full combo on you. People like you are scum. Why are you conflating two real tragedies? Yu Menglong has already “logged off,”. and you say I’m spreading rumors? What’s wrong with you? Besides, in my work. I’ve collaborated with Chiang Tsu-ping,. whom I respect deeply,. and she’s very kind in private. So regarding what she went through,. I’m really saddened,. and I truly hope Taiwan’s judiciary. gives her justice. The point is—this case. has been formally opened in Taiwan. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">You can look up the news online. Gong Yiting is currently barred from leaving the country. People can discuss it online freely. This is completely different from Yu Menglong’s case. Tying the two together—. all I can say is, if you’re not using your brain,. go donate it. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ</a></p><p>點擊優惠連結👉<a href="https://surfshark.com/potterking">https://surfshark.com/potterking</a> </p><p>或用優惠碼 [potterking] 以獲得額外 4 個月 Surfshark 服務！</p><p></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>于朦朧案最新消息！替于朦朧發聲慘遭公安逮捕！中國藝人無聲挺于朦朧</p><p>全智賢因為一句話辱華？</p><p>分析中共網軍如何製造辱華事件煽動中國人</p><p>粉紅特報146期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/g4wKwqw4LhQ/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1> <ul> <li>揭露中共當局如何系統性地壓制異議與敏感案件的討論，特別是涉及高層官員的醜聞。</li> <li>深入分析中國娛樂圈背後的「潛規則」及藝人面臨的言論審查與人身安全威脅。</li> <li>剖析中共透過轉移焦點、引導輿論來維護其統治合法性的宣傳手法。</li> </ul> <hr /> <h1>摘要</h1> <h2>離奇死亡與官方的制式說法</h2> <p>這段影片探討了<strong>余夢龍</strong>的離奇死亡事件，作者指出這不僅是一場人間悲劇，更因中國共產黨（CCP）的審查而完全被封鎖。作者強調，余夢龍的遭遇並非孤立事件，而是與自2015年以來多起年輕人不明死亡案例類似，例如央視主持人<strong>邊策</strong>、演員<strong>喬任梁</strong>、歌手<strong>本兮</strong>、演員<strong>任嬌</strong>以及江西致遠中學的<strong>胡鑫宇</strong>。這些案例的共同點是，中共警方總是以「自殺」或「意外」草草結案，且缺乏可信證據，引發家屬與大眾的普遍質疑。作者舉例，邊策的母親曾質疑官方的吸毒墜樓說法，認為兩包毒品和吸管不可能在16樓墜落後「恰好」整齊落在兒子身旁，更像是有人刻意佈置，她懷疑這是一起涉及權貴的謀殺案。然而，中共警方一如既往地迴避關鍵點，草率結案，如同處理余夢龍案。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_166.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>官方打壓與言論審查</h2> <p>作者在本集節目中，除了更新余夢龍案的最新進展，也旨在讓觀眾了解中共慣用的消音手法。他提到，在余夢龍去世後，中共當局發現境內刪帖封號仍無法壓制輿論，於是發布官方聲明。然而，這份聲明並非為了順應民意展開調查，而是選擇率先打擊討論此案的中國網民。聲明的主要內容是將持續「淨化網絡」，打擊所謂的「謠言」，聲稱余夢龍被設局、毆打、釘指甲、開膛破肚、吊掛等說法均屬捏造，並已懲處三人。作者質疑，在中共警方慣用逼供手段下，這些「認罪」的真實性存疑。當局並未立案調查，而是以幾句簡單的話語敷衍一切，聲稱一切都是捏造，甚至暗示將持續逮捕「造謠者」，這使得等待許久的民眾感到失望。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_347.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>案件疑點與高層涉入傳聞</h2> <p>作者指出，余夢龍案在事發24小時內即被定調為「意外」，甚至其已解散的工作室也代為發表聲明，排除刑事嫌疑。一位擁有兩千多萬粉絲的明星，死因充滿疑點，卻沒有立案、沒有驗屍、沒有告別式、沒有監控畫面，且在死後立刻被火化，這是不尋常的。即便余母親自按指紋發聲，要求為兒子伸張正義，官方仍視為「謠言」。作者強調，此事件最大的爭議點在於，有內部消息洩漏，指向中共高層官員<strong>蔡奇</strong>的私生子涉嫌將余夢龍玩弄致死。這也解釋了為何案件遭到徹底封鎖，甚至連質疑死因都被禁止。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_522.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>發聲者的遭遇與行業潛規則</h2> <p>許多為余夢龍案發聲的人士也面臨了打壓。中國博主兼退役軍人<strong>林北川</strong>，曾發文證實有「不准討論、不准關注、趕緊結案」的指令，隨後在被「傳喚」至北京後便從此失聯，其支持余夢龍的帖子也被刪除。另一位中國女演員<strong>孫琳</strong>，質疑余夢龍的死因，呼籲警方不要結案，但在發帖後數秒即被刪除。她更在當晚外出時遭到不明人士從高處拋擲花盆襲擊，並收到匿名威脅，警告她停止發聲，否則微博將被封鎖。此外，常在牆內評論明星八卦的<strong>向太</strong>，在直播中被問及余夢龍案時，直接表示「我不能說」，但仍暗示中國娛樂圈中男性也面臨「潛規則」。余夢龍的生前好友<strong>華晨宇</strong>，在音樂節上演唱歌曲《好想我回來啊》，並特地更換視覺背景，畫面中隱約暗示一名男子被黑手推落，最終被另一隻手接住。另一位藝人<strong>易烊千璽</strong>則在直播中面無表情地疊石頭，似乎也藉此表達無言的抗議。作者指出，許多中國娛樂圈人士都深知行業內幕，卻無人敢公開發聲。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_810.jpg" /></p> <hr /> <h2>轉移焦點的輿論戰術</h2> <p>當中共壓制余夢龍案的討論時，他們也同時設置了一個新的攻擊目標：韓國演員<strong>全智賢</strong>。起因是Disney+上的一部韓劇《特區》中，全智賢飾演的聯合國大使說了一句「中國為什麼寧願開戰？」這句話被「小粉紅」斷章取義，指責她「辱華」。作者解釋，這句話是全智賢的角色在劇中根據邏輯質疑，因為戰爭爆發的核爆地點也會影響中國，角色其實是在為中國說話，試圖澄清誤解。然而，許多未看過原片的中國網民和「小粉紅」，在網絡水軍的引導下，在牆內發布大量攻擊全智賢的帖子。作者強調，中國互聯網的審查制度決定了哪些議題可以討論，哪些不行。他指出，全智賢這樣一個微不足道的、甚至是捏造出來的事件能夠在內部網絡上迅速發酵，正是因為它得到了中共的允許。中共不希望公眾討論余夢龍這樣被高官迫害的案件，因此透過引導輿論攻擊另一個無辜者全智賢來分散民眾注意力。作者認為，這次的「辱華」事件與過往不同，因為它百分之百是由中共網絡水軍所推動。<p> <p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/g4wKwqw4LhQ_19.jpg" /></p> <hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Yu Menglong’s case is truly a human tragedy. But due to CCP censorship,. discussion inside the Great Firewall is now completely banned. But what can’t be spoken inside,. will be spread by me outside the wall and by all of you viewers. Yu Menglong’s injustice is not an isolated case in China. Let me list a few similar cases since 2015. CCTV host Bian Ce, age 32. Actor Qiao Renliang, age 29. Singer Ben Xi, age 22. Actress Ren Jiao, age 29. Including earlier, at Zhiyuan Middle School in Jiangxi. Hu Xinyu, only 15 years old. All died mysteriously at a young age. Yet the CCP police gave the same explanation:. “Su*cide” or “accident,”. without credible evidence. Which triggered widespread doubt among families and the public. For example, Bian Ce’s mother. also questioned her son’s cause of death,. saying her child never touched drugs. Even just an hour before the incident,. he was still on the phone with her. As for Beijing police. claiming her son died from drug use after falling,. with two small packets of drugs and straws beside him,. she felt deeply puzzled. She asked: after falling from the 16th floor,. those two packets of drugs and straws. just happened to land neatly right beside him? This makes no sense at all. It’s more like someone deliberately placed them there. She suspected it was a murder involving powerful figures. But the CCP police simply. avoided the key points,. closed the case hastily,. just like in Yu Menglong’s case. So when CCP announcements lack credibility,. the public tends to believe unofficial reports. Yet only hard evidence and truth. can truly stop rumors. But the police have yet to release any. Instead, they accuse the public. of “spreading rumors” and “fabricating lies,”. completely disregarding human life. Oh right—. Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink News Report. If you’re watching this show for the first time,. just a reminder—. you’re now watching. what’s called the “Chinese version of Discovery.”. And I’m your internship mentor in China,. AKA “centrist voter,”. Potter King. If you don’t mind being a Chinese Taiwanese,. congratulations—. you’ve found this program. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Remember to subscribe,. and let’s take a look at the real China together. Last episode we talked about Yu Menglong’s case. For those who haven’t watched that video,. you can check it out later,. so more people can understand this case. Because the discussion heat on this issue. is already fading away. A big reason behind this. is the CCP government’s suppression. So today I’d like to take this opportunity. to update you on Yu Menglong’s case,. and at the same time. let everyone understand. the CCP’s usual methods of silencing speech. Through real-life cases,. we’ll see how the CCP systematically controls. the issues they don’t want people to discuss. After a one-minute ad,. Following Yu Menglong’s death,. the CCP saw that deleting posts and banning accounts inside the wall. still couldn’t suppress public opinion. So the authorities finally spoke up. But not to follow public opinion. by opening a proper investigation. The CCP didn’t intend to reveal the truth for Yu Menglong. Instead, they chose to crack down first. on Chinese netizens discussing the case. Let’s take a look at the official statement. It’s a long one—. but the main point is clear:. they will continue “cleansing the internet”. to crack down on so-called rumors. Regarding Yu’s fall from a building,. they claim some people just wanted attention,. maliciously spreading false information online,. and producing fake videos. They said three people have been punished by law. Including claims that Yu was set up, assaulted, and then fell,. that he was hung from a high building,. had his nails pulled out,. was cut open and thrown down,. and that his mother was being controlled, etc. They said these were all lies. They also said the arrested people had confessed. But given the CCP police’s usual ways,. the number of times they force confessions—. I don’t need to spell it out. We can see that. the authorities didn’t even open a case to investigate,. but instead used a few simple lines. to gloss over everything,. saying it was all fabricated,. and even hinting at threats,. saying they’ll keep arresting those who “spread rumors.”. After everyone waited so long,. the first notice they issued. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">turned out to be a crackdown. on all Chinese netizens seeking justice for Yu. After reading this police bulletin,. I felt they didn’t need to write that long,. because they never intended to handle it. Next time they could just write four words:. “What can you do?”. After the death occurred,. within 24 hours they set the line:. it was an accident. And even the studio that Yu himself had already dissolved. issued a statement on his behalf,. saying criminal suspicion had been ruled out. A film star with over twenty million followers in China. dies in a case full of doubts,. yet there’s no case opened,. no autopsy,. no farewell ceremony,. no surveillance footage. Yu wasn’t some heinous criminal,. nor did he die of an infectious disease,. yet right after his death. he was immediately sent for cremation. To silence an artist with no wrongdoing. to this extent—. is that normal? Even Yu’s mother issued a statement herself,. with her fingerprint,. asking everyone to seek justice for her son,. yet in the authorities’ eyes that’s “rumor” too. It makes no sense. Allow me to point out something:. though there’s been lots of messy online “exposés,”. they’re chaotic—. but the core of this whole matter,. the biggest controversy,. is that insiders’ leaks all indicate. involvement of senior CCP official Cai Qi. They allege Cai Qi’s illegitimate son. toyed with Yu to death. Hence the total blackout on Yu,. and even questioning his cause of death is forbidden. Beyond the obvious total blackout. that everyone can see,. another Chinese blogger,. Lin Beichuan, came forward to confirm,. a retired Chinese soldier. He later spoke up for Yu inside the wall,. and now he’s disappeared. He had posted, revealing that. orders had been handed down from somewhere. to “pay no attention” to Yu’s case,. not to discuss it,. and to settle it quickly. His last post said he. was called to Beijing from Hong Kong,. stressing he was “called,”. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">so he couldn’t refuse. But after he was called to Beijing on September 19,. someone who used to post almost daily. up to now—. the cutoff for this video is the 25th—. he hasn’t posted again. Even his posts supporting Yu. have been deleted. Another Chinese actress, Sun Lin,. also questioned Yu’s cause of death,. pleading with the police not to close the case. There are still many doubts to verify. But soon after her post went up,. it was deleted in seconds. On the night of the 21st, when she went out,. she was attacked:. someone threw a flowerpot from above, hitting her head,. and she received anonymous threats,. warning her. to stop speaking up,. or her Weibo would be shut down. They said this was just a “small lesson.”. Another key indicator:. Xiang Tai, who often gossips about celebrities inside the wall,. didn’t dare comment on Yu. Chinese netizens flooded her livestream with,. “Help Yu.”. She replied directly:. “Stop spamming.”. I can’t talk about this. But although she avoided mentioning Yu Menglong,. she still had things to say about the unspoken rules. in China’s entertainment industry. She hinted that. men face this too. It seemed like she said nothing,. yet it felt like she said everything. And Yu’s close friend while alive, Hua Chenyu,. recently, at the Foshan Music Festival,. performed his own song,. “I Really Wish I Could Come Back,”. and specifically changed to a new visual backdrop. The visuals subtly suggested. a man being thrown downward by a black hand,. and by the end, another hand. catches the falling man. Another Chinese artist, Jackson Yee (Yi Yangqianxi),. also suddenly went live—. but didn’t interact with viewers at all,. just stacked stones with a somber look. Let me show you a short clip,. so you can watch his expression change. You can see that many Chinese entertainers. know the industry’s inside stories,. yet no one dares to speak up. When the CCP suppressed discussion of Yu’s case,. besides banning netizens from discussing it,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">they also set up a new target to attack—. Jun Ji-hyun. Let me briefly explain the Jun Ji-hyun issue. There’s a new K-drama on Disney+. called “Storm Zone.”. In it, Jun Ji-hyun plays a UN ambassador. There’s a line that says,. “Why would China prefer war?”. The “little pinks” seized on that and started hurling abuse,. accusing her of “insulting China.”. But the point is,. the line Jun says in the show—. “Why would China prefer war?”—. is her character questioning it. Because in this spy-thriller’s setup,. if war breaks out,. the nuclear blast location. would also affect China in the story. So Jun’s character. says that line. Her character’s logic. is that war would not benefit China,. so she finds the push for war suspicious. Sorry for the spoiler. But in the show, Jun Ji-hyun. actually seeks help from China’s ambassador. In fact, her character speaks up for China. She’s trying to clear up a misunderstanding. But many who never watched the original,. Chinese netizens and “little pinks,”. were blindly steered by bot armies. As a result, inside the firewall. there were tons of posts attacking Jun Ji-hyun. Allow me to remind everyone again:. China’s internet is censored. What you may discuss,. and what you may not,. as Yu’s case already showed,. should be clear to you. So think about this:. why can such a trivial matter about Jun,. and one fabricated at that,. blow up across the internal internet? Exactly. It’s just as you suspect:. it’s allowed by the CCP. Inside the wall, it’s rule by men. The CCP doesn’t want the public discussing. Yu, persecuted by high-ranking officials,. so they want you distracted. by attacking another innocent—Jun Ji-hyun. I must say, this so-called “insulting China” case. is different from past ones. I’ve covered many such incidents before,. where the “little pinks” lashed out,. but this time it’s different,. because this is 100%. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">driven by CCP cyber-armies. Take a look at these attack pieces:. they claim she read the script, so she’s not innocent; that the show smears China as warmongering; that it uses fabric with yellow stars as a carpet; that the villains speak Chinese; and that it vilifies Dalian and Hong Kong, etc. These astroturf marketing accounts. are the ones truly smearing others. If you’ve watched the show,. you’ll know. the starry carpet scene is set in the White House,. and the crew used it to recreate the real setting. 299. Take a look at President Biden’s earlier video tour. See? You saw it, right? The real White House carpet does have stars. And that’s because the U.S. flag. itself has stars, okay? Also, the villains in that show are Koreans themselves,. not Chinese. Nor does it smear Dalian or Hong Kong or anything like that. But the posts inside the firewall. keep churning out piece after piece,. sounding all “credible,”. and the narrative gets steered. Uninformed Chinese netizens. are used to attack Jun Ji-hyun,. thinking they’re righteous. I find it ironic. Stirred-up netizens go after Jun Ji-hyun. while forgetting their fellow Chinese. are the ones being persecuted. Yu Menglong hadn’t even been laid to rest,. before CCP bot armies spun the story away,. and the authorities suppressed public opinion. From this case you should understand:. Menglong won’t be the last,. and neither will Jun Ji-hyun be the only target. The CCP is good at manufacturing enemies. for the public to attack,. to divert attention from what’s happening at home. Taking a step back, though,. if the “little pinks” truly think Jun insulted China,. she’s just acting,. she didn’t write the script. If you’re really that upset,. Chinese netizens shouldn’t support the Korea-ban; I suggest doing the opposite:. the “little pinks” should fund Korean artists. to shoot pro-CCP patriotic films. Don’t you say the motherland is powerful? Whatever the fee is,. have Chinese producers. pay a hundred times more and hire Jun Ji-hyun,. and have her, in a patriotic CCP film,. shout “I love China.”. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Wouldn’t that be great? Otherwise, why are you yelling while watching pirated copies? So, what did you think of today’s video? Feel free to share in the comments below. In the latter part of today’s video,. let me show you a few. “self-own” comments on the channel. “I’m watching from beyond the wall, but I’m not a little pink.”. “So don’t call everyone who climbs the wall a little pink.”. Looks like you’re new here. Let me remind you of one thing:. if it’s not your seat,. don’t sit in it. The wording I use on this show. is carefully considered. I strive to be precise. Of course I know. there are Chinese people we can talk to. and there are party-blind “little pinks.”. So when I refer to Chinese people,. I say “Chinese netizens outside the wall.”. Likewise, when I mean the little pinks,. I say “little pinks outside the wall.”. Clear enough? Lately I kind of feel. Taiwan and China have flipped. I’m seeing many Chinese. gradually waking up,. while some in Taiwan. are moving closer to the CCP. Like this one:. “Isn’t Taiwan part of China?”. “Why can Taiwan talk about it,. but people inside the wall can’t?”. That made me think they watched my video. and started to reflect. Next one:. “It’s meaningless to elevate an isolated case to a national level.”. “Which country doesn’t have money–power–sex deals?”. With Yu Menglong wronged like that,. you still say such nonsense? If you’re not a CCP troll. sent here on a cleanup mission,. I’d suspect you might be one of the perpetrators. Using a burner account to comment here. CCP bot armies, stop muddying the waters. with “other countries do it too,”. or “don’t make it a national issue.”. That’s whitewashing. Back to the core question:. let me ask you—. who took Yu Menglong’s life? Multiple pieces of evidence and insider leaks. point straight to a senior official’s child. persecuted by the red second and third generations. Why do they dare do this? Because they control China,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">and officials shield one another. They know they have the CCP regime backing them. That’s why they dare to do whatever they want inside the wall,. and then suppress Chinese netizens afterward,. not allowing them to speak up for Yu Menglong. The ones doing all this. are the CCP authorities. So you’re saying this matter. is something I alone elevated to a national level? Absolutely not. The ones who persecuted Yu Menglong. are the CCP authorities. It’s the CCP government suppressing the Chinese people. It’s your state persecuting your fellow citizens. Every country has bad actors,. but wrongdoers in other countries. can they act like the CCP princelings? Suppose this happened in Taiwan:. an official’s illegitimate son colludes with a celebrity. to abuse another star—. it would absolutely rock the country. The media would report it morning, noon, night—and late-night. Taiwanese netizens would share and discuss it online,. and they wouldn’t be purged or banned. In the end, besides that politician. getting blasted out of office,. people would support jailing the perpetrators. Prosecutors would open a case. So compared with Yu Menglong’s case,. where the CCP deployed state machinery. to suppress, persecute, and silence,. it’s entirely different. Ha—trying to cover up the SET executive’s son assaulting a woman? Using lies to cover facts—. so “humane,” huh? I’m speechless. This idiot is here to whitewash too,. and trying to slap a label on me. The case of SET vice GM’s son, Gong Yiting, assaulting an actress—. what’s there to be afraid to talk about? If you dared say that to my face,. I’d land a full combo on you. People like you are scum. Why are you conflating two real tragedies? Yu Menglong has already “logged off,”. and you say I’m spreading rumors? What’s wrong with you? Besides, in my work. I’ve collaborated with Chiang Tsu-ping,. whom I respect deeply,. and she’s very kind in private. So regarding what she went through,. I’m really saddened,. and I truly hope Taiwan’s judiciary. gives her justice. The point is—this case. has been formally opened in Taiwan. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">You can look up the news online. Gong Yiting is currently barred from leaving the country. People can discuss it online freely. This is completely different from Yu Menglong’s case. Tying the two together—. all I can say is, if you’re not using your brain,. go donate it. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g4wKwqw4LhQ</a></p><p>點擊優惠連結👉<a href="https://surfshark.com/potterking">https://surfshark.com/potterking</a> </p><p>或用優惠碼 [potterking] 以獲得額外 4 個月 Surfshark 服務！</p><p></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>于朦朧案最新消息！替于朦朧發聲慘遭公安逮捕！中國藝人無聲挺于朦朧</p><p>全智賢因為一句話辱華？</p><p>分析中共網軍如何製造辱華事件煽動中國人</p><p>粉紅特報146期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/g4wKwqw4LhQ/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <pubDate>2025-09-27T09:45:03.000Z</pubDate>
    </item><item>
      <title><![CDATA[于朦朧冤案｜于朦朧母親心痛發聲！還我兒公道！中共紅二代潛規則中國男影星！此人靠山是習總親信蔡奇！專門網路維穩｜粉紅特報145期]]></title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8</link>
      <itunes:title><![CDATA[于朦朧冤案｜于朦朧母親心痛發聲！還我兒公道！中共紅二代潛規則中國男影星！此人靠山是習總親信蔡奇！專門網路維穩｜粉紅特報145期]]></itunes:title>
      <itunes:author><![CDATA[波特王好帥]]></itunes:author>
      <itunes:summary>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/AlCiC5fdWt8/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1><ul><li>深入了解中國<strong>娛樂圈的權力腐敗</strong>與明星<strong>被壓迫的悲慘現況</strong>。</li><li>揭示中國共產黨(CCP)如何利用<strong>「太子黨」</strong>背景的權貴，對異議或不順從者進行<strong>殘酷打壓與全面封鎖消息</strong>。</li><li>警示<strong>「防火牆內」</strong>的普通民眾，無論身份高低，在中共統治下都可能淪為<strong>「韭菜」</strong>，個人權益與生命安全毫無保障。</li></ul><hr /><h1>摘要</h1><h2>影片引言與案情概述</h2><p>影片的說書人，又名Potter King，開宗明義指出此影片將探討中國男星<strong>于孟龍</strong>的悲慘遭遇。最初，說書人並不熟悉于孟龍，但因眾多觀眾請求，他深入調查此案。他強調這不僅是又一起<strong>「中共韭菜」</strong>的悲劇，更充滿疑點，旨在讓觀眾一窺「防火牆內」作為中國人的真實生活。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_0.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>事件的開端與疑點</h2><p>于孟龍案始於9月11日下午1時59分，中國狗仔隊爆料他墜樓身亡。消息迅速傳開，現場照片顯示窗戶螢幕有奇特的破損。同日下午，于孟龍工作室發布聲明，確認他去世，並稱警方已排除刑事嫌疑，將此案定調為「意外墜樓」。然而，此舉引發軒然大波，<strong>一個擁有2000萬粉絲的男星離奇死亡，官方急於撇清刑事責任，顯得疑點重重</strong>。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_90.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>揭露殘酷真相與求救影片</h2><p>隨著事件發酵，內部人士爆料于孟龍並非意外墜樓，而是<strong>被活生生從樓上拋下兩次</strong>，手段極其殘忍。影片中更驚人地播放了一段據稱是案發前一晚秘密錄製的影片。畫面昏暗，但清晰可聞于孟龍因懼高症在五樓窗外被倒吊時<strong>心碎的求救聲</strong>。此影片不僅是受害者被虐待的真實畫面，也被說書人視為為受害者保留的證據，盼有朝一日沉冤得雪。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_160.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>背後的權勢與威脅</h2><p>說書人進一步揭露，于孟龍的悲劇早有伏筆。他自25歲出道以來，就屢次因拒絕「潛規則」而遭受權勢打壓，甚至被<strong>封殺三年</strong>。2017年事業剛有起色，又被影視製作人<strong>辛奇（辛曉雄）</strong>盯上。辛奇的真實身份被指為中共政治局常委<strong>蔡奇的私生子</strong>，擁有<strong>「太子黨」</strong>背景。蔡奇身為習近平親信，負責網路監控與維穩，導致辛奇在「防火牆內」幾乎<strong>橫行無忌，無人能動</strong>。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_250.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>金錢交易與致命證據</h2><p>辛奇以成立粉絲俱樂部為藉口接近于孟龍，隨後利用威脅利誘的手段，以于孟龍的名義註冊了兩家公司，強迫他簽訂合約。合作綁定後，辛奇試圖強行施加「潛規則」，但于孟龍堅決拒絕。在絕望中，于孟龍意外發現這兩家公司被辛奇用於<strong>洗錢</strong>，為中共充當「白手套」。于孟龍暗中收集證據，並將關鍵證據儲存在隨身碟中，原欲以此擺脫辛奇的騷擾。然而，觸及中共高層利益的證據反而將他推向致命危機。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_360.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>官方壓制與母親的控訴</h2><p>于孟龍墜樓消息傳出後，中共迅速啟動輿論管控，<strong>大量刪除微博、小紅書、抖音等平臺的相關討論</strong>，于孟龍在公眾視野中被<strong>「抹去」</strong>。更甚者，于孟龍工作室再次發布聲明「洗白」，以于孟龍母親的名義，聲稱是醉酒意外墜樓，試圖平息輿論。然而，于孟龍母親本人並不接受此說法，匿名在網路上發文，以<strong>「竇娥之母」</strong>自稱，用帶指紋的手印證明身份。她哭訴兒子枉死，握有事發前後的關鍵影像與內部證詞，足以證明並非意外，而是<strong>蓄意加害</strong>，懇請世人為她兒子討回公道。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_450.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>作者的省思與警示</h2><p>說書人總結此案，感嘆連擁有2000萬粉絲的明星，在中共統治下也難逃迫害致死的命運，更遑論普通民眾。他警告所有在中共統治下的國民，無論是否有名，在中共高官眼中都只是<strong>「韭菜」</strong>，是可供開採的<strong>「人礦」</strong>。說書人希望那些翻牆出來的<strong>「小粉紅」</strong>能看清，所謂「偉大祖國」的GDP和高樓大廈，都不是屬於人民的，因為在黨的眼中，人民並非「人」，而只是被利用的資源。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_540.jpg" /></p><hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink News. I’m your intern mentor for being Chinese.（false flag）. AKA the swing voter. Potter King. Some wanted to hear Potter King’s take on the Yu Menglong case. I’m not a fan of Yu. But hearing the news was heartbreaking. Hello, Potter King. Could you talk about the Yu Menglong incident in China’s entertainment industry? This matter may involve many celebrities or high-ranking officials. It has already been suppressed inside China. I hope you can help more people pay attention to it. This week I’ve received several such comments. Hoping I would talk about Yu Menglong’s case. But beforehand I wasn’t familiar with this Chinese star. Nor had I seen any of his dramas. But since so many wanted me to talk about it,. I went to research the case. And after understanding what he went through,. I can only say it’s another tragedy of the CCP’s chives. And I do think this case is full of suspicious points. But just now,. many Taiwanese have accepted CCP propaganda. They think being Chinese. seems pretty good. So in this week’s video,. we’ll learn about Yu Menglong’s ordeal. to get a taste of life as a Chinese inside the Great Firewall. After a one-minute ad,. we’ll get right into today’s topic. First I must say,. this case is hard to explain fully. Because the CCP inside China. has already been maintaining stability on it. A lot of the information is fragmented. I can only piece it together in order. If there are parts I didn’t mention,. I welcome informed viewers. to add them in the comments. OK, let me quickly explain. what exactly happened. It started on September 11 at 1:59 p.m. when a paparazzi inside China posted on Weibo. saying Yu Menglong had fallen to his death. At first the news wasn’t confirmed as true or false. The post only had text plus a few photos from the scene. He said he had confirmed with staff. that the one who fell was Yu Menglong. And in one of the photos,. there was a close-up of the window screen where it happened. At first Chinese netizens. could still discuss how weirdly the screen was broken. They questioned who would cut it open and then jump. The incident site was a luxury apartment project in Chaoyang, Beijing. The Sunshine Upper East community. Later that afternoon,. Yu Menglong’s studio released a statement. confirming his death from falling. He was 37. Still very young. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Although this confirmed. the paparazzi’s report was correct,. what’s strange is. Yu Menglong’s studio replaced the police to announce. that the police had ruled out criminal suspicion. Clearly wanting to frame the case as an accidental fall. But Yu Menglong, as. a male star with 20 million fans in China,. suddenly died like this—. it naturally drew huge attention. It even shot up to number one on Weibo’s trending. And that’s when insiders began revealing. that Yu Menglong didn’t fall by accident,. but was thrown off. And not just once. He was thrown twice. The method was extremely cruel. There was even a video. directly filming the window of the crime scene,. the same one in the leaked photos we saw. But the video. was secretly filmed the night before. So the footage is dark. But you can still clearly hear. Yu Menglong’s heart-wrenching cries for help. With his fear of heights,. he was hung upside down outside a 5th-floor window and toyed with. A reminder—the next clip. may make people uncomfortable. It’s real footage of persecution. If you’re especially empathetic,. consider muting the sound. and just reading the subtitles. Even though this might get yellow-tagged,. I think it’s necessary to show it. Because this video has already been censored inside China. So by posting it here,. I’m also preserving evidence for the victim. Hoping one day his injustice will be redressed. In addition, reports also pointed out that on the night of his fall... There were multiple people at the scene,. including well-known figures from China’s entertainment industry. It’s said Yu Menglong was set up at a gathering that night,. drugged and plied with alcohol,. and then forced to have relations with a man. Afterward, the other party tossed him two Rolex watches,. trying to buy him off. I’ve also reviewed many related materials. and compiled a few key points to share. Yu was targeted when he debuted at 25. Rumor had it a powerful woman in the industry tried to coerce him,. but he refused,. and was blacklisted for three years,. disappearing from public view,. with no job opportunities. By 2017,. he finally landed work again,. appearing in “Eternal Love” (Three Lives, Three Worlds, Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms). As his career began to recover,. he was targeted by someone else,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">who tried to force the unspoken rules on him. That person was later identified. as Xin Qi,. birth name Xin Xiaoxiong,. a film producer. You might ask, can a Chinese film producer. really wield such power over an artist? Perhaps not,. but Xin Qi. isn’t an ordinary producer—. he’s a princeling, the child of a senior CCP official. According to news reports,. Xin Qi is suspected to be. the illegitimate son of Politburo Standing Committee member Cai Qi. With that princeling background,. his backing inside the Great Firewall is extremely strong. Moreover, Cai Qi. is a Xi loyalist who has been heavily favored,. in charge of China’s online surveillance and stability maintenance. With such a patron behind him,. and a system ruled by men, not law,. where the Party decides everything,. you can imagine that. almost no one could touch Xin Qi. Princelings in China can indeed act with impunity. Even if he treats the entertainment world like a brothel,. it wouldn’t be unheard of. But Xin Qi initially adored Yu,. approaching him under the pretext of organizing a fan club,. with the real aim of getting close and monitoring him. After getting familiar with Yu,. he registered two companies in Yu’s name,. using both carrot and stick. to make Yu sign contracts. Once the partnership was bound,. Xin tried to impose the casting-couch rules on him. But Yu had boundaries,. and still refused at all costs. Yet given Xin’s backing,. Yu had no real recourse against him,. essentially with nowhere to turn. In this desperate moment,. Yu happened to discover. that the two companies in his name. were being used by the other side for money laundering—. acting as a white glove for the CCP. So Yu quietly gathered evidence,. and once he had key proof,. he went to deregister the companies. and stored the evidence on a USB drive. Presumably, Yu intended to use this as leverage. to free himself from Xin’s years of harassment. But because he held evidence of a senior CCP official’s laundering,. he touched the Party’s interests,. and in China’s system of official protectionism,. with Yu still physically inside the Great Firewall,. it instead brought fatal danger upon him. That earlier SOS clip you saw. wasn’t captured by chance,. but because Xin planned a setup against Yu. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">and brought in paparazzi to film. Xin originally wanted to use a sex scandal as leverage,. but it ended up accidentally capturing. footage of Yu pleading for help while alive. After this news broke inside China,. it’s easy to imagine. the CCP’s opinion-control machinery kicked in at once:. mass deletions on Weibo, Xiaohongshu, Douyin, and more. From trending #1 to vanishing into thin air—. Yu was thus erased from public view. Worse still, there’s more:. Yu’s studio. issued yet another statement to whitewash,. this time invoking Yu’s mother’s name,. aiming to quell netizens’ doubts,. claiming he fell accidentally while drunk,. and asking everyone to stop speculating. But once that statement came out,. Yu’s mother herself. apparently did not accept it. The very next day,. Yu Menglong’s mother anonymously posted online herself,. attaching a fingerprinted handprint to prove it was really her. She stayed anonymous because. the CCP had already banned discussion of Yu’s cause of death. But how could a mother who lost her own child. possibly remain silent? With grievance in her heart,. she chose to speak out under a pseudonym. She didn’t use Yu’s real name—. she called herself “Dou E’s mother.”. By the way,. “The Injustice to Dou E” is a Yuan-dynasty zaju by Guan Hanqing,. about a kind woman who was framed,. tortured and forced into a confession. Because both are injustices,. she used “Dou E” as a stand-in. The gist of Yu’s mother’s statement was:. I hope to seek justice for my child who died wronged. The killer’s claim to the public that it was an accident. is false. I hold key footage from before and after the incident,. plus testimony from insiders,. enough to prove it wasn’t an accident. but a deliberate assault. Since my child passed,. I have run around seeking help many times,. yet the killer still walks free. and is even suppressing the truth. My child was once so sunny and kind—. he should not have died bearing injustice,. nor should the killer dismiss his life. with the word “accident.”. I earnestly ask every conscientious compatriot:. if you know any clues from before or after my son’s incident,. if you are willing to speak for justice,. please help forward this petition of grievance,. so more people can know the truth,. return justice to my son,. and justice to this world. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I stand by every word I say. That’s roughly the current progress of Yu’s case. My first thought when looking at this was:. even someone like him—. a male star with 20 million followers inside the Firewall,. under intense public attention—. could be persecuted to death like this. All the more so for ordinary Chinese people. Famous or not,. as long as you’re under CCP rule,. in the eyes of senior cadres,. you and I are no different from “chives.”. Among my viewers. are some little pinks who scale the Firewall to watch. I hope these little pinks. can recognize one thing:. the “great motherland” you praise all day,. the GDP you boast about,. the city high-rises—. none of that is the point,. and none of it is yours. Because in the Party’s eyes,. we’re not people—. we’re just “human ore” to be mined. Those who oppose the CCP. don’t hate it because of skyscrapers,. but because under CCP rule,. people have no rights—. only the lives of high officials count. Even if you’re currently a vested beneficiary inside the Firewall,. with a job better than other “chives,”. it’s only temporary. Look at Yu’s past posts—. did he not love China? He wrote plenty. of patriotic articles. But once he caught the eye of a cadre’s child,. he still ended up with no remains. When the CCP’s iron fist. one day slams into your head,. aside from people like me,. the “rebels” you dislike so much,. there will truly be no one left to speak for you. And think about this:. an artist as famous as Yu inside China. could have all news completely blocked. It’s not hard to imagine. similar cases happen daily inside the Firewall—. unknown to anyone,. because others are even more nameless. So, little pinks, reflect:. while you help the CCP with external propaganda. and conduct cognitive warfare against Taiwan,. the more “successful” you are, the more you hurt yourselves. If your state becomes all-powerful,. no one will be able to save you. And in Taiwan, indeed quite a few people. no longer mind becoming China’s “chives.”. Some are bored of eating proper meals. and suddenly crave eating poop instead. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">What they see. is just the pink bubble you’ve blown up. But deep down you know better than anyone. that it’s fake. You’ve sung the March of the Volunteers so many times—. “Arise, you who refuse to be slaves.”. Was that all fake singing? If Chinese people had some guts,. I’m telling you honestly—. the whole world would help you overthrow the CCP. But if Chinese people willingly kneel as slaves,. then Yu Menglong won’t be the last. What do you all think about this case? Feel free to share below. And other viewers are also welcome. to add more details of Yu’s case. In the second half of today’s video,. let’s look at a few self-own comments on the channel. “Potter King represents the fence-sitters.”. Fence-sitters, huh? I’m a swing voter right now. That’s not fence-sitting—. that’s supporting Taiwan’s mainstream public opinion. But this isn’t the first time I’ve seen such comments. After I shifted my channel’s direction,. I do see these kinds of remarks occasionally. It makes me feel a lot. Is it that the Oscars owe me a statuette,. or that these netizens. truly lack logical thinking skills? They can’t even grasp the meaning of words. Even if you don’t understand what “swing voter” means,. you should at least understand this:. after I’ve walked you through the real China,. if after watching. you still think China is good,. and want to be invaded by the CCP to become Chinese,. then that just shows. you truly love China. In this life,. you’re destined to be the Party’s little chive. Loving it to a tragic end. If that’s really the majority view in Taiwan,. then I can only say it’s fate. And if you can’t understand this,. I suggest you stay off the internet. Seriously, please—. in this era of rampant disinformation,. you really shouldn’t be online. No wonder Taiwan’s losing the info war so badly—. there’s a reason. It reminds me of how some people. couldn’t even tell Bit King, who never shows his face,. from Potter King, who does. I was speechless. But as I said,. scolding won’t help. We can only keep playing into the headwind. And actually, thinking of it another way, it’s fine—. the appearance of such people. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">reveals something very important:. that my pivot was necessary. The purpose of my pivot. was to make dialogue. break through the echo chamber. Now with comments like these appearing,. it shows I’ve succeeded. I’ll keep working hard—. please keep supporting me. There are many ways to love Taiwan—. everyone, keep fighting from your own positions. “Potter King is actually trans. I have evidence but I won’t say it. So Potter King, please post a video to prove it. Thanks. If you don’t dare, that proves you’re guilty.”. The logic of this comment. sounds like kids quarreling in grade school. Wait, no—. if I call you grade-schoolers,. real kids might be offended,. saying, “We’re not that dumb!”. Let me analyze this little pink’s logic. for you all:. first he throws out an accusation,. saying the other person is trans,. then says he has evidence but won’t show it,. and shifts the responsibility back to the accused. He’s the one making the claim,. yet demands the other party film a video to clear themselves. This is a classic case of shifting the burden of proof:. offering no evidence himself,. but requiring others to prove innocence. It’s pure logical fallacy,. with no content and no credibility. Then he adds one more jab:. “If you don’t dare to film, that means you’re guilty.”. Basically he set up a sure-win condition—. no matter how the other side responds,. he can twist it his way. Shameless. But good for self-entertainment. So with this little pink example,. I’ll respond the same way once. Then you’ll know how to reply to these dumb pinks in the future. Here’s how:. I have proof you’re brainless—. but I won’t say it. Please film yourself,. open up your skull,. and prove you have a brain. Ah, if you don’t dare film it,. that means you’re guilty. Proves I was right—. you really are brainless. “Potter King saw Kuan Chang,. now he’s anxious because he can’t lick red money. Mom, love me once more.”. I’m not jealous of Kuan Chang. But since you mention him,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I recall Kuan Chang said himself—. he licked the CCP at his own expense and lost money. And there’s also this recent video of Chinese netizens’ comments on Kuan Chang. I can only say—. pathetic. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8</a></p><p>點擊優惠連結👉<a href="https://surfshark.com/potterking">https://surfshark.com/potterking</a> </p><p>或用優惠碼 [potterking] 以獲得額外 4 個月 Surfshark 服務！</p><p></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>于朦朧冤案！于朦朧母親心痛發聲！還我兒公道！</p><p>中共紅二代潛規則中國男影星！</p><p>此人靠山是習總親信蔡奇！專門網路維穩！</p><p>粉紅特報145期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </itunes:summary>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/AlCiC5fdWt8/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1><ul><li>深入了解中國<strong>娛樂圈的權力腐敗</strong>與明星<strong>被壓迫的悲慘現況</strong>。</li><li>揭示中國共產黨(CCP)如何利用<strong>「太子黨」</strong>背景的權貴，對異議或不順從者進行<strong>殘酷打壓與全面封鎖消息</strong>。</li><li>警示<strong>「防火牆內」</strong>的普通民眾，無論身份高低，在中共統治下都可能淪為<strong>「韭菜」</strong>，個人權益與生命安全毫無保障。</li></ul><hr /><h1>摘要</h1><h2>影片引言與案情概述</h2><p>影片的說書人，又名Potter King，開宗明義指出此影片將探討中國男星<strong>于孟龍</strong>的悲慘遭遇。最初，說書人並不熟悉于孟龍，但因眾多觀眾請求，他深入調查此案。他強調這不僅是又一起<strong>「中共韭菜」</strong>的悲劇，更充滿疑點，旨在讓觀眾一窺「防火牆內」作為中國人的真實生活。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_0.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>事件的開端與疑點</h2><p>于孟龍案始於9月11日下午1時59分，中國狗仔隊爆料他墜樓身亡。消息迅速傳開，現場照片顯示窗戶螢幕有奇特的破損。同日下午，于孟龍工作室發布聲明，確認他去世，並稱警方已排除刑事嫌疑，將此案定調為「意外墜樓」。然而，此舉引發軒然大波，<strong>一個擁有2000萬粉絲的男星離奇死亡，官方急於撇清刑事責任，顯得疑點重重</strong>。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_90.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>揭露殘酷真相與求救影片</h2><p>隨著事件發酵，內部人士爆料于孟龍並非意外墜樓，而是<strong>被活生生從樓上拋下兩次</strong>，手段極其殘忍。影片中更驚人地播放了一段據稱是案發前一晚秘密錄製的影片。畫面昏暗，但清晰可聞于孟龍因懼高症在五樓窗外被倒吊時<strong>心碎的求救聲</strong>。此影片不僅是受害者被虐待的真實畫面，也被說書人視為為受害者保留的證據，盼有朝一日沉冤得雪。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_160.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>背後的權勢與威脅</h2><p>說書人進一步揭露，于孟龍的悲劇早有伏筆。他自25歲出道以來，就屢次因拒絕「潛規則」而遭受權勢打壓，甚至被<strong>封殺三年</strong>。2017年事業剛有起色，又被影視製作人<strong>辛奇（辛曉雄）</strong>盯上。辛奇的真實身份被指為中共政治局常委<strong>蔡奇的私生子</strong>，擁有<strong>「太子黨」</strong>背景。蔡奇身為習近平親信，負責網路監控與維穩，導致辛奇在「防火牆內」幾乎<strong>橫行無忌，無人能動</strong>。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_250.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>金錢交易與致命證據</h2><p>辛奇以成立粉絲俱樂部為藉口接近于孟龍，隨後利用威脅利誘的手段，以于孟龍的名義註冊了兩家公司，強迫他簽訂合約。合作綁定後，辛奇試圖強行施加「潛規則」，但于孟龍堅決拒絕。在絕望中，于孟龍意外發現這兩家公司被辛奇用於<strong>洗錢</strong>，為中共充當「白手套」。于孟龍暗中收集證據，並將關鍵證據儲存在隨身碟中，原欲以此擺脫辛奇的騷擾。然而，觸及中共高層利益的證據反而將他推向致命危機。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_360.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>官方壓制與母親的控訴</h2><p>于孟龍墜樓消息傳出後，中共迅速啟動輿論管控，<strong>大量刪除微博、小紅書、抖音等平臺的相關討論</strong>，于孟龍在公眾視野中被<strong>「抹去」</strong>。更甚者，于孟龍工作室再次發布聲明「洗白」，以于孟龍母親的名義，聲稱是醉酒意外墜樓，試圖平息輿論。然而，于孟龍母親本人並不接受此說法，匿名在網路上發文，以<strong>「竇娥之母」</strong>自稱，用帶指紋的手印證明身份。她哭訴兒子枉死，握有事發前後的關鍵影像與內部證詞，足以證明並非意外，而是<strong>蓄意加害</strong>，懇請世人為她兒子討回公道。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_450.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>作者的省思與警示</h2><p>說書人總結此案，感嘆連擁有2000萬粉絲的明星，在中共統治下也難逃迫害致死的命運，更遑論普通民眾。他警告所有在中共統治下的國民，無論是否有名，在中共高官眼中都只是<strong>「韭菜」</strong>，是可供開採的<strong>「人礦」</strong>。說書人希望那些翻牆出來的<strong>「小粉紅」</strong>能看清，所謂「偉大祖國」的GDP和高樓大廈，都不是屬於人民的，因為在黨的眼中，人民並非「人」，而只是被利用的資源。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_540.jpg" /></p><hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink News. I’m your intern mentor for being Chinese.（false flag）. AKA the swing voter. Potter King. Some wanted to hear Potter King’s take on the Yu Menglong case. I’m not a fan of Yu. But hearing the news was heartbreaking. Hello, Potter King. Could you talk about the Yu Menglong incident in China’s entertainment industry? This matter may involve many celebrities or high-ranking officials. It has already been suppressed inside China. I hope you can help more people pay attention to it. This week I’ve received several such comments. Hoping I would talk about Yu Menglong’s case. But beforehand I wasn’t familiar with this Chinese star. Nor had I seen any of his dramas. But since so many wanted me to talk about it,. I went to research the case. And after understanding what he went through,. I can only say it’s another tragedy of the CCP’s chives. And I do think this case is full of suspicious points. But just now,. many Taiwanese have accepted CCP propaganda. They think being Chinese. seems pretty good. So in this week’s video,. we’ll learn about Yu Menglong’s ordeal. to get a taste of life as a Chinese inside the Great Firewall. After a one-minute ad,. we’ll get right into today’s topic. First I must say,. this case is hard to explain fully. Because the CCP inside China. has already been maintaining stability on it. A lot of the information is fragmented. I can only piece it together in order. If there are parts I didn’t mention,. I welcome informed viewers. to add them in the comments. OK, let me quickly explain. what exactly happened. It started on September 11 at 1:59 p.m. when a paparazzi inside China posted on Weibo. saying Yu Menglong had fallen to his death. At first the news wasn’t confirmed as true or false. The post only had text plus a few photos from the scene. He said he had confirmed with staff. that the one who fell was Yu Menglong. And in one of the photos,. there was a close-up of the window screen where it happened. At first Chinese netizens. could still discuss how weirdly the screen was broken. They questioned who would cut it open and then jump. The incident site was a luxury apartment project in Chaoyang, Beijing. The Sunshine Upper East community. Later that afternoon,. Yu Menglong’s studio released a statement. confirming his death from falling. He was 37. Still very young. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Although this confirmed. the paparazzi’s report was correct,. what’s strange is. Yu Menglong’s studio replaced the police to announce. that the police had ruled out criminal suspicion. Clearly wanting to frame the case as an accidental fall. But Yu Menglong, as. a male star with 20 million fans in China,. suddenly died like this—. it naturally drew huge attention. It even shot up to number one on Weibo’s trending. And that’s when insiders began revealing. that Yu Menglong didn’t fall by accident,. but was thrown off. And not just once. He was thrown twice. The method was extremely cruel. There was even a video. directly filming the window of the crime scene,. the same one in the leaked photos we saw. But the video. was secretly filmed the night before. So the footage is dark. But you can still clearly hear. Yu Menglong’s heart-wrenching cries for help. With his fear of heights,. he was hung upside down outside a 5th-floor window and toyed with. A reminder—the next clip. may make people uncomfortable. It’s real footage of persecution. If you’re especially empathetic,. consider muting the sound. and just reading the subtitles. Even though this might get yellow-tagged,. I think it’s necessary to show it. Because this video has already been censored inside China. So by posting it here,. I’m also preserving evidence for the victim. Hoping one day his injustice will be redressed. In addition, reports also pointed out that on the night of his fall... There were multiple people at the scene,. including well-known figures from China’s entertainment industry. It’s said Yu Menglong was set up at a gathering that night,. drugged and plied with alcohol,. and then forced to have relations with a man. Afterward, the other party tossed him two Rolex watches,. trying to buy him off. I’ve also reviewed many related materials. and compiled a few key points to share. Yu was targeted when he debuted at 25. Rumor had it a powerful woman in the industry tried to coerce him,. but he refused,. and was blacklisted for three years,. disappearing from public view,. with no job opportunities. By 2017,. he finally landed work again,. appearing in “Eternal Love” (Three Lives, Three Worlds, Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms). As his career began to recover,. he was targeted by someone else,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">who tried to force the unspoken rules on him. That person was later identified. as Xin Qi,. birth name Xin Xiaoxiong,. a film producer. You might ask, can a Chinese film producer. really wield such power over an artist? Perhaps not,. but Xin Qi. isn’t an ordinary producer—. he’s a princeling, the child of a senior CCP official. According to news reports,. Xin Qi is suspected to be. the illegitimate son of Politburo Standing Committee member Cai Qi. With that princeling background,. his backing inside the Great Firewall is extremely strong. Moreover, Cai Qi. is a Xi loyalist who has been heavily favored,. in charge of China’s online surveillance and stability maintenance. With such a patron behind him,. and a system ruled by men, not law,. where the Party decides everything,. you can imagine that. almost no one could touch Xin Qi. Princelings in China can indeed act with impunity. Even if he treats the entertainment world like a brothel,. it wouldn’t be unheard of. But Xin Qi initially adored Yu,. approaching him under the pretext of organizing a fan club,. with the real aim of getting close and monitoring him. After getting familiar with Yu,. he registered two companies in Yu’s name,. using both carrot and stick. to make Yu sign contracts. Once the partnership was bound,. Xin tried to impose the casting-couch rules on him. But Yu had boundaries,. and still refused at all costs. Yet given Xin’s backing,. Yu had no real recourse against him,. essentially with nowhere to turn. In this desperate moment,. Yu happened to discover. that the two companies in his name. were being used by the other side for money laundering—. acting as a white glove for the CCP. So Yu quietly gathered evidence,. and once he had key proof,. he went to deregister the companies. and stored the evidence on a USB drive. Presumably, Yu intended to use this as leverage. to free himself from Xin’s years of harassment. But because he held evidence of a senior CCP official’s laundering,. he touched the Party’s interests,. and in China’s system of official protectionism,. with Yu still physically inside the Great Firewall,. it instead brought fatal danger upon him. That earlier SOS clip you saw. wasn’t captured by chance,. but because Xin planned a setup against Yu. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">and brought in paparazzi to film. Xin originally wanted to use a sex scandal as leverage,. but it ended up accidentally capturing. footage of Yu pleading for help while alive. After this news broke inside China,. it’s easy to imagine. the CCP’s opinion-control machinery kicked in at once:. mass deletions on Weibo, Xiaohongshu, Douyin, and more. From trending #1 to vanishing into thin air—. Yu was thus erased from public view. Worse still, there’s more:. Yu’s studio. issued yet another statement to whitewash,. this time invoking Yu’s mother’s name,. aiming to quell netizens’ doubts,. claiming he fell accidentally while drunk,. and asking everyone to stop speculating. But once that statement came out,. Yu’s mother herself. apparently did not accept it. The very next day,. Yu Menglong’s mother anonymously posted online herself,. attaching a fingerprinted handprint to prove it was really her. She stayed anonymous because. the CCP had already banned discussion of Yu’s cause of death. But how could a mother who lost her own child. possibly remain silent? With grievance in her heart,. she chose to speak out under a pseudonym. She didn’t use Yu’s real name—. she called herself “Dou E’s mother.”. By the way,. “The Injustice to Dou E” is a Yuan-dynasty zaju by Guan Hanqing,. about a kind woman who was framed,. tortured and forced into a confession. Because both are injustices,. she used “Dou E” as a stand-in. The gist of Yu’s mother’s statement was:. I hope to seek justice for my child who died wronged. The killer’s claim to the public that it was an accident. is false. I hold key footage from before and after the incident,. plus testimony from insiders,. enough to prove it wasn’t an accident. but a deliberate assault. Since my child passed,. I have run around seeking help many times,. yet the killer still walks free. and is even suppressing the truth. My child was once so sunny and kind—. he should not have died bearing injustice,. nor should the killer dismiss his life. with the word “accident.”. I earnestly ask every conscientious compatriot:. if you know any clues from before or after my son’s incident,. if you are willing to speak for justice,. please help forward this petition of grievance,. so more people can know the truth,. return justice to my son,. and justice to this world. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I stand by every word I say. That’s roughly the current progress of Yu’s case. My first thought when looking at this was:. even someone like him—. a male star with 20 million followers inside the Firewall,. under intense public attention—. could be persecuted to death like this. All the more so for ordinary Chinese people. Famous or not,. as long as you’re under CCP rule,. in the eyes of senior cadres,. you and I are no different from “chives.”. Among my viewers. are some little pinks who scale the Firewall to watch. I hope these little pinks. can recognize one thing:. the “great motherland” you praise all day,. the GDP you boast about,. the city high-rises—. none of that is the point,. and none of it is yours. Because in the Party’s eyes,. we’re not people—. we’re just “human ore” to be mined. Those who oppose the CCP. don’t hate it because of skyscrapers,. but because under CCP rule,. people have no rights—. only the lives of high officials count. Even if you’re currently a vested beneficiary inside the Firewall,. with a job better than other “chives,”. it’s only temporary. Look at Yu’s past posts—. did he not love China? He wrote plenty. of patriotic articles. But once he caught the eye of a cadre’s child,. he still ended up with no remains. When the CCP’s iron fist. one day slams into your head,. aside from people like me,. the “rebels” you dislike so much,. there will truly be no one left to speak for you. And think about this:. an artist as famous as Yu inside China. could have all news completely blocked. It’s not hard to imagine. similar cases happen daily inside the Firewall—. unknown to anyone,. because others are even more nameless. So, little pinks, reflect:. while you help the CCP with external propaganda. and conduct cognitive warfare against Taiwan,. the more “successful” you are, the more you hurt yourselves. If your state becomes all-powerful,. no one will be able to save you. And in Taiwan, indeed quite a few people. no longer mind becoming China’s “chives.”. Some are bored of eating proper meals. and suddenly crave eating poop instead. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">What they see. is just the pink bubble you’ve blown up. But deep down you know better than anyone. that it’s fake. You’ve sung the March of the Volunteers so many times—. “Arise, you who refuse to be slaves.”. Was that all fake singing? If Chinese people had some guts,. I’m telling you honestly—. the whole world would help you overthrow the CCP. But if Chinese people willingly kneel as slaves,. then Yu Menglong won’t be the last. What do you all think about this case? Feel free to share below. And other viewers are also welcome. to add more details of Yu’s case. In the second half of today’s video,. let’s look at a few self-own comments on the channel. “Potter King represents the fence-sitters.”. Fence-sitters, huh? I’m a swing voter right now. That’s not fence-sitting—. that’s supporting Taiwan’s mainstream public opinion. But this isn’t the first time I’ve seen such comments. After I shifted my channel’s direction,. I do see these kinds of remarks occasionally. It makes me feel a lot. Is it that the Oscars owe me a statuette,. or that these netizens. truly lack logical thinking skills? They can’t even grasp the meaning of words. Even if you don’t understand what “swing voter” means,. you should at least understand this:. after I’ve walked you through the real China,. if after watching. you still think China is good,. and want to be invaded by the CCP to become Chinese,. then that just shows. you truly love China. In this life,. you’re destined to be the Party’s little chive. Loving it to a tragic end. If that’s really the majority view in Taiwan,. then I can only say it’s fate. And if you can’t understand this,. I suggest you stay off the internet. Seriously, please—. in this era of rampant disinformation,. you really shouldn’t be online. No wonder Taiwan’s losing the info war so badly—. there’s a reason. It reminds me of how some people. couldn’t even tell Bit King, who never shows his face,. from Potter King, who does. I was speechless. But as I said,. scolding won’t help. We can only keep playing into the headwind. And actually, thinking of it another way, it’s fine—. the appearance of such people. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">reveals something very important:. that my pivot was necessary. The purpose of my pivot. was to make dialogue. break through the echo chamber. Now with comments like these appearing,. it shows I’ve succeeded. I’ll keep working hard—. please keep supporting me. There are many ways to love Taiwan—. everyone, keep fighting from your own positions. “Potter King is actually trans. I have evidence but I won’t say it. So Potter King, please post a video to prove it. Thanks. If you don’t dare, that proves you’re guilty.”. The logic of this comment. sounds like kids quarreling in grade school. Wait, no—. if I call you grade-schoolers,. real kids might be offended,. saying, “We’re not that dumb!”. Let me analyze this little pink’s logic. for you all:. first he throws out an accusation,. saying the other person is trans,. then says he has evidence but won’t show it,. and shifts the responsibility back to the accused. He’s the one making the claim,. yet demands the other party film a video to clear themselves. This is a classic case of shifting the burden of proof:. offering no evidence himself,. but requiring others to prove innocence. It’s pure logical fallacy,. with no content and no credibility. Then he adds one more jab:. “If you don’t dare to film, that means you’re guilty.”. Basically he set up a sure-win condition—. no matter how the other side responds,. he can twist it his way. Shameless. But good for self-entertainment. So with this little pink example,. I’ll respond the same way once. Then you’ll know how to reply to these dumb pinks in the future. Here’s how:. I have proof you’re brainless—. but I won’t say it. Please film yourself,. open up your skull,. and prove you have a brain. Ah, if you don’t dare film it,. that means you’re guilty. Proves I was right—. you really are brainless. “Potter King saw Kuan Chang,. now he’s anxious because he can’t lick red money. Mom, love me once more.”. I’m not jealous of Kuan Chang. But since you mention him,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I recall Kuan Chang said himself—. he licked the CCP at his own expense and lost money. And there’s also this recent video of Chinese netizens’ comments on Kuan Chang. I can only say—. pathetic. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8</a></p><p>點擊優惠連結👉<a href="https://surfshark.com/potterking">https://surfshark.com/potterking</a> </p><p>或用優惠碼 [potterking] 以獲得額外 4 個月 Surfshark 服務！</p><p></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>于朦朧冤案！于朦朧母親心痛發聲！還我兒公道！</p><p>中共紅二代潛規則中國男影星！</p><p>此人靠山是習總親信蔡奇！專門網路維穩！</p><p>粉紅特報145期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]>
      </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<hr style="clear:both" />

<p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; "><p><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/AlCiC5fdWt8/maxresdefault.jpg" /></p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8</a></p><h1>值得閱讀的理由</h1><ul><li>深入了解中國<strong>娛樂圈的權力腐敗</strong>與明星<strong>被壓迫的悲慘現況</strong>。</li><li>揭示中國共產黨(CCP)如何利用<strong>「太子黨」</strong>背景的權貴，對異議或不順從者進行<strong>殘酷打壓與全面封鎖消息</strong>。</li><li>警示<strong>「防火牆內」</strong>的普通民眾，無論身份高低，在中共統治下都可能淪為<strong>「韭菜」</strong>，個人權益與生命安全毫無保障。</li></ul><hr /><h1>摘要</h1><h2>影片引言與案情概述</h2><p>影片的說書人，又名Potter King，開宗明義指出此影片將探討中國男星<strong>于孟龍</strong>的悲慘遭遇。最初，說書人並不熟悉于孟龍，但因眾多觀眾請求，他深入調查此案。他強調這不僅是又一起<strong>「中共韭菜」</strong>的悲劇，更充滿疑點，旨在讓觀眾一窺「防火牆內」作為中國人的真實生活。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_0.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>事件的開端與疑點</h2><p>于孟龍案始於9月11日下午1時59分，中國狗仔隊爆料他墜樓身亡。消息迅速傳開，現場照片顯示窗戶螢幕有奇特的破損。同日下午，于孟龍工作室發布聲明，確認他去世，並稱警方已排除刑事嫌疑，將此案定調為「意外墜樓」。然而，此舉引發軒然大波，<strong>一個擁有2000萬粉絲的男星離奇死亡，官方急於撇清刑事責任，顯得疑點重重</strong>。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_90.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>揭露殘酷真相與求救影片</h2><p>隨著事件發酵，內部人士爆料于孟龍並非意外墜樓，而是<strong>被活生生從樓上拋下兩次</strong>，手段極其殘忍。影片中更驚人地播放了一段據稱是案發前一晚秘密錄製的影片。畫面昏暗，但清晰可聞于孟龍因懼高症在五樓窗外被倒吊時<strong>心碎的求救聲</strong>。此影片不僅是受害者被虐待的真實畫面，也被說書人視為為受害者保留的證據，盼有朝一日沉冤得雪。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_160.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>背後的權勢與威脅</h2><p>說書人進一步揭露，于孟龍的悲劇早有伏筆。他自25歲出道以來，就屢次因拒絕「潛規則」而遭受權勢打壓，甚至被<strong>封殺三年</strong>。2017年事業剛有起色，又被影視製作人<strong>辛奇（辛曉雄）</strong>盯上。辛奇的真實身份被指為中共政治局常委<strong>蔡奇的私生子</strong>，擁有<strong>「太子黨」</strong>背景。蔡奇身為習近平親信，負責網路監控與維穩，導致辛奇在「防火牆內」幾乎<strong>橫行無忌，無人能動</strong>。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_250.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>金錢交易與致命證據</h2><p>辛奇以成立粉絲俱樂部為藉口接近于孟龍，隨後利用威脅利誘的手段，以于孟龍的名義註冊了兩家公司，強迫他簽訂合約。合作綁定後，辛奇試圖強行施加「潛規則」，但于孟龍堅決拒絕。在絕望中，于孟龍意外發現這兩家公司被辛奇用於<strong>洗錢</strong>，為中共充當「白手套」。于孟龍暗中收集證據，並將關鍵證據儲存在隨身碟中，原欲以此擺脫辛奇的騷擾。然而，觸及中共高層利益的證據反而將他推向致命危機。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_360.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>官方壓制與母親的控訴</h2><p>于孟龍墜樓消息傳出後，中共迅速啟動輿論管控，<strong>大量刪除微博、小紅書、抖音等平臺的相關討論</strong>，于孟龍在公眾視野中被<strong>「抹去」</strong>。更甚者，于孟龍工作室再次發布聲明「洗白」，以于孟龍母親的名義，聲稱是醉酒意外墜樓，試圖平息輿論。然而，于孟龍母親本人並不接受此說法，匿名在網路上發文，以<strong>「竇娥之母」</strong>自稱，用帶指紋的手印證明身份。她哭訴兒子枉死，握有事發前後的關鍵影像與內部證詞，足以證明並非意外，而是<strong>蓄意加害</strong>，懇請世人為她兒子討回公道。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_450.jpg" /></p><hr /><h2>作者的省思與警示</h2><p>說書人總結此案，感嘆連擁有2000萬粉絲的明星，在中共統治下也難逃迫害致死的命運，更遑論普通民眾。他警告所有在中共統治下的國民，無論是否有名，在中共高官眼中都只是<strong>「韭菜」</strong>，是可供開採的<strong>「人礦」</strong>。說書人希望那些翻牆出來的<strong>「小粉紅」</strong>能看清，所謂「偉大祖國」的GDP和高樓大廈，都不是屬於人民的，因為在黨的眼中，人民並非「人」，而只是被利用的資源。</p><p><img src="https://democwise2016.github.io/action-RSS-UT-Weekly-202501/file-cache/AlCiC5fdWt8_540.jpg" /></p><hr /><hr />================================================</p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Hello everyone, welcome back to this week’s Pink News. I’m your intern mentor for being Chinese.（false flag）. AKA the swing voter. Potter King. Some wanted to hear Potter King’s take on the Yu Menglong case. I’m not a fan of Yu. But hearing the news was heartbreaking. Hello, Potter King. Could you talk about the Yu Menglong incident in China’s entertainment industry? This matter may involve many celebrities or high-ranking officials. It has already been suppressed inside China. I hope you can help more people pay attention to it. This week I’ve received several such comments. Hoping I would talk about Yu Menglong’s case. But beforehand I wasn’t familiar with this Chinese star. Nor had I seen any of his dramas. But since so many wanted me to talk about it,. I went to research the case. And after understanding what he went through,. I can only say it’s another tragedy of the CCP’s chives. And I do think this case is full of suspicious points. But just now,. many Taiwanese have accepted CCP propaganda. They think being Chinese. seems pretty good. So in this week’s video,. we’ll learn about Yu Menglong’s ordeal. to get a taste of life as a Chinese inside the Great Firewall. After a one-minute ad,. we’ll get right into today’s topic. First I must say,. this case is hard to explain fully. Because the CCP inside China. has already been maintaining stability on it. A lot of the information is fragmented. I can only piece it together in order. If there are parts I didn’t mention,. I welcome informed viewers. to add them in the comments. OK, let me quickly explain. what exactly happened. It started on September 11 at 1:59 p.m. when a paparazzi inside China posted on Weibo. saying Yu Menglong had fallen to his death. At first the news wasn’t confirmed as true or false. The post only had text plus a few photos from the scene. He said he had confirmed with staff. that the one who fell was Yu Menglong. And in one of the photos,. there was a close-up of the window screen where it happened. At first Chinese netizens. could still discuss how weirdly the screen was broken. They questioned who would cut it open and then jump. The incident site was a luxury apartment project in Chaoyang, Beijing. The Sunshine Upper East community. Later that afternoon,. Yu Menglong’s studio released a statement. confirming his death from falling. He was 37. Still very young. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">Although this confirmed. the paparazzi’s report was correct,. what’s strange is. Yu Menglong’s studio replaced the police to announce. that the police had ruled out criminal suspicion. Clearly wanting to frame the case as an accidental fall. But Yu Menglong, as. a male star with 20 million fans in China,. suddenly died like this—. it naturally drew huge attention. It even shot up to number one on Weibo’s trending. And that’s when insiders began revealing. that Yu Menglong didn’t fall by accident,. but was thrown off. And not just once. He was thrown twice. The method was extremely cruel. There was even a video. directly filming the window of the crime scene,. the same one in the leaked photos we saw. But the video. was secretly filmed the night before. So the footage is dark. But you can still clearly hear. Yu Menglong’s heart-wrenching cries for help. With his fear of heights,. he was hung upside down outside a 5th-floor window and toyed with. A reminder—the next clip. may make people uncomfortable. It’s real footage of persecution. If you’re especially empathetic,. consider muting the sound. and just reading the subtitles. Even though this might get yellow-tagged,. I think it’s necessary to show it. Because this video has already been censored inside China. So by posting it here,. I’m also preserving evidence for the victim. Hoping one day his injustice will be redressed. In addition, reports also pointed out that on the night of his fall... There were multiple people at the scene,. including well-known figures from China’s entertainment industry. It’s said Yu Menglong was set up at a gathering that night,. drugged and plied with alcohol,. and then forced to have relations with a man. Afterward, the other party tossed him two Rolex watches,. trying to buy him off. I’ve also reviewed many related materials. and compiled a few key points to share. Yu was targeted when he debuted at 25. Rumor had it a powerful woman in the industry tried to coerce him,. but he refused,. and was blacklisted for three years,. disappearing from public view,. with no job opportunities. By 2017,. he finally landed work again,. appearing in “Eternal Love” (Three Lives, Three Worlds, Ten Miles of Peach Blossoms). As his career began to recover,. he was targeted by someone else,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">who tried to force the unspoken rules on him. That person was later identified. as Xin Qi,. birth name Xin Xiaoxiong,. a film producer. You might ask, can a Chinese film producer. really wield such power over an artist? Perhaps not,. but Xin Qi. isn’t an ordinary producer—. he’s a princeling, the child of a senior CCP official. According to news reports,. Xin Qi is suspected to be. the illegitimate son of Politburo Standing Committee member Cai Qi. With that princeling background,. his backing inside the Great Firewall is extremely strong. Moreover, Cai Qi. is a Xi loyalist who has been heavily favored,. in charge of China’s online surveillance and stability maintenance. With such a patron behind him,. and a system ruled by men, not law,. where the Party decides everything,. you can imagine that. almost no one could touch Xin Qi. Princelings in China can indeed act with impunity. Even if he treats the entertainment world like a brothel,. it wouldn’t be unheard of. But Xin Qi initially adored Yu,. approaching him under the pretext of organizing a fan club,. with the real aim of getting close and monitoring him. After getting familiar with Yu,. he registered two companies in Yu’s name,. using both carrot and stick. to make Yu sign contracts. Once the partnership was bound,. Xin tried to impose the casting-couch rules on him. But Yu had boundaries,. and still refused at all costs. Yet given Xin’s backing,. Yu had no real recourse against him,. essentially with nowhere to turn. In this desperate moment,. Yu happened to discover. that the two companies in his name. were being used by the other side for money laundering—. acting as a white glove for the CCP. So Yu quietly gathered evidence,. and once he had key proof,. he went to deregister the companies. and stored the evidence on a USB drive. Presumably, Yu intended to use this as leverage. to free himself from Xin’s years of harassment. But because he held evidence of a senior CCP official’s laundering,. he touched the Party’s interests,. and in China’s system of official protectionism,. with Yu still physically inside the Great Firewall,. it instead brought fatal danger upon him. That earlier SOS clip you saw. wasn’t captured by chance,. but because Xin planned a setup against Yu. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">and brought in paparazzi to film. Xin originally wanted to use a sex scandal as leverage,. but it ended up accidentally capturing. footage of Yu pleading for help while alive. After this news broke inside China,. it’s easy to imagine. the CCP’s opinion-control machinery kicked in at once:. mass deletions on Weibo, Xiaohongshu, Douyin, and more. From trending #1 to vanishing into thin air—. Yu was thus erased from public view. Worse still, there’s more:. Yu’s studio. issued yet another statement to whitewash,. this time invoking Yu’s mother’s name,. aiming to quell netizens’ doubts,. claiming he fell accidentally while drunk,. and asking everyone to stop speculating. But once that statement came out,. Yu’s mother herself. apparently did not accept it. The very next day,. Yu Menglong’s mother anonymously posted online herself,. attaching a fingerprinted handprint to prove it was really her. She stayed anonymous because. the CCP had already banned discussion of Yu’s cause of death. But how could a mother who lost her own child. possibly remain silent? With grievance in her heart,. she chose to speak out under a pseudonym. She didn’t use Yu’s real name—. she called herself “Dou E’s mother.”. By the way,. “The Injustice to Dou E” is a Yuan-dynasty zaju by Guan Hanqing,. about a kind woman who was framed,. tortured and forced into a confession. Because both are injustices,. she used “Dou E” as a stand-in. The gist of Yu’s mother’s statement was:. I hope to seek justice for my child who died wronged. The killer’s claim to the public that it was an accident. is false. I hold key footage from before and after the incident,. plus testimony from insiders,. enough to prove it wasn’t an accident. but a deliberate assault. Since my child passed,. I have run around seeking help many times,. yet the killer still walks free. and is even suppressing the truth. My child was once so sunny and kind—. he should not have died bearing injustice,. nor should the killer dismiss his life. with the word “accident.”. I earnestly ask every conscientious compatriot:. if you know any clues from before or after my son’s incident,. if you are willing to speak for justice,. please help forward this petition of grievance,. so more people can know the truth,. return justice to my son,. and justice to this world. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I stand by every word I say. That’s roughly the current progress of Yu’s case. My first thought when looking at this was:. even someone like him—. a male star with 20 million followers inside the Firewall,. under intense public attention—. could be persecuted to death like this. All the more so for ordinary Chinese people. Famous or not,. as long as you’re under CCP rule,. in the eyes of senior cadres,. you and I are no different from “chives.”. Among my viewers. are some little pinks who scale the Firewall to watch. I hope these little pinks. can recognize one thing:. the “great motherland” you praise all day,. the GDP you boast about,. the city high-rises—. none of that is the point,. and none of it is yours. Because in the Party’s eyes,. we’re not people—. we’re just “human ore” to be mined. Those who oppose the CCP. don’t hate it because of skyscrapers,. but because under CCP rule,. people have no rights—. only the lives of high officials count. Even if you’re currently a vested beneficiary inside the Firewall,. with a job better than other “chives,”. it’s only temporary. Look at Yu’s past posts—. did he not love China? He wrote plenty. of patriotic articles. But once he caught the eye of a cadre’s child,. he still ended up with no remains. When the CCP’s iron fist. one day slams into your head,. aside from people like me,. the “rebels” you dislike so much,. there will truly be no one left to speak for you. And think about this:. an artist as famous as Yu inside China. could have all news completely blocked. It’s not hard to imagine. similar cases happen daily inside the Firewall—. unknown to anyone,. because others are even more nameless. So, little pinks, reflect:. while you help the CCP with external propaganda. and conduct cognitive warfare against Taiwan,. the more “successful” you are, the more you hurt yourselves. If your state becomes all-powerful,. no one will be able to save you. And in Taiwan, indeed quite a few people. no longer mind becoming China’s “chives.”. Some are bored of eating proper meals. and suddenly crave eating poop instead. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">What they see. is just the pink bubble you’ve blown up. But deep down you know better than anyone. that it’s fake. You’ve sung the March of the Volunteers so many times—. “Arise, you who refuse to be slaves.”. Was that all fake singing? If Chinese people had some guts,. I’m telling you honestly—. the whole world would help you overthrow the CCP. But if Chinese people willingly kneel as slaves,. then Yu Menglong won’t be the last. What do you all think about this case? Feel free to share below. And other viewers are also welcome. to add more details of Yu’s case. In the second half of today’s video,. let’s look at a few self-own comments on the channel. “Potter King represents the fence-sitters.”. Fence-sitters, huh? I’m a swing voter right now. That’s not fence-sitting—. that’s supporting Taiwan’s mainstream public opinion. But this isn’t the first time I’ve seen such comments. After I shifted my channel’s direction,. I do see these kinds of remarks occasionally. It makes me feel a lot. Is it that the Oscars owe me a statuette,. or that these netizens. truly lack logical thinking skills? They can’t even grasp the meaning of words. Even if you don’t understand what “swing voter” means,. you should at least understand this:. after I’ve walked you through the real China,. if after watching. you still think China is good,. and want to be invaded by the CCP to become Chinese,. then that just shows. you truly love China. In this life,. you’re destined to be the Party’s little chive. Loving it to a tragic end. If that’s really the majority view in Taiwan,. then I can only say it’s fate. And if you can’t understand this,. I suggest you stay off the internet. Seriously, please—. in this era of rampant disinformation,. you really shouldn’t be online. No wonder Taiwan’s losing the info war so badly—. there’s a reason. It reminds me of how some people. couldn’t even tell Bit King, who never shows his face,. from Potter King, who does. I was speechless. But as I said,. scolding won’t help. We can only keep playing into the headwind. And actually, thinking of it another way, it’s fine—. the appearance of such people. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">reveals something very important:. that my pivot was necessary. The purpose of my pivot. was to make dialogue. break through the echo chamber. Now with comments like these appearing,. it shows I’ve succeeded. I’ll keep working hard—. please keep supporting me. There are many ways to love Taiwan—. everyone, keep fighting from your own positions. “Potter King is actually trans. I have evidence but I won’t say it. So Potter King, please post a video to prove it. Thanks. If you don’t dare, that proves you’re guilty.”. The logic of this comment. sounds like kids quarreling in grade school. Wait, no—. if I call you grade-schoolers,. real kids might be offended,. saying, “We’re not that dumb!”. Let me analyze this little pink’s logic. for you all:. first he throws out an accusation,. saying the other person is trans,. then says he has evidence but won’t show it,. and shifts the responsibility back to the accused. He’s the one making the claim,. yet demands the other party film a video to clear themselves. This is a classic case of shifting the burden of proof:. offering no evidence himself,. but requiring others to prove innocence. It’s pure logical fallacy,. with no content and no credibility. Then he adds one more jab:. “If you don’t dare to film, that means you’re guilty.”. Basically he set up a sure-win condition—. no matter how the other side responds,. he can twist it his way. Shameless. But good for self-entertainment. So with this little pink example,. I’ll respond the same way once. Then you’ll know how to reply to these dumb pinks in the future. Here’s how:. I have proof you’re brainless—. but I won’t say it. Please film yourself,. open up your skull,. and prove you have a brain. Ah, if you don’t dare film it,. that means you’re guilty. Proves I was right—. you really are brainless. “Potter King saw Kuan Chang,. now he’s anxious because he can’t lick red money. Mom, love me once more.”. I’m not jealous of Kuan Chang. But since you mention him,. </p><p style="max-width: calc(100vw - 1rem);  word-wrap: break-word; overflow-wrap: break-word; ">I recall Kuan Chang said himself—. he licked the CCP at his own expense and lost money. And there’s also this recent video of Chinese netizens’ comments on Kuan Chang. I can only say—. pathetic. </p>

<hr style="clear:both" />
=============
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlCiC5fdWt8</a></p><p>點擊優惠連結👉<a href="https://surfshark.com/potterking">https://surfshark.com/potterking</a> </p><p>或用優惠碼 [potterking] 以獲得額外 4 個月 Surfshark 服務！</p><p></p><p>點連結成為我的Youtube頻道會員：<a href="https://goo.gl/MFNUKr">https://goo.gl/MFNUKr</a></p><p></p><p>于朦朧冤案！于朦朧母親心痛發聲！還我兒公道！</p><p>中共紅二代潛規則中國男影星！</p><p>此人靠山是習總親信蔡奇！專門網路維穩！</p><p>粉紅特報145期</p><p></p><p>追蹤我IG：</p><p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/">https://www.instagram.com/potterking712/</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我Threads：</p><p><a href="https://www.threads.net/@potterking712">https://www.threads.net/@potterking712</a></p><p></p><p>追蹤我臉書粉專：</p><p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking">https://www.facebook.com/Realpotterking</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/AlCiC5fdWt8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <pubDate>2025-09-20T11:50:06.000Z</pubDate>
    </item></channel>
</rss>